My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Say it out loud, you love Takehiko Henmi!
So you admitted this girl, Misonoo Nanako, into the Sorority.
You wanted her to worship you so much that she would leave Henmi!
I, Misonoo Nanako, first year, section B...
...for certain personal reasons, hereby resign from the Sorority.
26. The Promise in the Snow
What's going on?
What?
You're not speaking to me today?
It's not like that.
It is like that!
I said "good morning" and you just mumbled.
Did I?
What happened?
Eh?
Last night at the Sorority house!
What happened with Miya-sama?
Listen!
My brother...
I can't tell Mariko-san...
...about what happened with Miya-sama
...or with Saint-Juste-sama...
or that I have written a letter of resignation.
Hi, Misonoo-san.
I need to speak to Miya-sama.
She has a cold. She's resting at her summer place.
...her summer place?
That summer place...
Have you seen Rei, today?
I've been looking for her since yesterday.
Well, I...
We have an exhibition game tonight.
I'd asked her to lend a hand, but I guess she won't make it.
Could you remind her if you see her?
Tell her it's at the auditorium at 7.
Ok...
Thanks!
Yes, that's right my Brother.
The one suffering the most from all this,
...might actually be Saint-Juste-sama.
She, who has eyes only for Miya-sama,
...now knows that Miya-sama is in love with someone else.
Saint-Juste-sama.
My mother had just died,
...and your family was about to adopt me.
Around that time, you took a trip to the north.
You told me that you had a sudden desire to see the snow.
But I knew perfectly well the real reason for the trip.
Those fiercely proud eyes of yours,
...they told me the real story.
Long ago, when I was a child...
...I collected glass miniatures.
Glass has such purity, such clarity...
Delicate and glowing... I love them!
But one day one of the maids was cleaning,
...and carelessly broke one of the pieces I had on the shelf.
I immediately smashed all the rest!
With my own hands!
Your own hands?
Yes, I had to. Otherwise, someone might have broken another.
No one can break or defile the things I cherish.
They can't. I'll never allow it! It would be unforgivable.
But for us, it's still not too late.
It's not too late to seal our beautiful time forever.
No one will ever desecrate it.
Do you understand, Rei?
Yes.
I knew you would...
I understand, completely.
I'll be joining you. Soon.
Yes. Soon.
Oh, you're there!
You're there, aren't you, Saint-Juste-sama?
Hello? I'm coming right over.
What kind of soup do you want?
Vegetable? Chicken? My Chinese soup is good, too!
So, my Brother... I thought I'd cook something for her.
It's the only thing I can do for her.
If she falls asleep, or won't talk, it's okay.
Even if she won't so much as smile... it's okay.
Why is it you are seeing Rei today?
I... thought she'd like some soup...
That's very nice of you.
But it's not necessary. She doesn't need anything.
She doesn't need anything. Go on back home.
Miya-sama!
I won't go home! I won't go home!
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to go home.
I... here...
It's my resignation.
I'm crushed...
It hurts that you misunderstood me so!
I'm only exchanging letters with my Brother! That's all!
I'll look in on that girl myself.
Go on now. Back home.
But I know her!
I know how cold her room is!
How she's always alone, and never eats...
So, I said I'd be with her, go home!
That's not true! You never do anything for Saint-Juste-sama!
Choose your words with care.
I am her sister.
I'm not going home!
Rei!
Saint-Juste-sama!
I was waiting.
I thought you would join me. I waited for you.
I believed that you would join me soon.
I was there waiting for you.
The cold of the snow was so comforting.
As I was losing consciousness,
...I felt that you were there watching over me.
The snow's coldness was soon replaced with warmth, softness...
...and I drifted into a flowering springtime.
Yes, I knew my body temperature was falling,
...my consciousness began to fade,
...and I remember nothing more.
When I woke up, I was in a hospital bed.
And there you were... you were at my bedside.
You tilted your head and looked at me intently.
On the other side of the window, it was still snowing.
I can still remember the sound of the falling snow...
Koto koto...
Koton koton...
Koton...
Listen here, fellow.
It's an import. So, how about 25,000 yen?
Hey, I'll give you a discount even.
Lets see your wallet... what?
Huh? What is it?
This guy is...
Damn! Wait!
Come back here, dammit!
Come back!
You're gonna get it now!
Some time passed, and you came to see me.
It turned out I wasn't to be living with the family.
Instead, I'd be alone in an apartment.
So you paid me a visit there.
Here, I'd like to give you this.
I can't live with you here,
...but take this doll in my place, to remind you.
And one more thing...
Someday, I will honor my promise, and try again with you.
Take this bracelet as a token of my promise.
Until then, will you wait for me?
Yes, I'll wait.
Stop here.
It's sad, isn't it, how you and I ended up being such wonderful sisters.
And it's so sad that we have different mothers.
The more we come to like each others, the more it disturbs me.
It's all unforgivable.
So before sadness overtakes us... before it's too late for us...
Yes, Fukiko-sama!
I want to see the snow.
It was you who first said it,
"Let's just end it all."
But then... after all that... you didn't join me.
Help! Help me, someone!
Someone help me! It's my sister!
I've been looking for you, Rei.
You're hurt... because you think I'm in love with someone else.
But it's not true. There is nothing between him and me.
He means nothing to me.
You are the only one who matters to me.
Really. Please believe me.
Lies! Those are all lies!
In the snow when you said "let's die", it wasn't for us.
It was because he hurt you so badly,
...you had to drag me into your pain!
No! That wasn't it!
It was only for you and me! No one else!
I have eyes only for you. You alone!
But I don't want to see you the way you are now.
I have to stay away from you so I don't see how you really are!
I'll show you proof.
This time, I'll go first.
Then you can follow me.
Or... shall we go both at once?
Yes. That would be best.
This time.
We'll fly like birds, and in that brief moment,
...I'll trust you a hundred times... a thousand times... more than now.
Come on...
Let's stop. That's enough.
It's true. I saw your proof!
No more! That's enough!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Welcome home!
Have some chicken stew, with lots of vegetables.
I looked all over for you. But I knew you'd come back here.
I thought you would. I was sure of it.
I thought you'd want something to eat.
I'll leave now.
Could you die?
If someone you loved asked you to die with them,
...could you do it?
Could you die?
I...
I've never thought about it!
Absolutely never!
I couldn't! Never!
How could I... No!
That's... No! No, no!
No!
That's mustn't happen! Don't!
Don't do it!
Thank you.
My dear Brother...
A week passed, then something else happened.
Nanako-san, Shinobu-san is here.
Wow, Mariko-san! Hello!
I came over!
I came here to stay overnight.
Can I stay over, in your room?
I suppose it's okay, but...
Oh good... don't worry, just one night, okay?
Please don't ask me why...
Well... what about your parents?
I asked them already. Sorry for the intrusion. Thank you.
Wow, great! Your bed is softer than mine!
Really?
Light out?
Sure!
Good night. Good night.
Sorry I didn't call.
It's okay.
Mariko-san?
Mariko-san!
Nanako-san!
My brother... It's about Mariko-san. She is...
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...