My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Is that her?
Yeah. Misonoo Nanako!
She looks so plain!
It's just not fair.
Look!
She's so clumsy!
She trips so elegently.
She is no good at all!
Really!
Serves her right!
Nanako-san!
Miya-sama...!
Here...
Thank you very much...
Don't become discouraged.
Miya-sama is truly great. Such majesty!
Who were the ones bad mouthing you?
Say, Misonoo-san, what did Miya-sama say just then?
What? Nothing...
6. Lost and Alone
Nanako, what time was it on Sunday?
What?
What? You'll be baking a cake with Tomoko?
Oh! That... well, we may postpone it...
But you were looking forward to it so...
There's an English quiz next week... and we are both busy with our clubs...
Thank you.
Are you enjoying school?
Of course!
I see.
Our usually talkative Nanako doesn't say much about her school lately...
Don't worry! I'm enjoying it a lot.
It's so different from Junior High.
You're a liar!
I hate it.
I've been slandered by people I don't even know.
How can I say such a thing?
Really.
Brother, dear brother...
I cannot write a letter now.
I wonder if I could possibly meet you some day.
We have to assemble at the gymnasium because of the rain.
I'd hoped the class was canceled.
Instead there is strength-testing today!
So, let's go!
What's the matter?
My bag is gone.
What?
It has my gym clothes.
I'm sure I left it here this morning.
Hey, daughter of a rat dog!
Shinobu-san!
What do you want, pornographer's daughter!
Hand back her gym bag!
You must have hidden it!
Don't... Mariko-san...
Stop with the nonsense.
Why would I want to do such a thing?
Yes, you must have left it somewhere.
Right, you're getting absent-minded due to being chosen as a Sorority member.
Guess so!
Dear me!
For sure!
Wait a minute!
Stop! Let them go.
You can't accuse her. There is no evidence.
But...
It's ok, I can borrow gym clothes from a friend.
A friend? Tomoko-san?
Yes.
So you can go on ahead. To the gym.
But will she lend you her gym clothes?
What?
She seems to be avoiding you lately.
Did you two... have a quarrel?
Don't worry! She'll help me out.
Bye!
Tomoko!
Finally we can talk! I've been worrying...
When I called you last night. I was told you were already asleep.
What do you want?
What?
Is there something you want from me?
I believe you called out to me.
Um... I...
I was wondering if I could borrow your gym clothes.
My gym clothes aren't good enough.
They wouldn't be appropriate for a Sorority member.
Tomoko...
Since you are no longer the Nanako I knew.
perhaps someone else could loan you some gym clothes.
Tomoko!
Wait!
Excuse me!
Please sign this.
Please.
What for?
To expel Miss Misonoo from the Sorority due to her being chosen unfairly.
Please sign here.
Did you see her expression?
Why couldn't she have signed it herself? That would be great!
For sure!
Oh, hey... Arikura-san!
Weren't you in junior high school with Misonoo-san...?
Um... Yes...
How did she get chosen? You must know all her dirty tricks...?
Come on, tell me... please!
She has none.
What?
None. Not at all.
But...
Absolutely none!
I know Nanako and her family very well! They don't use dirty tricks!
Well I never!
You didn't have to make such a fuss about it!
What's happened to you, Tomoko!
You hate me just because I was chosen as a Sorority member!?
You fool!
Good. Tomoko refused. I knew she would.
Misonoo-san! Misonoo-san!
You couldn't get them? Why? Why not?
No...
She didn't bring hers today.
Ok, then come on!
I can borrow them from a big sister for you. Let's go.
Come on!
What are you doing here?
Class is starting!
You see...
...I've lost my gym clothes...
We are going to borrow some from...
You can use mine.
Oh!
But what about you then?
No problem, I'm leaving early today.
I'm off to the hospital to have some follow-up tests done.
I may look healthy but I'm still recovering.
These might be big for you...
Thank you very much!
Thank you...
so very much...
They had a certain sweet and clean smell...
...with the crisp touch of Biyakudan.
I found myself entirely encircled by Kaoru-no-Kimi...
All that morning, I felt I had the ability to keep on going.
In the afternoon, the rain stopped,
and my only remaining class was English.
I planned on going home early and washing Kaoru-no-Kimi's gym clothes.
I was feeling much better...
...and I started feeling a little bit happier too.
I decided to buy a notebook before class.
Here, twenty yen.
Thanks.
Just a second, Miss.
Aren't you Miss Misonoo, a freshmen, section B?
Yes.
We are sophomores.
We'd like to speak to you a moment.
I'm sorry, I should probably get back right away.
My class is about to start.
Hold it! It would be wise to obey us while we're still reasonable.
What?!
Get over here!
This won't take long.
Unless you don't pay attention, that is!
Resign from the Sorority.
Resign, of your own volition.
You understand why, don't you...?
You didn't even attend the party.
You shouldn't have been chosen.
We won't permit such an injustice.
Injustice?!
There is no injustice!
If it's not an injustice, how could it have happened?
I don't know how it happened!
Damn you!
Take it easy! Hey!
We, too, once were candidates for the Sorority.
We faced the selection process fairly...
...but were not chosen.
But still...
...still we have our pride!
Follow your conscience. Think on it.
Brother...
...Dear Brother, I...
I looked into those eyes and saw hearts filled with hatred and anger,
and despair, jealousy... even sorrow, such as I've never seen before.
I fear that someday I could become like her.
You're kidding! Surely you're not serious!
I'm serious.
But Nanako, that's crazy!
You can't leave the Sorority! You can't!
I've already made my decision.
I will ask Miya-sama to let me leave tomorrow morning.
In the past, members have been disowned,
...but no one in their right mind has left willingly!
You absolutely can't! Nanako-san!
Here it is. My sports bag.
So cruel.
I can't wait.
What?
I can't wait till tomorrow!
Nanako-san!
No!
Leaving the Sorority is utterly unthinkable.
If you quit, you would be giving in to the rumors and slander.
I will protect you from those people.
I will always be happy to extend my hand on your behalf.
So, don't quit now.
All right?
Are you enjoying school?
You plan to bake a cake with Tomoko...
What do you want?
What?
Is there something you want from me?
I believe you called out to me.
I was wondering if I could borrow your gym clothes.
My gym clothes aren't good enough.
They wouldn't be appropriate for a Sorority member.
I don't know how it happened!
Damn you!
Dad... Mom...
I don't like school at all.
Hey, is this ok? Here?
Yeah, I want to stop at the bookstore.
See you later...
Sure, later...
I'll take these.
Thank you!
I can't endure this anymore.
So, did you like it?
The music box?
No!
It's not...!
It can't be!
It just can't be true.
What's so unbelievable?
I... I was just thinking how I wished I could see you...
Well then! Perhaps it isn't true after all.
So what are you doing, out so late?
Oh! Well... um...
Never mind then.
Eventually you'll tell me in a letter...
Yes, I will!
Oh, good.
What?
Never mind...
Anyway, I'll send you home now.
It's rather late for a high school student to be out alone.
Great! Please do!
So what about tomorrow and the day after?
Well, well...
Sorry...!
Brother, I am fine.
No one hurts me.
No one hates me, or slanders me, or scoffs at me.
I don't hate anybody.
I am neither angry, nor jealous, nor crying over being slandered.
Nothing like that. My life is peaceful and happy.
If somehow you saw me crying, it must have been over something minor.
Anyway, I have been quite fine.
Because, whatever happens,
I still have my brother...
And also Tomoko... so I can't be unhappy.
Tomoko, my friend since childhood...
Tomoko!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako flees to the clock tower, trying to escape her tormentors...
...only to find it already occupied by Saint-Juste, and her mysterious smile.
Then Nanako sees that Saint-Juste is holding a handful of sharp knives...!
Next episode: The Darkness in the Clock Tower
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...