My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Sorry, I'm late...
It's okay. I'm used to it.
You're annoyed anyway, I can tell.
How's your thesis... half-done, maybe?
Silly question...
Another break from work, then...
Now?
Me too.
So?
So what did you do?
About what?
The Nyugaku-iwai, the high school gift... you sent it?
Yeah...
With your name on it?
Yes... They'll find out sooner or later....
Ever hear of Seiran Sorority?
Yeah... I've heard of it...
She was selected as a candidate.
What the heck does that mean?
Well, it's not that easy to explain...
Brother, to my surprise...
I was selected as a candidate!
3. Is Nanako Disqualified?
I collected some information about what the Sorority sisters dislike most.
Girls who cannot use keigo.
Girls who cannot dress and behave in a "classy" manner
and especially, girls who can't be punctual.
Who is it I can hear from so far away, ladies?
That's better.
Who is that?
It's her.
Is she the one?
She's the outsider who was chosen as a candidate!
I don't see anything special about her.
Not exceptionally pretty...
So, she must be the only daughter of a very rich family.
No, she's lower middle-class.
You're kidding. That makes no sense to me.
I can't figure it out either.
This is a narrow stairway.
We can't pass if you walk spread out like that.
By all means, go on, then...
Thank you. Nanako, let's go.
You must have used some kind of dirty trick.
Otherwise you'd never have been selected as a candidate.
What a nasty upstart she is!
Somehow she got chosen over you!
She must have some very sneaky way of cheating.
It would be even more mortifying if she is chosen as a member!
It's ok. She'll withdraw.
I finally got the goods on her.
What "goods"?
I found Nanako Misonoo's weakness. A truth she can't deny...
How did you find this out?
In my father's office,
there are many such secrets to be found.
That's right! Your father is a famous lawyer!
I wish I'd been born into the elite like you.
And you, the most elite of the elite...
How I hate her!
There's always some girl like her...
Feigning such innocence...
Who somehow steals what is rightfully mine!
Shut up!
Nanako, it's Tomoko.
What's up?
How are you?
Ok. I've been better. But I'm okay.
I see.
What is it? Anything urgent?
Nothing in particular. Just a meaningless good-night call,
So anyway good night!
Good night...
They say a rumor runs its course in 75 days.
75 more days, Nanako.
Bye! See you later!
Ok!
Good morning, Misonoo-san!
Good Morning!
Hey, listen, what did you decide to wear to the party tomorrow?
I'm still torn!
Between a black dress and a bright red one.
But yours has got to be pink. Especially powder pink.
What do you want?
Strange. They look at us even colder today.
What is that?
I'm dreading some sort of exam announcement...
What? An exam?
Good Morning!
Morning...
Beats me...
Sometimes they have unscheduled exams.
Well, it says...
We suspect there was cheating in the selection of the Sorority candidates,
...and this cheating led to the selection of Nanako Misonoo.
She doesn't have the looks and charm to qualify.
More importantly, she's not really the daughter of Professor Misonoo.
It's an injustice that such a person be selected as a candidate.
This is terrible!
Misonoo-san!
Tomoko! Tomoko!
Don't go!
Listen, I'm on your side!
Nanako-san!
Tomoko!
Nanako-san...
Move aside!
Move aside a moment...
This garbage belongs in a garbage can!
This is too much!
I'm sorry!
Are you... are you okay?
I'm so sorry... I...
Over there...
What?
Hand it here...
These pills?
Like a man...
...there's something about her almost like a man...
So cruel.
Who would do such a thing?
I decided...
I decided not to go to the party.
After such an incident... I just can't go.
You were... defeated.
Yes.
Yes. That means...
The winner is hate itself.
The winner.
Painful, isn't it?
Well, is it finally painful enough?
I know how much you respect and love your father!
Sure, you're not his real daughter...
...but I know how close you two are.
So this is torturing me as well!
This is a dirty thing they are doing to you, and an outrageous insult, Nanako!
Tomoko...
Go! Go to the party!
Not going because of this would just increase the pain.
But...
There's nothing to be ashamed of!
Nothing at all! You are innocent!
Go!
But damn. Not going was my final decision.
That's the decision you made.
I really wonder why I was selected.
I would have selected you, Nanako.
What!?
Right here!
Your real self.
The Sorority members saw into your heart!
Tomoko!
Don't... don't cry!
Misonoo-san!
Where have you been? I thought you might have gone home.
Sorry to make you worry.
It's okay.
Please don't say you won't attend...
Tomorrow's party...
I will...
I will attend.
My dear brother...
I confess... I must confess that...
There's been a lot happening and I've been thinking a lot.
When I decided to go, I somehow thought I might be accepted after all.
I don't have much confidence, nor any faith,
But I thought, wouldn't it be nice...
Wouldn't it be nice...
To see and experience the Big Sister's gorgeous life style.
I... I realized that I am somewhat vain, frivolous, and a social butterfly...
Despite its perhaps being wrong, I'm still so excited.
This feeling is new to me... completely new.
Nanako? Nanako-san?
Yes?
There was a phone call from Ichinomiya Fukiko.
From Miya-sama?
Yes, about tomorrow's Soro... Soro...
It's Sorority, Mom.
Yes, the Sorority party...
The time is changed to three o'clock. And she said "hello".
Three o'clock? okay. Thank you!
Nanako!
I'm stunned!
You really dressed up!
I can tell you're determined to make a perfect impression.
I'm impressed!
Well, first things first! Please be so good as to kindly be seated!
Well I'm stumped! That's you asked to meet me at twelve!
That's the time for the Sorority party!
The time was changed! That's why we can meet now.
If we can't bake a cake like I promised...
At least we can eat one!
Your treat, right?
I thought it was your treat!
You said so on the phone!
You remembered!
So I'll order... some angel cake, a lemon square,
and a New York cheese cake with blue berries!
What can Nanako be doing?
Shinobu-san?
Yes?
Misonoo-san is the only one who hasn't arrived yet.
Do you know what happened to her?
She's... I mean...
Could... Could I use the phone?
Excuse me...
I'll be right back!
I didn't sleep well last night.
I was just getting sleepy when the sky got lighter and I heard the delivery boy.
I tried shutting my eyes even harder...
But the sky just kept getting lighter and lighter.
I got up and took a shower...
Then I thought I'd use the time for homework, at least.
I sat at my desk but couldn't do anything.
It's good to talk like this!
Thank you, Tomoko!
Hello, this is the Misonoo residence.
Nanako has left already.
She has?
She did leave already?
Yes. But something must have happened.
She would never be this late without calling us.
So now, everyone... Now we will start the interviews.
When they hear their name called,
each candidate should come into the interview room.
Interviewers, please come with me.
Thank you!
You are welcome.
It's time! Time to go home and do my homework.
Tomoko...
Thank you. I finally feel a little relaxed!
Homework for me, party for you... What a difference!
This won't happen again.
I wonder about that...
But why would it?
If you are selected...
Sorry!
Bye!
Good luck!
Default, Shinobu Mariko...
Coming!
When did you start ballet?
When I was six, my mom took me to lessons...
You had a part in a play in English in Junior High.
Yes, I've had a tutor for English and French since elementary school.
Well, you may go back now.
Thank you very much.
That finishes the last of the candidates.
Misonoo hasn't arrived yet...
Misonoo-san? A very unfortunate case.
The first rule for the Sorority is being on time.
Yet she is late by more than two hours.
Is that how she feels about being a member?
The party is over. So, let's wrap it up.
I beg you!
Please, Miya-sama! Please give her a little more time!
Seiran School, Seiran School.
I wonder if Shinobu-san is already here.
I wonder if this dress makes me look too girlish...
Well, too late to worry about that!
Kaoru-no-kimi...
Udaishou Kaoru-no-Kimi in The Tale of Genji was born with a beautiful aura, like hers...
Her chest...
Oh! I'm sorry! I didn't mean to stare.
That's ok, no problem.
Did you just arrive?
What?
Aren't you going to attend the Sorority party?
Yes! That's right...
You're late.
Everybody left a few minutes ago.
What!
The party was finished a long time ago.
No way! The party starts at three!
So calm you are. Amazing.
There you are, Misonoo-san!
Why on earth are you here?
All the freshmen have left already.
The Big Sisters are so angry!
But... the phone call...
Anyway, hurry up!
Why? Why?
Hurry up! Hurry up!
What... what happened?
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Despite being terribly late for the selection party,
Nanako is nevertheless selected for membership.
Misaki Aya, rejected by the Sorority, starts a campaign of slander against Nanako.
...revealing the affair between her father, Professor Misonoo, and Nanako's mother...
Next episode: The Music Box
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...