My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
I'm back...
Welcome home.
Where's Dad?
He's not home yet...
Oh, Nanako-san, there's a letter for you...
Let's see... it's from Henmi-san...
What! Really? Thank you!
Wow! A big envelope! I wonder what it is.
Dear Nanako-san, how have you been?
First, I must apologize for not writing very often...
I'm enclosing the brochure for our Gakuin University Fair.
Please take a look at it,
...and if it appeals to you, please do plan to attend.
There aren't any formal invitations,
...in fact, they told us to invite all the women we can!
I heard a rumor that there are prizes for all the women.
So please bring your friends.
P.S.—
P.S. These days, I don't hear from you quite as often.
I assume "no news is good news".
So I'm happy you're doing well.
20. The Gardening Shears
Well, there are clubs for English, comedy, anime...
Wow! All kinds of music ensembles too!
There's lots of food stands, also...
Let's go! Mariko-san will want to go too, I bet!
Sure!
Oh, look, look!
There's a masquerade dance too!
You'd be wearing a mask. Then you could even hold hands in public!
"There are many masks to choose from"...
I'll take this one, "Snow White".
How about you?
This one, "Juliet".
Woo-woo! Then you'll meet a "Romeo"!
The University Fair? There's a dance party?
How utterly disgusting!
Why? What's so disgusting about that?
The whole thing!
A man and woman holding hands, bodies touching...
Just thinking about it gives me the creeps!
You're twisted!
Who's twisted?
Anyway, I can't let you go to such a repulsive affair alone!
Mariko-san!
Give me back that program!
Geez!
Hey, hold up!
Now see here!
Shinobu-san!
Hey! Give it back! That's Nanako's!
Is this program that important?
Of course!
Is it true, Nanako?
What?
That you're dating a boy?
That he's a student at Gakuin?
Shinobu-san!
I told you not to!
Now listen. This guy is like a brother to Nanako.
It's not like he's her...
"Like" a brother, right? Not actually her brother, right?
What are you thinking about?
What business is it of yours who she associates with?
Well well! Now it's obvious that something's happening!
Can you believe this?
You won't catch me hanging out with you anymore!
Let's go, Nanako.
There's no point in asking her to go with us...
...'cause she can't stand being near "disgusting" places!
But...
Just watch.
What?
I... I'm coming!
See?
It's just too big a risk for you two to go alone.
It's far too dangerous!
I have to protect Misonoo-san from the hands of men.
That's okay. I'll protect her!
So, what time and where do we meet?
My dear Brother,
...everyone is looking forward to the Fair this Sunday!
Professor Takada's "International Relations"
Don't worry, I have that book too...
Thanks! I've looked all over, but it's out of print.
I can't sell it to you, but you can borrow it as long as you like...
But don't lose it.
Alright.
The brakes don't feel quite right.
Go ahead. You know where my room is?
Yeah, sure.
Go on in while I check these out...
Oh, Fukiko-san... It's been a while! How are you?
Taking care of the roses?
Yes...
Your roses are always so gorgeous.
Ouch!
Sorry... not very talkative, is she...
She must not like me.
Hah. Who knows.
When I first met her she was in grade school.
Now she's a lovely young woman. Amazing!
I bet she's an alien.
Whatever goes on in her head, it's a complete mystery to me.
There we go! Got it!
Have a seat!
Why not join us for dinner?
No, no thanks. I have things to do.
You know, you haven't been here since you graduated!
Oh, I guess you're right.
By the way, did you invite your high-schooler to the fair?
Yes, I sent her a program.
She said she's coming, and plans to bring a couple of friends.
Great! Girls usually enjoy university fairs.
Bye!
See you later...
Yoshino naru, natsumi no kawano kawa yodo ni, kamo no naku naru yamakage ni shite...
What focused vision this poem has!
It is so suggestive, idyllic, and eloquent.
Note the many "N" syllables used in it...
I have a great idea!
It might have been too plain without that
I don't think it's gonna work.
You'll never know unless you try.
Hey, over there! What's going on?
And ending that as "yamakage ni shite" is so suggestive, so...
Excuse me, Kaoru-no-Kimi?
Saint-Juste-sama... I have a message for you.
A message?
Yes, on behalf of Misonoo Nanako-san.
Yes, on behalf of Mariko-san.
Mariko-san would like you to come to the fair.
The University Fair? Tomorrow?
We'd love to have you and Kaoru-no-Kimi go with us,
So, here I am asking you for her,
...and Nanako-san is asking Kaoru-no-Kimi for me.
Asking Kaoru to go to a fair at Gakuin University...
What? Um... but what's so funny about that?
The odds are probably ten thousand to one. There's no way she'll go.
Why not?
Best you don't know why.
Also... I appreciate the offer, but I can't go either.
The Gakuin Fair?
Yes... I know a graduate student there... so...
I'm sorry... we have another scrimmage on Sunday.
Really? Mariko-san will miss you.
Sorry!
I can forget, because I love.
I can forget, because I loved.
Here's some tea...
Good, thanks.
Did Nanako go to bed?
Not a chance.
Hey, look, Mom!
Don't you think the pearls would go perfectly with this dress?
Maybe, who knows...
For sure it would!
So, would you lend them to me, please?
But it's only a university fair! Why a necklace?
Please! Just one day!
Well, if you insist.
Thank you!
In the upstairs dresser, right?
Walking on air, isn't she?
Yes...
I wonder how she feels about Takehiko-san...
We should let her know soon.
But...
Don't worry.
I'm not brave enough for that yet.
But I know I'll have to, someday.
Ok! All right!
Yes, Misonoo residence...
I'm sorry to call so late. I have a favor to ask.
Miya-sama?
Do you have any plans for tomorrow?
Um... tomorrow?
Yes, Sunday.
Well... yes. In the afternoon... with Shinobu-san.
Oh good! Could you spare some time in the morning?
Well... sure!
A tea ceremony?
Yes! I have a tea ceremony every Sunday morning,
...and I invite one of the Sorority members.
It seems everyone is busy tomorrow... so I'd like to invite you.
So, would you? Come to my house tomorrow?
All right, I'll be free tomorrow morning.
I'm very grateful for the invitation.
Thank goodness! I'm sure it will be lovely, just you and me.
Thank you, Nanako-san.
You're welcome!
Also...
Yes?
Please don't mention this to anyone.
Why?
This is the first time I've invited a freshman to a tea ceremony.
You understand. Some others might feel jealous about that.
Ok, I understand.
Then, good night.
Thank you very much. And good night.
I'm sorry, I forgot to tell you something!
Before you come over to my house, could you stop at the Sorority?
Ok!
You know the storage room there? Please pick up the Meissen tea set.
The Meissen tea set?
Yes... a special set just for special guests.
I'd like to use it for our ceremony tomorrow.
Well...
The key is at the security desk.
Sorority members can always pick it up from there.
Ok. All right.
Bye, now....
See you then!
One o'clock sharp at Reuben's, in front of the university. okay?
Ok. Be on time!
It should be okay.
If the tea ceremony finishes by 11:30; I can make it...
The key to the Sorority's storage room?
Yes, it's right here.
Sign your name and grade.
You're a member of the Sorority, right?
Yes, I am.
There it is.
Now let's see... a Meissen tea set...
This one... is a Seiburu soup set...
They're all in boxes which look alike!
This is beyond me... I should have gotten more details...
It's locked! How on earth?
That's strange. The door couldn't have locked itself!
Who's there? Who locked the door?
Open the door! Stop playing games!
Please! I know you're there!
Open the door! Please, open the door!
Please! I beg you!
Who's doing this? Open up! Please open the door!
What can I do now?
If I stay locked up in here,
...I'll miss the tea ceremony and the university fair!
I knew it! There's someone out there!
Wait! Don't go! Help me, please!
Let me out!
Please!
Stay there until evening.
Sorry I'm late.
Hi, Tomoko-san!
I was afraid you were all waiting for me,
...but Nanako still isn't here?
Give her 5 more minutes...
Hey, let's charge her 100 Yen for each minute!
It's a deal!
My dear Brother, I'm sorry.
It looks like I won't be at the fair.
And how will I be able to apologize to Miya-sama?
You're working far too hard for a Sunday!
And you? You're smoking far too much for a Sunday!
I'd promise to quit smoking.
...if you went to the Gakuin University Fair.
Her program!
So, I'll have a little fair just for me...
Miss Fukiko, there's a phone call...
...it's from Misonoo-san...
What?
I'm very sorry. I can't apologize enough.
Kaoru-no-Kimi broke the lock and then she...
I can't believe this happened! I'm sorry I missed everything.
Really? I had no idea. What an experience!
We'll have the tea ceremony some other time.
Don't keep Shinobu-san and the others waiting. Enjoy the fair.
Oh really? Really?
Of course, enjoy it! Have fun.
Thank you!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako, Tomoko, and Mariko go to the Gakuin University Fair.
There, Mariko is determined to protect Nanako from all the men.
Nanako becomes upset when she discovers how little she knows about Henmi.
Next episode: The University Fair
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...