My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Give it to me please!
What are you going to do with it?
I'll smoke it. I can smoke too!
No way.
Yes I can!
Inhale then!
See? Now you understand.
Don't smoke. It doesn't suit you.
I want you staying just as you are... until the end of time.
I... I love you!
I love you!
19. The Utakata Game
Let's go back.
If we hurry we can make the afternoon classes.
I... I love you!
That was some surprise.
Huh?
...Rei having that girl with her...
I suppose it could happen, since both of them are Seiran students...
...I bet both of them had morning classes, though.
We skipped classes in high school too, didn't we?
I guess so, but still...
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Huh?
Since the last time you saw Rei.
Yes...
...and the last time you saw Orihara Kaoru.
Are you really okay with that?
I have no choice.
I'll go on ahead!
Dreamtime ends now.
Nanako-san!
Nanako!
Um... Good morning.
Hey now! It's too late in the day for a "good morning"!
What is it? Did something happen?
We called your house over and over!
You called my house?
Nobody answered.
Oh yes, Mom said she'd be out today...
What could possibly have happened to you today?
Well, I... uh...
On the way to school I started feeling ill.
...so I took a long rest at the coffee shop near the station.
So... how do you feel, now?
I'm fine now. Sorry to make you worry.
So at last, I finally said it.
I love you!
It's done.
That dreamlike moment,
...that one moment alone with her it is gone now.
I went to afternoon classes... then they were over...
I thought I would become myself again.
But I didn't.
The dreamtime isn't over.
Instead, it is expanding, inflating like a giant bubble...
...getting bigger and bigger.
This morning Saint-Juste-sama was just sitting there...
Nanako! Nanako, for goodness sake!
It's the last stop! The last stop! We're at the station!
These familiar stores, and even the city itself,
...have somehow taken on a new look today.
You spent your 3000 Yen on that? What's with you?
But it's so pretty!
My dear Brother,
I think I want to cherish and care for my special "bubble"...
...my big, inflated bubble...
...and hope it doesn't burst!
So, where is it? That cafe where you rested this morning?
What?
You know! The one you were at while you felt sick this morning.
Oh! Oh! Um...
You've seen it I'm sure... "Cafe la Moulin".
Oh, Cafe la Moulin? That one?
Let's try one more... It looks so pretty on you!
Really?
But you know... Cafe la Moulin doesn't open until afternoon...
What?
Well, let's go home...
Tomoko...
See you later. See you tomorrow.
Tomoko!
It's okay, it's all right!
Today your face says "I'm happy!" and I really like it that way!
Tomoko!
Tomoko...
Tomoko.
It's okay.
Can you stay a little longer with me?
I...
I don't want to be alone.
Suddenly I don't want to be alone...
How is Rei doing in school?
Why do you ask?
Is she attending classes? Everyday?
I don't know... I don't see much of her,
...because she and I are in different grades.
I saw her today.
...in the park, in the morning, during classes.
You're always acting as if you couldn't care less about her, but...
Rei "kidnapped" a freshman today.
Do you know Misonoo Nanako?
Yes, barely...
We inducted her into the Sorority this year.
Is she close to Rei?
I don't know.
I hope Rei doesn't corrupt her...
I should be going.
Brother, how did you become acquainted with this freshman?
Well, never mind...
Good night.
I didn't want to be alone.
I didn't want to be alone, today.
I... I love you!
That's the first time I've ever said those words.
I've heard myself thinking those words,
...but I never thought I would say them.
...not aloud, not face-to-face, I thought.
That's why I couldn't bear being alone.
I'm back...
Welcome home.
You're late today, Nanako.
Before you go upstairs... would you come to the living room?
Yes, only one moment...
What?
Your father's done it again!
Yes, I guess I did...
I wondered if it was a bit too young...
It was in a display window at a store near the university.
I was sure it would look good on you, so I bought it.
Thank you, Daddy!
It might make a good party dress.
Thank you, Daddy...
Ma cherie La Poupee... She looks just like you.
I knew what would be in store for me,
...when I finally was able to be alone.
See, now it's starting.
Oh... Saint-Juste-sama!
I told Saint-Juste-sama!
How was I able to speak to her like that?
How on earth does she feel about me now?
Saint-Juste-sama!
Hey, keep it down in the gallery!
This isn't a regular season game. It's just a scrimmage!
You're all welcome to watch quietly.
...but we can do without all the screaming!
How about a picture of you and Saint-Juste-sama together?
...maybe later after the game, please?
Well I don't know about all this.
I've been trying to get you to practice with us,
...but can't you do something about your "groupies"?
Maybe we should spray them with insecticide?
You've gotten really cocky!
No, it just doesn't mean much to me.
Anyway, I'm counting on you to start the next game.
Does this mean the end of Seiran basketball, I wonder?
Was it foolish to speak up like that to her?
I can't even say "hello" like I used to, anymore...
And while I'm thinking all this, what is she thinking?
Is she one of your groupies, too?
What?
That one... watching you from behind the tree.
What are you talking about?
Ok, nevermind then...
She's an acquaintance of Henmi Takehiko.
Yesterday, at the park.
We ran into him and my brother there.
Henmi was still the same old Henmi Takehiko.
I've forgotten him. Completely.
We were able to translate literally up to here.
The important part begins at line 18.
So... let's see... Miss Misonoo?
Oh! Nanako! Your turn!
Uh, yes!
Would you translate from line 18, please?
Ok!
Not the literal meaning, please.
Express the text using your own feeling for the meanings within it.
Go for it!
Go right ahead, please.
Ok!
Ai no Hyohaku-sha... Wanderer of Love...
"Koi no"
Because of the context, "Koi" would be better here.
And try "sasuraibito" instead of "hyohaku-sha" for "wanderer".
O-Okay.
A wanderer of love, I hear the whistle through the evening glow.
Yes, very good!
The last train leaving the city has just departed.
Once again, I am not on that train. Once again, I am not leaving.
Once again, I can't bear to face the depth of my own heartbreak.
Dusk is approaching.
Dusk is approaching. Once again, I wait, dreading the coming solitude.
I sit alone on these tracks, tracks reddened with rust.
Far in the distance... do I hear another whistle?
Did I hear it? Or just imagine it...
Nanako-san!
What's wrong? Easy, easy!
I'd like a window seat, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Have a seat.
Ok.
We're close to the ocean, so there are lots of seagulls flying about.
Do you like seagulls?
What? Yes.
Have you heard?
The Seiran cafeteria's fried chicken...
...is actually fried seagull?
What!?
It's in the hamburgers, too.
What?!
Anything I say that doesn't make you laugh, seems to make you cry instead....
I'm sorry, I'm sorry....
I'm strange. I'm not myself lately.
It isn't all that strange.
Falling in love makes all of us feel a bit strange, you know.
I wanted to tell you something. So I invited you here.
If it is Rei you've fallen in love with, you're going to be hurt...
Because Rei's soul is enslaved to a goddess.
That's all I had to say.
They say "to love is to suffer"...
I suppose that's all right if you're the only one hurt by it.
Of course, one avoids hurting the other, if possible...
If that's love, then I'd like to fall in love, too...
I can forget, because I love.
I can forget, because I've loved.
And even... I'll even forget that I've forgotten.
I loved you that much...
I almost asked "Did you hurt the one you love?"
...but then I saw that she had loved so very deeply,
...her love was so profound,
...that it was beyond my ability to even imagine,
...and that even now she might still feel that way.
Love is "utakata". "Utakata" no koi.
Utakata?
Yes, utakata.
Love is just like a bubble...
It pops to the surface, lingers for an instant, and is soon gone.
Life's fleeting instant is like a bubble too.
So, all of us in that brief bubble seek to love and be loved...
Its beauty lies in its brevity.
But we must never despise it for being merely ephemeral.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's how we should look at it.
Yes!
Yes?
I've been thinking about... the old days.
The day I first met you.
I... uh...
You were 10, and I was 11...
It was in our back yard. Do you remember?
Uh... yes, of course!
I was crying.
You were the only one...
Yes!
...the only one to see me cry.
You were the only one, my sister...
Yes!
That's why you must look only at me.
Understand? You must never look at anyone else.
My dear brother...
Should I have kept these words to myself?
Should this have remained my secret forever?
But... but I... was helpless to hold it in!
I love you, Saint-Juste-sama!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Henmi invites Nanako to attend a university fair,
...and Nanako is thrilled to accept.
But, Fukiko becomes upset upon hearing of it.
On the day of the university fair,
...Fukiko calls Nanako to the Sorority house.
And then...
Next episode: The Gardening Shears
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...