My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Excuse me... Could you repeat that, please?
I move that the Sorority be abolished!
My dear Brother...
Kaoru-no-Kimi made a courageous speech,
...and took the assembly in a totally unexpected direction.
The student's frustration and resentment came to the surface.
It's a social caste system, for sure!
I've had it with those arrogant snobs!
A problem like this is not one for discussion solely among ourselves!
Please, don't allow your emotions to get out of control!
Who's out of control?
We're certain we can get the necessary two-thirds majority.
Go right ahead, then,
...if you think you can so easily abolish this venerated tradition.
30. The Petition
As you who attended the assembly heard already,
...I have spoken out against the existence of the Sorority.
All students must be equal.
No one should decide who is better than whom.
If you agree with this statement,
...please sign this petition.
What's the matter?
Yesterday, everyone had a lot they wanted to say!
...about what a problem the Sorority was.
Won't the school board hold it against me if I sign?
The Sorority is so close to the School Board,
...I'm reluctant to risk signing my name.
The School Board consist of Sorority Alumni!
Do you think a petition will have any effect on the School Board?
But that's it! That's why we have to do it!
Do you want to stay at school that ignores petitions from the students?
Do you want to support the system that causes such a oppression?
Does this system even have the right to exist?
Whether you are the one injured,
...or you are the one causing the injury.
...you both are victims of the Sorority.
Our curriculum should teach us this:
...that all of us are free, and equal!
I'm available to take your signature whenever you are ready.
Bye!
I'll sign. I want to sign!
Is this okay?
Thank you.
Not at all...
I'll sign too.
I agree with abolishing the Sorority too!
Me too!
And me!
What is it, Nanako?
I need a favor.
A favor?
Yes, a favor.
Now, at lunchtime?
Beginning with today's lunchtime... we want everyone to see us,
...so, won't you please give us a hand?
Kaoru-no-Kimi would carry on all alone, but the more the better.
Ha ha... well, I'm not someone who likes attracting attention, you know.
I'm actually kind of shy.
As far as the Sorority goes, I guess you could say I was against it,
...but I don't really hate it enough to abolish it.
That's right, I remember you saying just the other day,
... "This isn't all the fault of the Sorority".
The whole Sorority thing, it's so alien to me, you know.
It's really more your thing than mine, after all.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who's sorry...
Oh, don't be silly.
Bye!
Why can't I ever do fashionable things like everyone else...
Please sign the petition!
Please sign to abolish the Sorority!
My dear brother... I'm surprised at myself.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
But, it's not just me, there's Kaoru-no-Kimi too.
She's shouting into a megaphone.
I'd have thought this was totally unlike me,
...even more so than Tomoko.
Go for it!
Thank you!
Kaoru-no-Kimi, if I sign, would you autograph my notebook?
Me too!
You must be kidding!
Abolish the Sorority? She makes me so mad!
You're right! Until recently she was a member.
How can that Misonoo-san girl change her position so quickly?
She sure seemed to enjoy the Sorority when she was a member.
You know, she's just that type. Anything goes.
Just like her mother.
You didn't hear me say that!
But then again!
Ok, let's split up.
I'll go to the assembly hall
Ok, then I'll take the garden.
Go for it!
You too!
It's so strange... at first, my heart was pounding.
Then bit by bit I felt more positive.
I even began looking forward to doing it.
My dear brother...
Your Nanako is actually rather good at this!
Yes... sign your name there.
And don't forget your grade and section.
Don't push it! You made me scribble it!
I don't have to look good, as long as it's legible.
That's not nice, Saint-Juste-sama!
So, who's next?
Me!
Me too!
Please sign!
We have a petition to abolish the Sorority.
Please sign our petition!
Oh! Thank you!
You should be careful whom you ask.
You were a member, just like us.
Until recently!
You have no class at all.
It's no wonder that you were expelled.
I wasn't expelled!
I resigned on my own!
You're shameless!
Nakaya-san!
I know that you left on your own, unlike me...
So, should I put my name and section?
Yes.
Do you think I could help too?
What? Really? Of course! Yes!
Tomoko!
This crusade may be a good thing,
...but skipping lunch isn't good.
Really, Nanako! If I weren't looking after you all the time...
Don't misunderstand me. I'm no part of her crusade.
I'm just here to be Nanako's manager.
What. What are you smiling at?
You! You, the nice lady there,
...just put your signature right here,
...you mustn't put up with the Sorority!
Yes, you too, this way please, come on, come on!
I don't feel quite right about doing it like that...
It'll be okay! I have my own unique style at this.
Did she say anything?
No, nothing.
We can't just do nothing.
I wish I knew what Miya-sama was thinking.
Wow... I did pretty well! I got five people.
Let's see... I have eight!
I have six!
I guess I'm a girl with a talent for getting signatures!
You do have a talent, Tomoko!
So, the goal is a two-third majority?
Yes. If we can get two-thirds of the students to sign,
...we can submit it directly to the school board.
Let's work and get 10 more after school!
Great. Let's do that, then visit Shinobu-san.
At her house?
Sure!
How is Shinobu-san doing?
She's feeling much better.
Oh good.
But she can't stop worrying about Misaki-san.
Misaki-san?
She gets really depressed sometimes over what she did to Misaki-san.
What? You're not going to stop for tea with us?
Not today, I think.
Does it hurt?
Sure.
Misaki-san seems to be depressed since it happened.
Yes... She's not assertive and confident like she usually is.
I liked her that way better.
It doesn't feel right having tea, just us two.
It doesn't feel right.
Oh, Sonobe-san, Furuta-san...
Oh, Borgia-sama... Mona Lisa-sama!
We'd like to have a word with you, if you don't mind.
So, how is Misaki-san's injury?
Well... she is getting much better...
But she doesn't really want to talk about it.
Is that so?
Your coffee's getting cold...
Oh... Yes!
By the way...
Perhaps you were aware that the Sorority has two vacancies now,
...due to the departure of Shinobu-san and Misonoo-san.
And when we have a vacancy,
...we can choose another candidate from the freshmen.
It should be quite a big occasion for the school.
There are many students who would want to be selected.
Yes. I guess so.
To tell the truth,
...we thought about recommending Misaki-san.
What should we do?
Miya-sama is very concerned about this petition.
The thrust of this crusade is from your classmates.
What should we do?
Perhaps, if she were helpful to us,
...we could recommend her.
Being in the Sorority was a dream of Misaki-san's.
Yes, since Junior High. Her more than anyone.
My dear brother...
Each person has their own way of thinking.
I was floating along, aimless and giddy,
...then something brought me back down to earth.
It's okay. They're in the locker room.
It happened on the third day of the petition.
We have to open it.
Uh... yeah.
Let's do it!
What are you doing?
That's the petition book.
Did you ask Kaoru if you could burn it?
I think not.
Most certainly not.
If you disagree with me, say so.
I don't hide from discussion.
But to do this, behind my back...
...it makes me sad.
Do you realize what you were doing?
Say something! Furuta-san! Sonobe-san!
I can't let the Sorority be abolished!
Yes, that's why I wanted to kill off this stupid campaign.
The rest of you too! You used to love the Sorority!
We'd like to hear the truth.
What do you mean?
This was Misaki-san's idea, wasn't it?
What?!
That's enough.
Let's forget it.
The petition have been returned unharmed.
No, let me finish, Kaoru-no-Kimi...
You two! Misaki-san put you up to doing this, is that right?
Right! It's just the thing Misaki-san would come up with!
No! Absolutely not!
It's true!
Her accusation is true.
I asked Sonobe-san and Furuta-san to do this for me.
Misaki-san!
More than anyone, I wanted into the Sorority.
More than anyone, I admired the Sorority.
I had committed my heart to it,
...something that a mere opportunist like you wouldn't understand.
As soon as you were abandoned by Miya-sama,
...you ran off to join this petition campaign.
You'll grab anything good that gets within reach,
...just like your mother!
Misaki-san!
I resent that! How... how can you say such a thing!
You're... you're nothing more than a wretched failure!
Yes. I am wretched.
Is that so bad?
I don't mind.
Everyone else says that too.
Wait, Misaki-san!
Misaki-san!
Why did you say such a thing?
We did it because Mona-Lisa-sama and Borgia-sama asked us!
You didn't ask us to do anything!
We did it on our own!
Misaki-san!
If you do this, you'll get the blame for everything!
Please, stop.
Please don't do me any more favors!
Misaki-san...
Farewell.
It's the truth! We weren't lying!
We did everything on our own!
They said if we could help the Sorority,
...she'd be recommended for membership.
Really! Misaki-san didn't know anything!
Misaki-san wanted to protect us!
She wanted to help us!
Please! Believe us!
Now, everything will be her fault.
We were worried about her!
She seemed so depressed recently.
That's why... that's why we had to...
I hardly know what to say.
But I believe you.
Is that enough? Is it?
How long has it been...
...that I have been so detestable?
Aya-san!
It's time to take Halloween for walk!
Please!
Aya-san!
This is from the first year of junior high.
Here, look at this picture.
This was the fall tournament.
The preliminary, to choose the anchor runner for the class relay.
I'd already felt a sense of rivalry towards her.
But at this point, the feeling became very strong.
No matter what, I couldn't allow her to beat me.
I'm sure she must've felt the same way.
She was first, I was second.
We'd passed the last turn, and were in the home straight.
Why? Why did you stop?
You'd have been the anchor if you hadn't stopped!
It meant nothing if I won because you fell.
I wanted to beat you fair and square!
I was so furious.
I absolutely hated her.
I resolved never to let this girl even see me smile.
Hate ran through my body like a fire.
But now... it's very strange.
We've been through a lot since then, and now...
Now all that's left is an appreciation of her.
All I remember is that she was very straight, and very fair.
Yes, she has some good qualities. I admit that.
Watching out for her friends, that's especially good.
I'm...
I'm going to apologize to Misaki-san!
Today... today I said something terrible to her.
Is it okay, Mariko, if I go?
Why ask me?
Why do you have to ask me?
I'm sorry.
She went out walking her dog, and isn't back yet.
Usually she's back within half an hour.
Yes, she always goes to the beach.
Thank you! Let's go!
Do you... do you love me?
Today, you'll be going home alone, Halloween.
Misaki-san!
I'll wait!
I'm waiting for you!
This time... if it turns out you're the one who falls,
...then this time, I'll be the one who waits!
No, don't!
If you do that, you'll not be the anchor!
My dear brother...
It was the next day.
Previously unthinkable names appeared on the petition.
From the freshmen, section B: Furuta Megumi-san,
...as well as Sonobe Miyuki-san.
And then, another...
Misaki Aya-san.
Please help us out there!
Sign the petition to abolish the Sorority!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...