My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Tomoko, it's Nanako on the phone...
Tomoko!
Tell her I'm sleeping.
Oh come on!
It's only eight-thirty!
Then tell her I'm not back home yet.
What's happened with you two? A quarrel?
I just can't talk to her now!
You shouldn't bother waiting for Nanako-san.
What?
She won't be able to go home with you.
As a member of the Sorority, she has a lot of socializing to do.
Keep in mind that she is no longer an ordinary student.
Tough!
So how is Tomoko?
She's not back yet...
Oh?
...but that can't be...
Good night!
Um... Nanako?
Yes?
With regard to...
...Henmi-san, the one who sent you the package...
What is your relationship with him?
Don't worry! There's nothing to worry about!
It's nothing at all.
He was just a teacher at our cram school.
That was just a present he sent me for passing my entrance exams.
Oh? That's nice. Did you thank him?
Yes... but I wouldn't tell Dad about it...
I wouldn't want him worrying...
Yes, that's best...
Of course Misonoo-san's womanhood...
...should be especially good as far as cooking and selling is concerned!
What! Why?
Her womanhood?
You didn't know?
Her mother used to work at an establishment near Jyoto University...
as a Cocktail Waitress!
Why are you looking at me that way?
Nothing, never mind...
Brother, dear brother...
The more I try to believe Mom and Dad, the more doubts I seem to have...
and I'm not brave enough to ask them.
Did he really have another child?
And another wife, the child's mother?
5. Thorns of Doubt and Suspicion
Oh no! I've got to get on the train, or I'm gonna be late!
What! She left half an hour earlier than usual?!
Tomoko is avoiding me.
Perhaps because I was chosen as a Sorority member?
He was still silent, and seemed to be lost in thought.
When I rose to leave, he did not invite me to stay...
But Tomoko will understand.
We've been together since elementary school.
We've been friends a long time.
Tomoko!
Is that for sure?
Yes! It's true!
You're kidding!
Tomoko!
So! What is your Cooking Club specialty?
I picked cookies and baking!
You know, I think I will too!
So anyway! The story you just told me was... the funniest yet!
Tomoko!
Tomoko, I need to talk to you!
Can't now. I have an appointment.
But it won't take long!
Anyway, there's someone waiting who is more your type.
What?
Nanako-san!
Tomoko!
My goodness, Arikura-san!
Tomoko...
Let's hurry!
We have to prepare for the Sorority initiation!
We should be the first ones there.
The Big Sisters frown on being late!
The Sorority is our highest priority!
You know that!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Rei!
You make me so angry!
You're still taking these!
When will it sink in?!
When indeed, "Doctor" Orihara...
I still have one left, you know.
You're looking great!
The light in your eyes makes me happy to be alive.
Is something happening here?
We are going to the Sorority House, Misonoo-san, Shinobu-san...
Won't you come with us?
You could be very helpful to us if you came too.
Saint-Juste-sama...
...she acts like a docile sheep whenever Miya-sama is nearby...
Rei!
Are you going to wear that bracelet forever?
Those flowers go there... and that table goes at the corner...
And this white vase... to show off the flowers!
Yes, like that, close to the tapestry...
Asaka-san... over here, please.
Over here...
Could you hold that corner?
What on earth is going on?
Shinobu-san... that should go on the table, on the right.
Blood! Bloodstains!
Please bandage me.
Use this.
You do it!
You!
Komabayashi-san, take care of her.
Ok.
You!
Let go!
Please let go of that!
Nanako, oh my!
I certainly didn't imagine that!
I'm certain that Miya-sama did that deliberately.
Why would she do that?!
Once again...
she acts just like a man would
Miya-sama, right?
Why is it?
Why do you insist on torturing yourself?
Enough is enough!
Rei!
So now, the new members will sign in...
and will receive some flowers and a greeting from Fukiko-sama.
Shinobu Mariko...
As an honorable Sorority member will you obey the rules of the Sorority...
and dedicate yourself to develop the spirit of the Sorority with love and pride?
I will!
Congratulations, Mariko-san.
Your smile is as refreshing as an azalea!
Please, never lose that lovely smile!
Thank you so very much!
Misonoo Nanako-san...
As an honorable Sorority member will you obey the rules...
The love that you receive
comes from the love you create within the kindness of your own heart.
Coming!
Who is it?
I'm sorry, I didn't call first...
Huh?
It's you!
Come on, geez, what's with you!
Nanako, you've been in such a weird mood all day!
When you bandaged Sainte-Juste, all by yourself?
Uh-huh...
Didn't you realize that Miya-sama was glaring at you?
It gave me a cold sweat!
You fool! Don't defy Miya-sama! You can't go against her will!
You can be voted out of the Sorority at any time!
Furthermore, her father is on the Board of Directors at our school!
Are you even listening to me?
Hey, Nanako-san!
My dear Brother...
I dare not tell anyone what Miya-sama did...
Nor about Saint-Juste's attitude toward Miya-sama...
...these glimpses of their true feelings...
This is all beyond my understanding.
And it frightens me.
You've never been able to forgive us...
At first, I blamed you for taking my father away from us,
And I resented my father for loving you more than my mother and me.
But then...
You kept sending money until I was an adult... even after Mother died.
Somehow, every month you couldn't have done it on a professor's salary alone...
As I grew older...
...I began to understand.
To forgive or not to forgive... to blame or not to blame...
Finally the issue somehow didn't seem important anymore.
Takehiko-san!
Nanako is charming!
I've come to feel... like she really is my sister.
But when I first found out, I was shocked!
Please! Be my brother!
Your name is?
Misonoo Nanako.
Misonoo? Daughter of Professor Misonoo of Jyoto University?
Accepting her request meant that eventually you would find out...
That bothered me.
On the other hand, if I could do something for her as a brother,
Then that's what I wanted to do.
I have one request... please...
Ok.
We haven't told Nanako that her father has another child.
If we tell her, she'd be hurt unnecessarily, and blame us, so...
We won't have to tell her.
I'll just be one among many... a friend she confided in, during her adolescence.
Thank you so much!
You're welcome.
Nanako! You'll hurt yourself! Stop!
...the hand which touched my hair, that often tossed the ball to me...
handing me "Tom Sawyer", cleaning out his pipe... only 6 months ago!
Father... I've lost you!
I should never have come here.
Surely...
Father... my father...
Father...
That was you on the phone just now, I know it.
I won't answer.
I'll get even for today, for hurting me so!
The love that you receive
comes from the love you create within the kindness of your own heart.
Thank you very much.
At the same time, love creates hate and doubt and anger.
Don't be afraid of people hurting you.
But if you do get hurt...
...then hurt the person who hurt you.
Nanako!
Nanako... are you okay?
It's nothing... I'm ok!
It was just a nightmare.
Ok.
If you can't go back to sleep, come to my study,
I'll be up for awhile.
Thank you, Daddy...
It rained until just before dawn...
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako's gym clothes, missing from her locker, are finally found. They are shredded.
The petition to oust her from the Sorority continues to circulate.
Nanako finally decides to leave the Sorority...
Next episode: Lost and Alone
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...