My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
You were 10, I was 11...
It was in our backyard garden that we first met.
I was crying. You alone saw me.
Yes.
Only you, my sister, knew of my tears!
Yes!
I was 10, you were 11...
It was in May, and such a bright day.
It was my very first visit to the Ichinomiya family.
Finally, the moment came,
...and you came into view.
You were the beauty my mother had often mentioned.
Who are you? This is my garden.
I'm...
Oh! I know...
...you're from the maid's family.
Come and sit down. Right here.
I was invited to a friend's birthday party, but... guess what happened!
They seated me all the way at the foot of the table.
That was the seat they gave me!
I have never been treated so badly!
I was so upset!
I got up and left!
Because she had a bad seat... is that all?
Listen, you'll not repeat any of this.
Not to your father, your mother, your brother... No one!
Miss, Miss!
You've come home already?
Remember, it's a secret!
Fukiko-sama! So this is where you are!
I saw the driver but not you so I was worried...
Don't concern yourself.
I didn't feel well, so I left. That's all.
You had a regal bearing that I will never forget.
You were only a girl of 11, who was crying so hard only a moment ago,
...yet your face was now clear and composed,
...because you couldn't allow the maid to see your tears of humiliation.
My young heart trembled to see such pride...
...it thrilled me with such joy!
Since that day, you have filled my heart.
Since that day, I've had eyes for no one but you.
But, I didn't know...
I didn't know that you had fallen in love... tragically in love,
...painfully in love, with Takehiko,
For one brief summer, for one scant week...
But that was like you.
You alone could have experienced such a thing.
25. The Scarlet Lipstick
Saint-Juste-sama!
I've been looking all over for you!
I called over and over.
And you haven't been at school, not since Miya-sama's birthday party.
Finally, yesterday I went to your apartment...
And now I'm here, right?
Well... yes!
Was there something you wanted? Something important?
Not really, I guess...
Later, then...
Wait! Your apartment door was open all day yesterday!
You need to shut the door when you leave!
Sure, okay...
Where are you going?
So here you are, Misonoo-san.
We've been looking for you.
Uh... yes?
Miya-sama wants to see you.
Oh! At the Sorority House?
Yes.
Ok. I'll be going then.
Wait... don't go right away.
She'll be expecting you at 8 o'clock in the Sorority's Kisaragi Room.
8 o'clock? In the Kisaragi Room?
That's ridiculous. That's too late!
Go on home first. Then come back later.
The main gate will be closed then!
This is none of your business!
She would like to discuss some important Sorority business.
There are matters she can only discuss with you.
Only with me?
That's what Miya-sama said. That should suffice. Right?
Ok.
Saint-Juste-sama!
Sew each stitch, one by one, from your heart,
...and give character to your needlepoint.
Make a stitch, and think about Mom. Orihara-san...
Yes, yes...
I'm not really expecting beautiful needlepoint from you...
I can't do this stuff!
But shouldn't you at least be able to sew on a button for your future husband.....
I'm looking for a husband who can sew his own buttons.
...and maybe some nice needlepoint on your child's lunch bag,
...even if the lunch is a frozen one...
What's wrong, Nanako-san?
What? Mmmm....
Are you worried about something?
You've been looking depressed all afternoon.
I may not be able to go see "Believe in Love" this evening.
What? Today's the last day!
Did you tell Tomoko-san?
No, not yet.
What's going on?
That's the movie you wanted to see...
Yes, but it'll be after 8 by the time the movie is over.
Yes? So what's happening at 8?
Miya-sama.
Hm?
Miya-sama wants to see me at 8.
Miya-sama? What does she want?
I don't know.
Do you have a second?
Huh? Sure!
Maybe you can answer a question.
Who, me?
You're Misonoo-san's friend, right?
Well... yes!
Could you tell me... about her and Henmi Takehiko?
Oh! okay.
What luck! To get this close to Saint-Juste-sama!
Well... the two of them first met when she...
Rei!
I was looking for you. I wanted to invite you to tomorrow's practice.
Did you know about this?
Huh? About what?
Takehiko taught at the cram school Nanako-san attended.
So, she made him into her brother and pen-pal.
Brother and pen-pal... Totally girlish, that's just like her!
So what? It's none of my business.
None of your business? Sure. That's nice.
Bye!
Rei!
My Dear Brother...
School ended at 4, and my appointment wasn't until 8.
I couldn't stay all that time.
...so I went to see "Believe in Love" with Mariko-san and Tomoko.
I decided to leave in the middle,
...so I could make it to my appointment.
Besides... the movie "Believe in Love" was...
Well, it was a bit more "adult" than I expected.
Who is it?
It's you.
Good evening.
Sorry for dropping in unexpectedly.
I wanted to ask you...
What's wrong? Are you drunk?
Probably.
But not one drop has parted these lips...
What?
No need for a doctor.
I get like this sometimes.
I have question... for you.
What?
So many questions...
...so I came here.
I'll make coffee. Come on, come inside.
So many questions!
But I don't want to... I mustn't...
...I can't even ask you now!
I can't do it, for her...
...for the sake of her self-respect...
I have to leave now.
They protested my leaving,
...but they were absorbed in the movie.
The Kisaragi Room?
Yes, you know about it?
The Kisaragi Room is a private lounge for the head of the Sorority.
You'll find it at the north end on the 2nd floor...
Come in.
Excuse me.
Come in. Come sit down.
Yes...
Come closer. Come sit down, here.
Ok...
Learn from me. Come, listen.
What's the matter? Come closer. Right here.
Ok...
When I was a child, I had a doll with lips much like yours.
See... beautiful, isn't it... this would suit you well.
Now, close your eyes,
...be very still, close your lips...
My brother!
How beautiful!
It's perfect for you.
In two years, maybe three,
...you'll be surprised how beautiful a lady you have become.
...then, many fine men will be attracted to you.
So...
Stop seeing Henmi-san.
But I told you...
He and I...
I mean... he's only...
I know!
I knew it from the start.
I knew everything from the start!
From the start?
Don't you understand?
Miya-sama?
I'm in love with you.
You're so adorable, I don't know what to do...
...even back on Orientation Day...
So... forget Henmi-san.
Saint-Juste-sama!
You...
Get out!
That magnificent bearing and composure,
...the exquisite dignity that made me tremble,
...such perfect pride... where is it all now?
This is... a disgrace!
How could you...
Admit it! You love Henmi Takehiko!
So you admitted this girl, Misonoo Nanako, into the Sorority.
You wanted her to worship you so much that she would leave Henmi!
My brother... and Miya-sama?
So that's why... I'm in the Sorority...
That's... that's terrible!
Now finally, all is clear to me.
I see your intentions and your motives.
Put a stop to this right now!
You have degraded yourself and I can't stand it!
You would do well not to speak such lies.
Nanako-san, you mustn't believe any of this.
Since you aren't going, then I will leave myself.
Saint-Juste-sama...
Which one?
What?
Which one was it? Which ear?
Which one? Which ear was touched by Miya-sama's lips?
Which one?
My dear Brother...
...I'm losing my mind.
Can it be true? What Saint-Juste said?
Miya-sama is in love with you,
...and that's why she chose me for the Sorority?
To keep me away from you?
This is humiliating.
So I wasn't actually qualified for the Sorority after all.
And... and unbearable.
As much as I worship you, Fukiko-sama,
...it seems I can only hurt you.
And now I've spoken words which can't be unspoken.
My love for him...
I nurtured it... so deep within myself...
It grew magically, becoming a living treasure...
...my very own treasure...
My secret, invisible treasure!
Faster! Drive faster!
Sure. okay!
I must resign.
I must resign from the Sorority.
Hi, Nanako!
Hi.
Let me fill you in on how "Believe in Love" ended!
How it ended?
Yeah, you left in the middle.
It got so intriguing!
Tell me, I want to know.
Well, you know, Elizabeth discovered that Tom had a lover,
...and that lover was her best friend.
She caught them meeting together.
That's...awful!
Yes it was!
She was helpless to do anything.
She faced the end of the relationship.
Guess what happened next...
It's so sad. She began traveling alone, still carrying his unborn child.
And?
That's it! That was the end.
That's the end?
Hey, Elizabeth? Are you okay?
Maybe tomorrow or the next day...
In a while, I guess.
Thank you, Tomoko.
Milady! We weren't told to expect you...
Has something happened?
Milady!
It was my treasure.
That treasure was mine alone!
They destroyed it! They... they trampled on it!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...