My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Saint-Juste-sama!
Fukiko-sama...
Eh?
I've been waiting!
All this time... all this time...
I knew you would someday keep your promise to me!
Oh, Fukiko-sama!
No! I'm not her!
It's just as you told me then...
...you've come here so we can... die together...
Saint-Juste-sama!
...you said... we could die together...
She's mad! She's gone completely mad!
Brother!
14. The Secret Door
I'm not her! Look at me closely!
I'm not Miya-sama!
Fukiko-sama!
No! I'm not her!
Fukiko-sama... why?
Why, Fukiko-sama?
She's heavily drugged again!
You said we could die together.
Look... here is the bracelet, still.
It never left my wrist since the day you gave it to me... just as you wished.
So now... finally, you came to die with me, after all...
There is nothing good to be said of Life.
Rather, let us die and dwell together in eternity.
The truth is this... that nothing can give any kind of meaning to life.
Now, Fukiko-sama!
It's your turn!
Stop!
Fukiko-sama!
Saint-Juste-sama! Saint-Juste-sama!
I'm not her! I'm not Miya-sama!
Don't be afraid.
I'll help you...
I'll lend you all my strength...
I'm not her! I'm not her!
Saint-Juste-sama!
It's just me!
Misonoo Nanako!
It's me! It's just me!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Brother, my Dear Brother...
I looked into Rei's deranged Fukiko-obsessed eyes...
...but I think I saw there... something...
...something more like love... than hate.
You said we could die together.
See, here is the bracelet still, just as you wished it.
And the scar... what if that scar...
...what if it is from a double-suicide attempt with Miya-sama?
Good morning!
Saint-Juste-sama is out today, of course.
How is it that I find you here?
What business would a freshman have here in a senior's room?
Um... well...
Your absences from the cram sessions are becoming conspicuous.
I know. I'm sincerely sorry.
I'll be certain to attend from now on, but—
You must study especially hard right now.
There's not much time left.
I will!
So you won't have time to be snooping around into other people's affairs...
Saint-Juste-sama...
Are you here?
Saint-Juste-sama!
Such a pleasant sleep...
...thanks to my little pills.
You're still taking these drugs?
No! Don't!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Um... maybe it would be wise to lock your door,
...at least when you are asleep, I would think...
Any stranger, or thief, could come right in.
They can take whatever they want. Anything.
Even my life.
Oh no, it's slipped my mind!
The year Shakespeare was born!
It's 1564... and he died in 1616.
I give up!
It's easy, just remember "He wrote many plays about murder." See?
"Hito goroshi?" 1-5-6-4...
Oh, I see!
Did you get that from the Sorority cram session?
Sure!
You're so lucky...
Yes, but I have heavy responsibilities, too.
You sure do. And lots of pressure!
Say, do you have a cram session today, too?
No, from now on we do self-study only.
Oh?
There's only five days left!
The Big Sisters have their own mid-terms to study for.
Let's... let's study together then!
Um... mm...
You started doing it again.
What?
Doing "Nanako has a secret."
That's okay. See you later!
Baroque music was played from the 17th century to the mid-18th century.
The main composers in that style were
Georg Friedrich Handel, Johann Sebastian Bach, and Antonio Vivaldi.
So then, I'll make a cheesecake.
And then... I'll make something from that roast beef I have...
You'd better copy that down! They say it'll be on the test.
Ok.
Misonoo-San! Excuse me!
Aw... I was hoping... that she'd help me with my French.
You should have come earlier!
Oh! Kaoru-no-Kimi!
So what's this about Misonoo-san?
Um... yes, she's just not been herself lately...
Daydreaming all day... not even a "goodbye" when she leaves for home.
Well, maybe my French will do, after all...
Huh?
As for today...
...if you'll accept me as Misonoo-san's substitute...
Oh, yes! Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Thank you! It starts on page 57...
Yes, yes...
How is it? My cheesecake?
Hm.
The roast beef sandwich is good too!
It's in the kitchen...
Now, now, Saint-Juste-sama...
What are you doing?
Give them back!
You mustn't!
Stay the hell outta my business!
Get out! I didn't ask for this!
I hate prying nuisances like you!
Stay the hell outta my business!
But... but I just don't think it's right...
...to ruin one's health with drugs like that...
I'm absolutely convinced of it.
But... I won't be able to visit her apartment ever again.
Get out! I didn't ask for this!
How long has it been since I came to look at the sea?
Here.
You didn't have to accompany me home.
Mid-terms begin tomorrow, right?
You even brought that with you.
But...
No more drugs for me today.
I promise.
Ma cherie La Poupee...
You're calling me that again...
What could it be about the doll?
Is there some memory behind it?
I'll be going.
Okay.
What is it that reflects from within those eyes?
How can... Who can possibly fathom their meaning, my Dear Brother?
Are you?
Um... oh... we met somewhere...
From cram school. Remember?
Hey! Henmi!
Oh, yes, that was it!
Sorry...
That's okay.
Do you... still get letters from Henmi?
Mm... yes... I do!
Really? He hardly ever writes letters!
Excuse me, but do you live in this apartment?
Uh... no, a friend of mine does.
Ah... Here it is...
Well, good-bye...
Bye.
Your "friend"?
Oh no! My flash cards!
Oh well, I'll be okay without them.
It's raining.
Yes...
Does she come here often?
More often than you do...
What do you want?
I wanted to see how you're doing.
What a nice surprise.
Are you still smoking?
You'd better quit. It's not good for you.
My dear Brother...
I regret saying this, but this must remain a S-E-C-R-E-T.
Tomoko!
You're as late as hell! I thought I'd miss the train!
I can't be late for the tests!
And I still have so much to memorize!
Shakespeare... "wrote many books on kidnapping."
Geez, Tomoko! Not "kidnapping"!
Then it's "hito bashira"? No? What then?
I have to buy an eraser!
See you later! Good luck!
Thanks!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Here...
Saint-Juste-sama...
Oh! Saint-Juste-sama!
Are you feeling well now?
Now, this is unusual!
You showed up for the first day of mid-terms!
What's with you?
Why should I force the teachers to give me make-up exams every term?
That's all.
My dear Brother...
Mid-terms have begun.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako is badly shaken to learn Fukiko's secret truth...
...regarding Nanako's admission into the Sorority.
Then a Sorority party is held aboard a yacht,
...and Fukiko has yet another surprise for Nanako.
Next episode: Fukiko; The Sea Rumbles
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...