My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Dear Brother... when it happened, I was looking at the ocean.
I was looking at the beautiful sunset reflected on the ocean.
The sweltering heat of the midday was subsiding,
...and a cool breeze had begun.
Brother...
Brother!
34. Ablution
Look! There's a police car.
One of our students must have done something.
Well, everyone, I'll be going.
See you later!
Orihara-kun! Orihara-kun, wait!
You know Asaka Rei-kun well, is that correct?
Yes...
What are you talking about, sensei...
It is true. The police just notified us about it.
It's a case of mistaken identity.
But...
It's a mistake!
Stop lying to me!
Sunset was over. I waited until 7:30.
Then, I returned home.
I assumed that something urgent had come up,
...so that Saint-Juste-sama couldn't make it there.
That's what I thought.
"She owes me an outing in the future."
...I told myself that to avoid being too disappointed.
And then, I saw Tomoko waiting at the ticket booth.
Though I could see clearly that it was indeed Tomoko there...
...I couldn't fathom why she would be meeting me.
It felt so strange...
Let's go... to the hospital.
The hospital?
Saint-Juste-sama is waiting for you at the hospital.
No no, that's all wrong...
Our meeting place is Shiohama station, Lane 2.
Yeah, but she couldn't make it and...
Oh I see, Tomoko...
...Saint-Juste-sama sent you to ask me to meet her.
Um...
But why the hospital?
Oh... Tomoko... don't cry...
That hurts, Tomoko!
Dear Brother...
I couldn't really understand what Tomoko was saying.
I... I felt like I was in a strange dream again...
That's how it felt.
Over here. This way.
Go inside. That's the room.
That's not right. Her room's on the fifth floor.
Isn't that so?
Stop it, Tomoko you're acting strange.
Soup... yes, I should make her some soup.
Tomoko?
Right? We should make soup before she wakes up.
Isn't that a good idea?
For whom? For whom are you going to make soup?!
You know who it's for!
You know! Surely you know!
No!
Nanako!
Saint-Juste-sama! No!
Excuse me... Excuse me please.
I heard... I heard they won't let us take her body!
Why is that?
Um... these people think she might have...
Suicide?
We haven't determined that, but we don't have the complete picture yet.
As a matter of policy, we must retain the body for forensic examination.
We can release her body to you by tomorrow afternoon.
Her body... Rei's body... mustn't be touched by a scalpel...
If only she left a will...
...but she was alone at a remote location,
and apparently fell into the path of an oncoming train.
There are too many unanswered questions.
Please try to understand.
Thank you for bringing her home, Tomoko-san.
Nanako...
Please call me, for any reason at all.
I will be right over.
Was she someone Nanako knew?
Yes...
She was one year older. I hear she was very kind to Nanako.
Hm.
At around 3:15pm today, the body of a student was found near the Shiohama train station.
She was a second year student at the prestigious Seiran High School.
The body was discovered by a train operator heading in the opposite direction.
At this point, police have been unable to locate any witnesses.
The police have not ruled out suicide.
Suicide?
Not good. Suicide would not be good at all.
Dear...
Can she hold up?
This is probably the most shocking event for Nanako in her life.
Just at the most delicate and sensitive age, she is met with a close friend's death.
Her confusion and pain are probably deeper than we can imagine.
But...
Yes?
She needs to hold up through this.
Yes. She can survive this.
Hm.
I am certain.
Is Ms. Fukiko Ichinomiya present?
Miss? Miss Fukiko?
A bouquet of roses?
I am terribly sorry to bother you at this hour,
...we took this order this afternoon but due to our error the delivery was delayed.
To Ichinomiya Fukiko-san from Asaka Rei-san...
These flowers are for you.
To your bright future, to your beautiful tomorrow,
...and foremost, to your love, with all the gratitude I can express.
For you, just for you... Love, from your one and only sister.
For you, just for you, Love, from your one and only sister...
"With all the gratitude I can express" ...she says.
How can you leave this one little letter behind...
...and then go off and die by yourself, alone?
Who gave you permission to do that?
Does this mean you want me to take that jump myself?
Rei... Rei... Rei!
Rei!
What? Suicide?
It said so in the morning paper.
Really?
No! Saint-Juste-sama!
Saint-Juste-sama has passed away?
Yes, she was taking a lot of drugs.
She had a lot of pills with her.
"Angel of Death"?
Yes. I was shocked to hear that it was suicide,
...but you know, she did fit the profile.
I'd like to get a list of Asaka-san's friends.
Hello, this is Arikura. How is Nanako doing?
She's kept herself in her room since it happened.
She hasn't eaten at all?
Don't worry I take her meals, and she does manage to eat about half...
That's good, then. I just wanted to check how she was doing.
I will come by after school.
Nanako?
Will you be going to school?
Yes... staying at home doesn't help.
Nanako...
I'm going now.
Dear Brother...
At first, I really was going to school.
I believe that was my intention when I left home.
But my feet were going another way.
To the final place.
To that final spot where Saint-Juste-sama had said good bye.
She jumped... Saint-Juste-sama...
...this is where she jumped!
Kaoru-no-Kimi...
What do I do? From now on?
Sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm overwhelmed with my own emotions right now.
I don't think I can help you.
I myself can hardly understand.
Sorry.
Um, do you know...
Is there a place near here with a particularly beautiful sunset?
Sunset?
Did Saint-Juste-sama ever speak to you about it?
Yesterday... Saint-Juste-sama had planned to take me to a place like that.
"Planned"? That trip that Rei had planned was with you?
Yes.
So Rei was passing through here to meet you?
Then... then...
Yes! It was no suicide!
Someone who is committing suicide will not make plans to meet someone!
Thank you. Knowing it wasn't suicide makes me feel better.
But... but it still hurts... the awful reality that she is gone.
It can't change the fact that we will never hear her voice again.
That smile is no more.
There is nothing anymore!
Nothing at all!
Dear Brother...
Like yesterday, today was very hot.
Pardon the interruption again...
Please be seated.
You are acquainted with Misonoo Nanako-san?
Yes.
According to Misonoo-san, they had planned an outing yesterday.
The overpass was a shortcut, and it seems she took it to save time.
We don't have confirmation from Misonoo-san's parents yet,
...but Arikura-san provided confirmation that the trip had been planned.
We will return the body to you this evening.
The police have concluded that it was an accident.
We have an eye witness.
He is a delivery person who happened to pass by.
He was late for his three o'clock appointment.
He says he saw her fall.
She tried to reach for the flowers.
Flowers?
She tried to grab the flowers that she dropped, and fell.
And he also said this...
Asaka-san flew very, very high.
It was terribly unfortunate. A train was coming.
She flew high in the air, like a bird in flight.
High...
Now... my heart has found great strength for living.
Dear Brother...
There is a place with the most beautiful sunset,
...but its location will forever be a mystery.
Rei, you gave me these roses.
Dear Sister, this is your final gift.
I loved you.
You understood that, didn't you?
Rei... Rei...
I'm lonely.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...