My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
"Education?"
Kyouiku.
Next: "polite"?
Teinei-na.
"Individual"?
Tandoku-no, koko-no,dokutoku-no.
"Trend?"
Sonohou e muke, katamuku, hucho...
"Unbecoming?"
Hm? Mm...
Niawa nai, husouou-na...
That's it!
She'll be back in school beginning today, Shinobu-san.
Mm?
Mid-terms are next week, and she feels much better.
Mmm...
Why don't we have lunch together some time. The three of us.
What do you say?
I'll think about it!
My dear brother...
Shinonu Mariko-san is coming back to school.
It was partly my fault,
and I can't say everything is going to be the same,
...but I'd rather that we forget all the unpleasant things,
...and concentrate on these coming mid-terms instead.
Stop the car! Right here is fine.
Take this.
The one you wanted, a Jean Saint-Teauille first edition...
But it's so precious, you said you'd never part with it...
You'd prefer I weren't so... changeable?
No...
11. Under the Elm Tree
Sorority members: please assemble at the Sorority House at once.
Look! Sorority members!
They're going to the Sorority House!
They'll study there for the midterms.
The senior members always help the junior members study.
They're so lucky.
I'm envious!
As you know, mid-terms start next week.
The Sorority expects all our new members to do well, of course.
This will be the first major exam for our new members...
...and I must remind you that our rules require that you place in the top 50.
The top 50!
But there is nothing to worry about.
Our senior members are here to help our junior members study.
This is our Sorority's tradition.
Perhaps you'd like to see the kind of questions...
...you can expect to find in Seiran's exams?
We'll start this afternoon.
Since it is the first day, we'll meet at my house.
We can enjoy tea and study.
How wonderful to be able to go to Miya-sama's house!
I'll see you all this afternoon.
Shinobu-san?
Yes?
You were hospitalized recently?
Yes.
Don't forget that being healthy is another requirement of the Sorority.
But, I'm glad your hospitalization was a short one.
Thank you very much.
It may start raining...
It was so beautiful this morning.
Is Jean Saint-Teauille to your liking?
Yes!
Sorority members are getting together at my house today.
Do you want to come?
To my house?
To your house?
Yes, to my house.
I will take you to my house.
Wait for me at five o'clock under the elm tree in the court yard.
All right?
After school, all junior members were divided into groups.
We got into the senior members's cars...
...and headed to Fukiko-sama's house.
The darkened sky seemed ready to shed raindrops like tears.
Though I was excited, I also felt somewhat anxious and uneasy.
Perhaps I was feeling a premonition of the unforgettable event...
...which was about to unfold before me.
Please do come in.
We'll be serving tea and cakes.
Yes, this "Nubatama-no" is a Makura Kotoba modifying "night".
Makura Kotoba will be covered on the mid-term.
Yes, this requires factoring.
Underline in red the rule on page 90 of your text book.
It's an important point.
Spring goes, and summer comes.
Ame-no-kaguyama, where the gods dry their white robes.
You must not only memorize this poem,
but make sure you understand the meaning also.
Wherefore du I hesitate, though my heart is at your side?
Good. Next, the Spring Poem by Ootomo Yakamochi?
Though the sky is clouded with snowflakes falling.
The nightingale chirps in the garden of my house.
If one could die from only a though...
Surely I would have dies one thousan times by now.
Wow, it's raining hard!
Continue, Misonoo-san...
The dark of the night is a painful thing,
will the moon I await not shine for me soon?
What's wrong, Nanako-san?
What's the matter, Misonoo-san?
Oh my, I'm sorry... I left my French reading book and notebook at school!
I'll go back to pick them up!
But it's raining.
Suppose we study mathematics instead of French today...
Yes, but I have a homework due tomorrow, and I need my notebook...
Well... Then I'll have my driver take you there.
I won't hear of it! It's okay, I'll be right back.
Darn! I've forgotten my umbrella...
Take this.
Thank you! I'm very grateful...
Rain during this season is very cold.
Thank you very much!
Did you see that? Miya-sama lavishes her attention on Misonoo-san.
Yeah...
Even the studying Miya-sama has been teaching only Misonoo-san.
Do you think it's true?
"It"?
What "It"?
The rumour that it was Miya-sama alone who insisted that Misonoo-san be chosen.
Hold it, what do you mean—
Everyone...
Let's take another break for tea.
That song... it's the one Saint-Juste is always playing...
Here it is!
Exhaustion and relief, combined with the steady soothing sound of raindrops,
...made the classroom feel like a quiet haven at the bottom of the sea...
But now it was dark outside. I had been asleep over an hour.
Oh, no! I've got to go back!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Saint-Juste-sama! Saint-Juste-sama!
You're soaking! You'll catch a cold, Saint-Juste-sama!
What are you doing here?
Why was she there, wet and alone under that elm tree?
...I had no idea then and what could she be thinking...
She was cold as ice, soaked to the bone, and couldn't even talk.
So I took her to her home, using the address on her student ID.
Saint-Juste-sama, are you okay?
Snap out of it! Come to your senses!
Itlu-chome, you said?
Yes! 1-17-15 Maison d'Eduard.
Saint-Juste-sama!
I'm taking you to your home.
Fukiko-sama...
I was to wait there!
...wait... for Fukiko-sama!
Whaddaya think you're doing!?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Watch out!
I'm leaving you here!
I don't need this kind of trouble!
Saint-Juste-sama!
I need to get back.
To the elm tree.
Saint-Juste-sama!
That's the opposite direction from your home!
I must go.
To where?
She's... feverish!
I must get back...
No, you mustn't! You have a fever!
You need to go home! Please go home!
Otherwise... otherwise I'll...
Saint-Juste-sama!
Please! Please wait!
Yes, sweet peas...
Thank you very much.
I'll... I'll give these to you...
So...
don't pay any mind to me... anymore.
Thanks.
Saint-Juste-sama!
I can't make Kukiko-sama wait.
Miya-sama?
She's going to take me to her home.
She told me to wait, at 5 o'clock, under the elm tree.
But... Miya-sama...
Miya-sama is already at her home!
You're a bad girl.
Such a liar!
That was no lie!
I must hurry...
Fukiko-sama... Fukiko-sama, I'm coming right now...
NO!
Don't... Saint-Juste-sama... you mustn't...
Is this the place?
No... wait... I'll open it.
I'll do it!
Ok...
Mirrors?
Mirrors...and so many of them!
Where is everyone?
"Everyone"?
There is no "everyone" here.
Alone?
She lives here alone, surrounded by mirrors?
Ma cherie La Poupee...
Where's the bathroom? Where is it?
You have to dry off and change right now! Which way is it?
Ma cherie La Poupee....
Ma cherie La Poupee...
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Kaoru-no-Kimi arrives at Rei's apartment...
She slaps Rei and angrily rips the bracelet from her wrist!
And Nanako can now see what was concealed beneath the bracelet...
Next episode: The Scar
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...