My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
You shameless bitch!
Fukiko-sama!
That song is the one I hate the most in the world!
24. Encore
Why?
Why did she say she hates it?
I knew perfectly well it was her favorite piece.
Why?
Why did she get so upset when I played it?
Nanako! What are you doing?
The 12-minute-after train is coming!
What happened to you this morning?
She hasn't been back since last night.
What? Who? Where?
If you don't know, don't ask!
Ok I won't!
My Dear Brother...
I don't understand. Not at all.
About Saint-Juste-sama and Miya-sama.
But, though I can't understand the world they share...
...I know that their kind of world frightens me.
As I see the increasing gloom in Saint-Juste's eyes,
...and the rage hidden behind Miya-sama's kindness,
...I understand their world less and less.
The 25-after bus! The 25-after bus!
Darn!
What'll I do...
My first-period English teacher, Kusunoki, is very strict!
I'm sorry!
Rei!
Hello.
I'm always telling you, don't smoke in this car.
So I do it anyway.
Hey, now!
Can I... play this?
Sure.
That music!
Are you still upset over yesterday?
I thought you might know something...
This violin music...
That piece... once... was one Fukiko practiced very hard on.
I was a freshman then... Six years ago, in the summer.
Six years ago?
I remember that summer very well.
We stayed at the vacation house, near the lake.
Henmi visited us there too.
Henmi Takehiko?
Though he only stayed for one week.
When summer ended,
...we had a farewell party, inviting the neighbors.
Henmi promised that he'd be back for the party.
He promised.
He said, he'd be back, for sure.
That's when Fukiko suddenly started practicing that song.
She said she was going to play it at the farewell party.
She practiced hard everyday, sometimes until midnight.
She must have really been looking forward to it.
She asked my opinion of it over and over.
And?
At the party, Fukiko did play that violin piece.
And what beautiful playing it was!
It was hard to believe it was being played by a 12 year old.
Henmi heard it, too?
No, he never showed up.
Oh?
He called right before the party.
He said there was an emergency, and he couldn't come.
When she finished playing, the guests applauded with admiration.
They were even asking for an encore.
An encore.
But she didn't respond with an encore.
Not only that, but she never played that piece again.
Never?
In fact I haven't even seen her pick up a violin since then.
How did you hear that song, Rei?
I've heard it many times.
When I think back, it was only when she was alone,
...or no one else was around, that she would play it.
I watched from the distance, without being noticed.
I see. That was it.
And then?
Hm?
After that, did Henmi visit often?
No... I'm fairly certain... that was the first and last visit he made.
I see.
Could it be?
Could it be what?
No. It's nothing.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Today, I met with Rei.
She came to the university to see me.
Any special reason?
No. We just had a talk.
On what subject?
About 6 years ago, at our vacation home.
Is that so.
And about Henmi.
Oh no!
A single ugly rose has vulgarized this whole arrangement!
That damned girl... this is not her business!
Fukiko-sama, I didn't know.
I honestly didn't know.
You were practicing that song just for him.
Just for him, for Henmi Takehiko.
You put your heart in it, you put your soul in it,
...but he never came back.
Isn't that right?
I didn't know! I really didn't know!
That summer day,
When I first met him,
Henmi... Takehiko.
Fukiko!
It's dangerous here! I told you not to come here alone.
I'm sorry, my brother.
Let me introduce you to a classmate from school, Henmi Takehiko.
This is my sister, Fukiko.
My name is Henmi. Good afternoon.
I'll be staying here for a while.
That day, everything seemed aglow,
...as if everything took place in a warm dream.
Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?
No, Thou art more lovely and more temperate.
Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May...
Hi!
This is a book of Shakespeare's poems.
Shakespeare?
Yes, I have to write a report.
Please, read some.
What?
Please read something to me.
...the poem that you like the best.
Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May,
And summer's lease...
...hath all too short a date.
This is no use... it's just as bad as outside.
Once more...
What?
Please read that poem once more.
Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?
No, Thou art more lovely and more temperate.
Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May,
And summer's lease hath all too short a date,
Sometime too hot the eye of heaven shines,
and often is his gold complexion dimm'd,
And every fair from fair sometime declines,
By chance, or nature's changing course, untrimm'd,
But the eternal summer shall not fade,
not lose possession of that beauty thou possessest,
nor shall Death brag thou wander'st in his shade,
When in eternal lines to time thou growest
I love this poem as well!
I love it!
The book is yours, then.
I have another copy.
Is it true what I heard?
You're really leaving tomorrow?
Yes. But I promise I'll be back for the party.
Can you promise me that?
Of course!
Then...
Okay, all right.
That summer's day.
The sweetest, brightest day of my whole life.
I was so happy then.
Saint-Juste-sama?
Saint-Juste-sama!
This is the song!
The same song!
Do you come here often?
W-what?
Do you come here very often?
Well I... I did when Saint-Juste-sama caught a cold...
...several times, actually...
But since then, I haven't—
I warned you back then...
Didn't I warn you back then to not get involved with her?
Y-yes!
My Dear Brother,
What was that all about?
Why did Miya-sama become so upset?
Just being in her room isn't reason enough.
That song... it must somehow be the song...
I was only 12. But my heart died on that summer's day.
We have so many guests here tonight!
Especially since you're going to play the violin...
...twice as many people came this year!
My red shoes! Tonight I need my red shoes!
Yes, right away!
Brother!
Does this look good? Red shoes?
Yes! Looks great. Are they new?
Yes. I got them especially for tonight!
One moment, Fukiko. There was a phone call.
That just can't be true, brother.
He had some kind of emergency.
Until this morning, he was planning to come.
But... he made a promise to me!
Come on, everyone is waiting.
Show them all the results of all your practicing.
After tonight, I'll be known as the brother of a violin prodigy!
So I played on in desperation...
With a pleasant smile, even...
...despite the thorns that were piercing my heart.
That summer night's party, in my 12th year...
...my first and last happiness died forever.
That was magnificent, Miss Fukiko!
Where are you going!?
Don't follow me! I won't forgive you if you follow me!
Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?
No, Thou art more lovely and more temperate.
But thy eternal summer shall not fade,
Nor shall Death brag thou wander'st in his shade,
In eternal lines to time thou growest.
No!
That sweetest day, that summers day,
...even if I was betrayed,
...it is mine, forever mine, and mine alone,
...until the day that he returns with me to that summer's day.
I won't allow anyone else to have him.
No matter who it is.
No matter who!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Fukiko suddenly summons Nanako to the Sorority House.
She approaches, drawing her lips close to Nanako's ears...
...when Rei suddenly rushes in, and reveals a secret,
...which gives Nanako the shock of her life.
Next episode: Crimson Lipstick
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...