My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
What is this about?
You know already.
Yes.
This is the elm tree where Rei waited for you yesterday!
She got soaked and caught a fever!
Don't you care at all what happens to Rei!?
It is of no concern to me.
But Rei...
But Rei is your younger sister!
13. A Tale of Double Suicide
Who's there?
Wait, please.
I haven't finished!
I don't need to waste my time listening to this.
Rei...
Did Rei send you here?
I'm certain she would never ask you to speak to me.
Regardless... you're an outsider, and must stay out of this.
Despite your friendship and despite your feelings.
Good day.
Her sister?
Saint-Juste is Miya-sama's sister?
No way... Can it be true?
Oh, my Brother...
Chigusa-Cho... 1-17-15 Maison d'Eduard.
Room 507.
An icy room filled with mirrors...
...a light in the kitchen that doesn't work...
...that's Saint-Juste's... that's her room...
That's her lonely room... her lonely little world.
My dear Brother... the sandwich I left for her...
That sandwich remains untouched at her door.
So... are you in your room right now? Or out?
My phone calls are all that can penetrate your world.
I can't enter your world myself.
I can only hope that you will open your door of your own free will...
...smiling, and saying "Hi"...
...emerging from your deep, dark, mysterious world.
From your private world.
I heard today that you are Miya-sama's sister.
The two of you have different last names.
How could this be? And what does it mean?
But, those things aside, are you eating well?
What about your fever?
I worry about you...
But Rei...
But Rei is your younger sister!
I've been looking for you all over, Rei!
What on earth are you doing out with a fever like that!
Leave me alone.
Let's go home.
You have to rest.
Tell me... please... did you visit the elm tree?
Yes.
She was waiting for me, right?
Mm...
Did you tell her why I wasn't there?
Did you explain it all?
Stop your nonsense.
Why won't you be reasonable!
Um... hello? Yes, Asaka....
S-Saint-Juste-sama!
How are you? How do you feel? Did you eat something?
Some soup.
I'm fixing some for her.
Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Oh, thank goodness! You're there with her!
I'm so relieved! Saint-Juste isn't alone!
She's sleeping right now.
She's still got a bit of fever, but it's nothing to worry about.
I'm coming over now!
Don't you know what time it is?
It's well past the time for freshmen to be out.
I'll get to the convenience store... and brings lots of good food...
No, don't. I'll hang up now.
Um... what kind of food... does Saint-Juste like?
Huh? Who knows...
Come to think of it... I don't remember ever seeing her enjoy eating...
Anyway, I'm coming!
I'd like to take a shower.
I won't allow it. Not with your fever.
Rei, what's the matter?
Rei!
If I could only wash it off...
...I want to wash all of it off!
I'm cold.
No wonder.
Here... here it is.
How about coffee? I'll make some.
Before you do that, maybe you should help me get her dressed.
Saint-Juste remained asleep the entire time I was there in her room with her.
This is fine here.
I'll catch a cab at the main street.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
You shouldn't go to school after getting no sleep all night.
I'll be fine. I'm good at handling hardships.
We can only wait for her...
Huh?
When she finally gives up fighting this thing alone,
...that's when she'll come to us for help.
So that she can get over it.
So that she can finally get over this agony and start to live again.
Waiting this out is a test of my friendship.
But she can be very trying...
Take care.
Thanks.
My Dear Brother...
This thing which connects them both so closely...
...is this what true friendship is?
If that is how real friendship works, it's so different from me and Tomoko.
We are much more selfish about our friendship.
We think of friendship as something which entitles,
...not as something which obligates.
They are only a year older than us...
...yet they are so much more kind to each other, so much more patient.
It's hard to understand why and how that could be.
Unless it is something more special than mere friendship.
Unless this is a deeper bond based on some kind of doomed emotion...
Ah... the sun is shining, everything is lush and green!
This is a heaven of dancing birds, glistening water, and singing flowers...
...all telling me to be happy!
But despite all this loveliness, a doom awaits us.
A terrible doom! Also known as "mid-terms"...
Tomoko-san!
You should eat something before afternoon classes start!
No thanks... I'm too depressed to have an appetite.
...but-but-but!
But eating is my way of fighting back!
Anyway, it helps me keep a positive attitude.
I envy all you Sorority members!
You guys are different from us... you look so confident.
Hey, I'm not confident!
I know about your cram sessions.
Your Sorority sisters are telling you what's covered on the tests!
Yes, but not all that's covered.
Please, Nanako, you're my friend!
Now you can prove your friendship!
Prove me?
Loan me your cram school notes! I'll make a copy and return them!
Oh! Please? Mariko, you too, please?
It was early afternoon after lunch...
...that was when the strange rumors began.
The first one was that piano music was heard in the music hall...
...but there was no one inside.
Another one was that during 4th period,
...footsteps were heard in the empty north building,
...going up and down, up and down the stairs.
Did you hear it?
Wow, that's scary!
Is it true?
Then there was the third rumor.
It gave me a bit of a chill.
That there was a sound from the elm tree,
...a deep, soulful, sad sobbing... ...carried aloft by the wind,
...which was heard from as far away as the library.
Those substances which oxidize other materials are called oxidants.
While oxidizing other materials, oxidants themselves are reduced during the process.
What?
Nanako-san, you're so naive!
We always hear these sorts of rumors just before exams.
Before exams?
Yes... everyone gets so terribly stressed and nervous!
So they start mixing up fact and fiction like that...
Mm... I get it.
Perhaps you could say it is a tradition here at Seiran...
The rumors before last year's exams were even scarier!
The story is that someone was seen at the piano in the music hall.
The scary thing was that there were actually two of them...
One was a splendid woman in men's attire, a white tuxedo;
The other was a female student in a hakama.
Every afternoon they were seen,
...climbing the stairs of the north building, up and down,
...in the fading light of the sunset.
They were said to be Seiran seniors from the beginning of the Showa era.
And they were doomed lovers.
Finally, they cut their wrists with a razor,
...together, under the elm tree, in the rain...
Somehow, those two always reappear at exam time!
Actually, I think it's a deliciously romantic story...
Hm... that elm tree, in the courtyard... it has such a history!
Why?
What?
Why did they have to die?
I don't know.
But it must have made them happy...
...being able to die with someone they loved...
Wait. Hey! Are you implying something?
Well, Nanako-san, let's go to the Sorority house!
Our cram session is about to start.
Well, off I go. See you tomorrow, Tomoko-san!
Ah... um... oh!
Good luck! Don't forget the notes!
Nanako, what's the matter?
Eh? Nothing...
You were up all night.
What?
That's okay, I guess.
Well! Study hard, then, at your cram session.
Bye!
Bye, Tomoko!
Oh, Tomoko...
It's coming from the music hall...
Is something wrong?
Go on ahead to the Sorority house, everyone.
I'll be there shortly.
I'm sure of it! That melody!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Hello.
So you came here.
Are you well?
I waited. Forever.
Forever!
Under that elm tree.
I heard you've had a fever.
That's not good.
Very bad. Your fever is still high.
I'd like you to go home. To your room.
Rest yourself there.
All right.
Saint-Juste-sama!
Be here! Saint-Juste-sama, you have to be here!
Saint-Juste-sama! Fukiko-sama!
I've been waiting!
All this time... all this time...
I knew you would someday keep your promise to me!
Fukiko-sama!
No! I'm not her!
It's just as you told me then...
...you've come here so we can... die together...
Saint-Juste-sama!
...you said... we could die together...
She's mad! She's gone completely mad!
Brother!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Rei embraces Nanako, insisting that they die together.
Though she struggles to escape from the deranged Rei...
...Nanako ends up cornered against the wall.
Rei draws her knife...
What is the madness which flashes in her eyes?
Next episode: The Secret Door
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...