My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
My Dear Brother, I'm finally here!
At your school, for the Gakuin University Fair.
So many people!
Yeah! University fairs are so different from the high school ones.
This is so exciting!
What's wrong, Mariko-san?
What?
You're so tense, especially your shoulders.
And why not, after all?
Protecting you two from all the males here is a grave responsibility.
Let's go!
What? But... wait a second!
I don't remember anyone asking her for protection!
What was that?!
There! They're here!
Hi! Glad you're here!
I'm very grateful that you sent me an invitation.
My pleasure! Thanks for coming.
May I present my friends, Shinobu Mariko-san and Arikura Tomoko-san.
I'm Henmi Takehiko.
How do... ...you do.
Hi Henmi-sensei, it's been a long time!
Huh?
I was in the same cram school with Nanako.
The name is Arikura.
Oh! It's you!
Sorry, we tagged along today.
Oh, the more the merrier!
Uh... This... this is my friend.
I'm Ichinomiya Takashi. Glad to meet you.
You said... Ichinomiya?
So you are...
Yes. He's Miya-sama's brother.
Huh?
Oh wow!
I understand you all attend Seiran with my sister.
Glad you came. Pleased to meet you.
This is a typical "guy" strategy!
They pretend to shake hands for "friendship",
...but they're probably already planning their next move!
Huh?
Even if he's Miya-sama's brother, he's still a guy!
So don't let down your guard.
Bleh!
21. The University Fair
How about it? Where shall we start?
How about the movies?
Our university's movie study-group is highly regarded.
Sounds interesting!
Yeah! I want to see that!
No way! Movies, of all things!
How obvious can you get?
Movies, as you well know, are shown in dark rooms!
And now for some magic with cards.
There is a gorgeous lady in our midst, with a diamond ring,
...my heart is on fire. Our love is in spades!
Watch out, both of you.
Huh?
Using this type of comedy...
...it's an attempt to put us at ease.
That should be obvious to anyone!
Here is a 140 to 1 scale model of Neuschwanstein Castle in Germany.
Very well made.
Rudreich the 2nd had it built in the 17th century.
It took him 17 years...
What an amateur you are!
...showing off knowledge, using a woman's feelings of inferiority...
...anyone can see through that!
A Haunted House! It looks like fun!
A Haunted house?
I haven't been in one since Junior High.
Shall we try it? It'll bring back memories.
Yes! I love these things!
Shinobu-san, don't you dare oppose this one!
I won't oppose it, but, let's separate into two groups...
Males go with males and females go with females.
This is sort of scary!
That's why we should have had them come with us.
Don't you get it?
They'd only invite girls into a place like this if they had ulterior motives.
Ulterior motives?
What sort of "ulterior motive"?
I'd rather hug the ghost than them, in this panic and confusion...
This is just an old familiar trick.
So what do you want?
Help me!
Uh... Are you okay?
Uh...
Aieeeee!
I've never been so humiliated in my life!
Humiliated? Wasn't it you that ran into me?
You shouldn't have been there!
And look, why do you have to sit so close to me?
Move further away.
Oh...sorry...
Further!
Yes, Ma-am...
Mariko-san! Please behave yourself!
Um... listen!
What is it?
Your vigilance in this respect is truly admirable,
...but come on, let's relax and have some fun.
This is our University Fair!
I didn't come here to have fun!
I came here to protect Nanako-san and Tomoko-san!
I'm completely at a loss.
Why do you hate men so much?
They are selfish... dirty... and the cruelest creatures on earth.
How can you say all men are like that?
How can you say they're not!
I can certainly say that I', not!
It's true! Men are all talk but no deed!
Henmi!
It's time to meet and be heard!
Assemble with us to defend our cultural heritage.
Exercise your constitutional right to free speech!
Doesn't it seem like there are more people here, now?
At 2 o'clock there's a concert in the gym.
It's an amateur band, and fairly popular.
A rock group. Do you want to go?
Yes!
I know them! They're "Mercury"! I love them!
Would you like a balloon?
No. Balloons always burst and too soon.
So, you dislike things that don't last?
You're a delicate one, aren't you.
And you're pretentious.
Look!
What?
Huh?
What happened to them?
They're lost?
I wonder if Mariko-san is okay?
She'll be okay. She's with Ichinomiya-san.
Now we can have some fun.
Hey!
Please! Slow down!
Can't you please stop following me!
I can't leave you alone!
I'm responsible for you!
Until I find Henmi and the others, I'm your bodyguard!
I'll have nothing of the sort!
If not a bodyguard, then, consider me a "practice date".
You make my flesh crawl.
All right then, all right.
By the way, where were you going?
To the public address booth. I'll have them page Nanako-san.
Not in this auxiliary buildings. That would be in the main building.
What?
Besides... during school fairs, they don't make announcements.
Stay at least one meter away from me.
That won't be easy...
Any further away from you, and we might be separated too.
If we get separated, that'll suit me fine.
Now, now...
Ichinomiya-san!
Hi!
A friend. In my class.
Is that so?
Ichinomiya-sempai!
Why don't you try shooting? I'll give you a discount.
Sure. But later.
She's in my ski club.
Hey, it's been a while!
Hi! How have you been?
And this lovely lady... your girlfriend?
We're complete strangers.
Well, see you later.
Uh... sure!
You certainly have a lot of female friends.
Oh! Oh?
I guess... you know, being a university student...
All men are like that.
They can't be satisfied with just one girl.
You're prejudiced.
I'd be very happy with one girl. But I need to have friends also.
Whatever you're male or female, try to make a friend whenever you can.
Don't presume to give me advice.
Oh yeah?
Yes!
What else looks interesting?
We've seen most of them...
We had so much fun! Really!
Yeah! This was our first university fair!
It's been so exciting!
In three years, you may be the ones putting on a fair.
What? Huh?
Is that too far ahead to think about?
Yes. It's just too distant in the future.
Wow... three years!
I could be walking hand in hand with my boyfriend...
By the way, do you have a girlfriend, Henmi-san?
What?
I must admit, it hadn't occurred to me before...
...but it wouldn't surprise me if my Brother has a girlfriend.
Oh, I'm sorry! Was that an improper question?
No girlfriend. Not right now.
Satisfied?
Well! You dodged that one! A different subject, then.
How did you come to select this university?
Well, now... in order to answer that question...
I gave you an easy one, this time!
That's right, my dear Brother.
I really don't know anything about you.
I wrote you so many long letters,
...they must've been a burden to you.
But I've only been thinking of myself.
You're such a considerate and gentle person.
Taking advantage of your generosity... is not very nice.
It's wrong of me, it really is.
Cotton candy!
It looks so good!
I'll go get some for you, too!
Thinking about something?
Huh?
You've been so quiet.
Oh! That was just...
I was just starting to worry a bit...
Worry?
Yes... It was selfish of me to make you be my "Brother".
You must be terribly busy with your studies, and everything else...
And so I'm worried...
...that I've become a burden to you.
A burden? I never thought of it that way.
Reading your letters reminds me of my own high school days.
Back then, the most trivial things could make me happy or angry.
Your letters bring all those feelings back to me.
Now, I look forward to checking my mailbox.
Really?
Really! It's true. Speaking of which...
Huh? Yes?
When's the next letter?
Where could they have gone?
In a crowd like this, it'll be next to impossible to find them.
It's like looking for a contact lens in a swimming pool.
But it's okay. We can always just wait for them at the main gate.
Look over here... Don't girls love this sort of things?
It's all nonsense!
Really? It looks fun! Whether it's true or not.
But... I guess I'll try it anyway.
You are strong-willed.
Is it strong will, or just a "hard-head"?
Shut up!
You are bright, and you have good luck with money.
Except...
Except?
Except there's a problem related to your family...
Your parents are...
Stop it!
How did you... What do you know about it!
I've had enough of this nonsense!
Hey! Wait!
300 Yen.
Hey girl! You alone?
How'd you like us to show you around?
We're students here.
Don't get uppity, now. Get that serious look off your face.
Well, hey... there's a disco party at 5 o'clock.
We wanted to go, 'cept for being just 2 guys alone...
Hey, listen here, wait up!
Let go of me!
Leave me alone!
I can't stand to be touched by your filthy hands!
I hate scum like you!
Stop following me! Get lost!
Get away from me right now!
I'm sorry. I'm a failure as a bodyguard.
Shall we go? Everyone's staring.
Leave yourself, if you're so concerned about what they think.
Or you can just stay and watch me like them.
All right, I understand. I'll wait until you're ready.
Let's go. This is foolish.
Hey Henmi!
Mariko-san!
I figured you'd be here!
Yes... when lost, one should backtrack to the point of origin.
I'm so glad. I was worried that we'd never find you!
You won't believe what happened... it was terrible.
Since we're finally back together, why don't we go for some coffee?
Yes, let's!
Don't be absurd!
It's time to go home!
What... Why can't we all have coffee?
But don't you see?
While we're drinking coffee, the sun will set!
Before we know it, it'll be totally dark!
No it won't!
Yes it will!
Let's go! Good bye!
Mariko-san!
Wait a second! Shinobu-san!
Oh! Oops! Thank you very much for today!
You're welcome...
Wait up!
You're too fast! Wait!
No, I won't wait!
You don't know how men change into dangerous wolves after dark!
What a girl!
It must've been terrible being stuck with her.
No...
I kind of liked it.
What?
I got to liking her.
Thank you Nanako!
Because of you I had such a good time!
Because of me?
Yes! Because you became a sister of Henmi-sensei.
That's right!
But, Mariko-san was so uptight today.
Her man-hating thing seems a little sick... I wonder why she does that...
Well, there's a problem. A complex problem in her family.
Is that so?
No, no, no!
The time flies when we're having fun,
...but tomorrow, it's back to school again.
...or so it seems...
This is heavy!
Yes!
Apple tea, your favorite.
Wow!
How was it, at the university?
I had fun! But there were so many people.
It was a little overwhelming.
Well. You're lucky you had someone to show you around.
Yes!
So... take your bath now.
Ok!
Brother, Dear Brother...
For the warmth of your company,
...and this wonderful, gentle day together,
...I would like to express my sincere gratitude.
Thank you very very much!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Visiting Fukiko's vacation home to help prepare for Fukiko's birthday party,
...she is stunned to overhear Fukiko's mournful suffering.
The following day, before Nanako's eyes, Fukiko jumps into the lake.
Next episode: A Summer's Serenade
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...