My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
...then Lebrand picked up the scythe, and cleared with it a circular space,
...three or four yards in diameter, just below the insect.
Then he told Jupiter to let the string go, and come down from the tree.
That's good. Next, Miss Misonoo.
Yes...
Lebrand placed a small stick into the ground
...at the exact place where the insect was buried.
He took from his pocket a long tape measure. He fastened it down and...
Resign, of your own volition.
We can't tolerate such an injustice!
...he went in front of his master, clearing away the bushes with a spade.
Ok, that will do.
What's wrong? You seem unwell!
Yes, well...
Next, Miss Yoshimoto...
Yes!
At the distance of fifty feet, Lebrand stopped,
...and put the second stick into the ground.
The ground around it was again cleared in a large circle, about four feet deep...
"The unqualified person should leave the Sorority.."
Such poor losers.
Don't let it bother you.
Ok...
Stand!
I found a nice Kyoto-style coffee shop at the train station!
I'm going home.
Come on, let's go!
No, go ahead without me.
It's really good. Their shiratama is wonderful!
I need to throw these in the incinerator.
What's that?
I found them in my desk this morning...
7. The Darkness in the Clock Tower
Brother...
I don't understand what's wrong.
I don't understand what's so hateful about me.
I wanted to be liked by everyone.
I wanted to be liked just a little, enough not to be hurt, or to hurt someone.
That was enough and is still enough for me.
Then, why am I hated so much...
...by so many?
What did I do?
What have I done to deserve this?
What is... What on earth is wrong with me?
I can't... I can't stand it!
So... this is the clock tower?
"M-sama, thinking of you has turned me into ashes."
"Say you love me once again. That will restore the life in me."
"I want you."
I'm not alone.
There have been many before me who came here to cry.
When they lost their courage to continue, they would come to this dark tower.
When they lost love, and when they lost friendship...
They found, in this tower, a place to escape
...to embrace themselves and wet their knees with their warm tears...
Last year, the year before last, and many many years before that...
So many sisters over these many years, coming here to share their pain...
What was that sound?
Saint-Juste-sama...
Smoking... she's smoking?
She... she is bad!
Excuse me?
Pick them up, won't you...
What?
Oh! Ok.
I see...
This must have been the sound I heard earlier...
There are so many marks here.
She's done this before.
What's this?
...this silhouette!
It's Miya-sama! It's a silhouette of Miya-sama!
Thanks.
Um...
Is that Miya-sama?
Yes.
But why?
They are so deep and so... many.
Like the rains which fall in this world...
What?
...the tears also fall in my heart.
What is it for, the sadness which creeps into my heart...
What is this sadness for?
Saint-Juste...
The name has an echo of loneliness in it...
And about Saint-Juste-sama and Miya-sama...
...there is a mystery between them I cannot understand.
Like the rain...
...the tears fall in my heart.
Saint-Juste...
Who named her Saint-Juste?
Who on earth... is Saint Juste?
I only have twelve minutes to catch that train, or I'll be late!
Twelve Minutes! Finally!
She won't be able to go home together with you from now on.
As a member of the Sorority, she has a lot of socializing to do.
She asked me to tell you this.
I want to hear from her directly! Where is she?!
Being her friend, can't you understand why...
What do you mean by that!
That's why she asked me to tell you.
I'd not be so easily hurt if she told me herself!
Good Morning.
Can I... call you some time?
Maybe?
Oh, Misonoo-san!
Let's go shopping for material for the pajamas we're sewing!
Oh, for home economics class...
It's early next week. So let's go today?
Oh! Well... I don't think...
You're busy with something else?
Yes, sort of... the library!
I have to find a book there...
If I don't go today, I'd have to go next week.
So you see...
You hard worker, you!
No, no, that's not it...
I get it! You're in a jam.
In that case, I'll choose your pattern too.
What?
That way you can go to the library!
Can I borrow your light?
If you're caught, you'll be suspended from school... or expelled!
I adore expulsion.
I'll take those.
And I adore...
Here!
Does your wound still hurt?
No...
Good.
Let's see... um...
Where shall I start?
You'll find it on the shelf over there.
Oh! Thanks...
Wait! The shelf over there? What?
You want to learn about The French Revolution and Saint-Juste.
Yes! But... but how...
The freshmen will all be in front of these books.
on the French Revolution and Saint-Juste in three months.
Well... I didn't mean that...
Hey, no problem!
Reading for any reason is always better then not reading at all.
I'll show you where they are.
Sorry for the trouble...
Let's see, there's this, and this...
And finally, this.
Thanks...
So funny!
But then I saw Ide-san and Kooriyama-san at the Paris Hotel...
No way!
Wow!
And then? What then?
Well, you know Urayama-san...
Hey, where do you think you are?
This is a library. If you want to talk, go outside.
Ok.
Excuse me, I'd like to borrow these.
One can't even read peacefully in the library these days!
You like books so much, Kaoru-sama?
Surprised?
Well... a bit.
I've heard that from someone else...
Saint-Juste-sama!
Yes.
Rei was transferred into our school in junior high school.
She was really different.
She seemed to always be alone, reading books...
...showing no interest in her surroundings.
Watch out!
Cool!
What are you reading?
I'm sure it wouldn't interest you... being such an athlete...
Oh, it's Verlaine.
What?
"As rain falls..."
Right?
Not bad!
Pretty cool!
Now we're even.
Then I recruited Rei for our basketball team.
She played basketball!?
She easily became a star player.
She had such life in her when she was playing basketball...
...and her eyes glowed.
That's why I liked watching her...
...or so I told myself.
But that wasn't it.
But, what really attracted me to her...
...was something inhuman in her nature;
and those eyes with such a distant, far-away look...
Far away?
What does she see so far away? What lies deep within her soul?
What could it be?
That smells good!
Cookies are baking!
Oh yes... it must be from Tomoko's cooking club...
You're really something!
Making overtures not only to Miya-sama, but now to Kaoru-no-Kimi as well.
You took after your mother the "hostess"...
...who will... with anyone, right?
So what do you want?
Here. You left it at school.
What?
It was in the incinerator!
Look at that... Miss Sorority has fallen!
Nanako!
Are you all right? Nanako! Nanako!
You! What did you do to Nanako?
W-hat? We didn't do anything!
That's right! She just fell down by herself!
If you mess with Nanako, you'll be facing me for it!
If you ever treat her mean you'll be dealing with me. Got that?
Tomoko...
Tomoko?
Hey...
It's ok...
...to call me.
Tomoko....
On second thought, I'll call you.
Just like always.
Leon de Saint-Juste was a young knight.
At eighteen, his heart broken by love, he was a dissolute young Parisian.
He attended Darcy University and studied Law.
After the French Revolution he joined with Robespierre of the Jacobin Club
And he sent many of the nobility and royalty to the guillotine.
His feminine beauty and cruelty made him both feared and hated,
And he became known as the "Angel of Death."
In 1794 his party lost power,
...and at age 24, he was guillotined alongside his friend, Robespierre.
Like the rains which fall in this world, tears also fall in my heart.
What is it creeping into my heart, filling it with sadness...
Angel of Death...
This was Saint-Juste of the French Revolution.
He gazed into death, even his own, with cool detachment.
Does her nickname reveal the sad vision which is reflected in her eyes?
Could it be a vision of Death?
My brother...
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Mariko gives an extravagant birthday party...
But... Nanako is the only guest!
After the party, Mariko invites Nanako to her home.
But Nanako is in for much more than she bargained for...
Next episode: I Want You...
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...