My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
There you are, Misonoo-san!
Why on earth are you here?
Hurry! Hurry!
Why? What happened?
4. The Music Box.
You are rather late.
I told you the party starts at noon.
Yes...
No...
I mean...
All right...
Please be seated, Misonoo-san.
Ok.
But Miya-sama called yesterday. So why would...
I will ask you a few questions.
Yes.
What are your hobbies? And what club will you join?
Sure! My hobbies...
I like baking!
But... I haven't decided which club to join...
I belong to the Flower Arranging Club and the Riding Club.
Flower Arranging?
I... I will join the Flower Arranging Club also!
She smiled! Miya-sama smiled...
Who is your favorite author?
Good! She may not be upset anymore.
Saint-Ex-Upery who wrote "The Little Prince" and Montgomery of "Ann of Green Gables"!
"The Little Prince"?
And "Ann"?
Like a little kid!
Oh no, they thought it was too childish! Well, let's see, um...
De Sade! I also like De Sade!
The Marquis de Sade?
The Marquis de Sade? Of sadism and masochism?
Wonderful! Which one do you prefer?
Um... Um...
Say sadism!
She's perverted!
Weird!
That's fine. She is liberal...
That's all, Misonoo-san.
The results will be announced tomorrow.
Failed. I have failed.
It's not final yet.
No... I'm sure. I couldn't even answer the questions.
That's not important at all! You did fine.
But... but it wasn't good that you were late.
What happened? I told you that being on time was so important!
But... yesterday Miya-sama called...
She said that the party would start at three instead.
I don't understand. Why would she do that?
Did she really call? Are you sure it was Miya-sama?
My mother answered...
It could have been anyone!
It's her!
Only she could do such a thing!
Misaki Aya...
After that...
How did I get home...
I don't remember.
It could have been a Sunday like any other,
Spent baking a cake with Tomoko...
My brother... can this really be happening?
A fake phone call... I can't comprehend such deception.
If it's really true, it's simply awful.
But... even worse, if I were in such a situation...
Could I be sure that I would not do the same...
Nanako, it's Tomoko. She's at the corner.
I figured you might be back already...
A fake phone call? What a cheat she is!
There's no way to be sure, but Shinobu-san thinks it was her.
I understand how you feel.
Being admitted into the Sorority is a fabulous experience.
Something that any girl would want.
Even I...
Tomoko...
But I always knew I hadn't the slightest chance.
I couldn't believe I could be chosen either.
True...
That's... that's true!
Now I don't have to worry about being slandered by anybody.
I feel much better.
What a relief!
We've been playing on these swings for so long...
Uh-huh!
We will be friends forever, okay?
Sure!
So anyway! Tomoko! The clubs!
So which will you join?
The Cooking Club, of course!
Then I'll join too!
I wasn't sure about the Flower Arranging Club...
I'll get you an application form tomorrow!
Yes, please!
Oh, good morning, Shinobu-san!
What's that all about?
It's about "Passed"! And "Chosen"!
What?
As in "membership"!
Congratulations...
Yes, and the same to you!
You mean you haven't seen the announcement?
Let's go! Come on!
Yes! It's amazing!
There were nineteen candidates.
Every one them is superior to Misonoo-san.
You miserable potato heads!
What!
Want me to say it again?
Potato heads!
It's still true what I said!
Go away! This is none of your business!
I'll not forget this!
I'll protest directly to Miya-sama!
You didn't even attend the party!
Aha! How is it you know that?
I'll tell you how!
Because it was you who made the phony call, pretending to be Miya-sama!
I don't know anything about that!
It's you that plays dirty!
That alone disqualifies you!
And I'd never tolerate you as a member anyway!
Well! Let's go, Misonoo-san.
Ok...
That's the problem...
Every year we have our arrogant lady, Miya-sama,
...playing her games with the hearts of the freshmen.
I don't like this.
Do you agree?
Well you don't really care, do you, Rei?
Cheer up!
You were crying yesterday.
You wanted to join the Sorority, right?
Yes, but why me? It doesn't make sense.
Never mind all that. You made it!
I'm so happy! And we're together, right?
Yeah...
Tomoko!
Tomoko, wait!
Tomoko...
So you made it after all...
Congratulations.
I didn't see the announcement, so this is news to me.
Tomoko...
You look happy.
I don't know if I'm happy or not.
Here's your application to join the cooking club.
You wanted to join!
You'll probably join Flower Arranging after all...
Just like the rest of the Sorority members.
Tomoko! Being a Sorority member doesn't mean I can't be your friend!
Tomoko!
I'll meet you after school as usual! Tomoko!
Tomoko...
This island consists mostly of beaches, and is about three miles long.
It is not more than a quarter of one mile wide.
It has no tall trees. And near the eastern end, there is a fort.
Ok, very good. Be seated. Miss Misonoo, please...
Nanako-san!
Here!
From the sixth line on, page twenty seven.
Yessir!
Near the eastern end of this small island,
Lebrand had built a hut, and lived with an old colored...
I can't hear you!
A little louder please!
You jerks...
Go on, Misonoo-san!
Yessir!
...and lived with an old colored man, Cora Jupiter,
Lebrand was an eclectic man, and had unusual mental powers...
I can't hear you!
...which greatly interested me.
His chief amusements were shipping, fishing...
I can't hear you!
Hey... you... what is...
Shut the hell up!
Sit next to me if you can't hear!
I hear her perfectly!
Hurry up! You and you...
Listen, you! Stop this violence!
Kaoru-no-Kimi, you're so marvelous!
Don't mix the sugar and egg white at once.
That's the key.
First, you separate the egg white from the yolk.
Please begin now.
Sensei, this is too much like a circus trick!
It's easy for girls, but for you?
It's like you're implying that I'm not a girl...
Give me reasons to imply you are a girl, then...
Ok! Whatever it takes!
I will do the eggs for you...
The key to resolving them into factors is to factor the common variables.
This is a key point.
For example, X minus forty-two times...
I can smell cookies...
It must be Nanako's cooking class.
Tomoko! Being a Sorority member doesn't mean I can't be your friend!
Tomoko!
I was wrong. It's not Nanako's fault.
I'll apologize and make up.
To squeeze the tube, start from the end.
And make sure the cookie sheet is cooled off before you put it back in the oven.
You are doing quite well!
You are really good at this!
You're being a proper woman.
But you gave up womanhood!
You're so kind!
Of course, Misonoo-san's womanhood...
...should be especially good as far as cooking and selling is concerned!
What! Why?
Her womanhood?
You didn't know?
Her mother used to work at an establishment near Jyoto University...
...as a cocktail waitress!
Cocktail waitress?
At a bar?
And at that bar she kept company with Professor Misonoo...
...who already had both a wife and child.
A wife and a child!?
And then her mother kicked out his wife and the child!
Scandalous!
Unbelievable!
Are there really women like that!
What the hell! Pornographer's daughter!
Shut up! You daughter of a rat dog!
My father is a lawyer!
Greedy cheap private detective!
How dare you!
It can't be!
It can't be true that my father had a child!
Mama and Papa met after he got divorced...
That's what my mom said.
She... she wouldn't lie to me...
There are times when you have to endure undeserved slander.
You don't understand!
No one truly understands another...
...but someone who cares can try to, anyway.
Thank you...
Sign here, please.
For Nanako?
From whom?
Henmi?
Henmi Takehiko?
Oh no...
How?
Why?
I hope Tomoko is waiting for me...
Misonoo-san? Let's go home together...
I'm sorry...
But Tomoko is waiting for me.
I see...
Sorry...
Tomoko? I saw her walking toward the music room...
Really? Thank you!
You shouldn't bother waiting for Nanako-san.
What?
She won't be able to go home with you.
As a member of the Sorority, she has a lot of socializing to do.
Keep in mind that she is no longer an ordinary student.
She won't be able to go home together with you from now on.
From... from now on?
She asked me to tell you this.
I want to hear it from her directly!
Where is she?
Being her friend, can't you understand why she isn't here?
So why the hell not?
Nanako asked me to tell you because she didn't want to hurt you.
I'd not be so easily hurt if she told me herself!
In that case...
Tell Nanako good-bye!
Tomoko didn't wait for me that day.
Tomoko didn't forgive me...
I don't want to think about it.
There is always tomorrow.
And if not then, the day after...
We have been friends all this time.
My brother... my dear brother,
I have to find out about us.
And also about my father, and my mother,
...and if my father had a child...
How can Takehiko know her?
How long?
Hi, I'm back.
Welcome home, dear.
Um... Mom?
Yes, what?
I was chosen as a Sorority member!
Oh, congratulations! How wonderful!
Here is a package for you.
Brother!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Mariko's deception causes Tomoko to shun Nanako.
And then, at the Sorority initiation party, Nanako is shocked by Miya-sama's actions:
Miya-sama deliberately drop a kenzan onto Saint-Juste's hand!
Next episode: Thorns of Doubt and Suspicion
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...