My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Miya-sama!
I'm sorry Nanako-san. I'm truly sorry.
I just wanted you to swim with me.
Are you okay, Nanako-san?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
23. The Forbidden Gift
My Dear Brother... this is my first real truancy.
After what happened, I couldn't face school today.
I still feel overwhelmed by all that happened there.
I want to avoid dealing with reality a while longer.
How are you? How's your fever?
Just a bit tired, that's all.
I'll feel better this afternoon.
Try some hot lemonade.
Oh, thank you, Mother.
I can call a taxi to take you to the hospital...
Ok. If my fever goes over 36.7.
Sorry, Mother...
A cold?
Yes, she has a low fever and feels weak.
She called as I was leaving, so I couldn't really talk.
I see.
I can give her a message, if you like.
I'm stopping at her house on my way home.
Never mind. Thank you.
I had no fever, yet somehow I wasn't myself.
Somehow I was weary to my very bones,
...and I continued to have terrifying nightmares.
Tomoko stopped by on her way home from school.
Would you mind if we went to the beach?
Of course not!
Playing sick, right?
What a phony you are!
You owe me for the cake.
What are you talking about?
Be nice, or I'll charge you interest!
Well, here's the first payment then.
Here! A souvenir, from the lake!
Oh, great!
Guess what! Miya-sama was looking for you today.
What?
So, what was it that happened at her place?
No... nothing to speak of! I had such a great time.
What a luxurious mansion!
Walking around, enjoying the view, listening to music...
So! How about a race? Let's race!
To the breakwater up ahead.
Let's go!
Nanako!
All right then! Wait!
I'm home!
Phone call for you... From Ichinomiya-san.
What?!
What's wrong?
I'll take it in my room.
Um... Hello?
I heard you were absent today...
Do you have a cold?
Y-Yes.
How are you feeling?
I... well... my fever is gone.
So... I'll see your smiling face again at school tomorrow?
Uh... Yes! I'll be at school tomorrow.
Thank goodness.
Then, staying home had nothing to do with what happened.
No... nothing.
I'm really sorry.
It was just because you looked so cute.
Playing a little trick on you was irresistible... that's all.
It's okay.
Changing the subject... it was decided at today's Sorority meeting,
...that junior members will serve the guests at my birthday party.
Won't you help us, Nanako-san?
My Dear Brother...
Miya-sama's voice made my whole body become tense.
My hand on the receiver was wet with cold sweat.
I couldn't wait for the conversation to end.
Thank you.
Good night.
But... those things that happened...
I can't talk about them. To anyone.
Say, Nanako-san!
...did you decide on a present for Miya-sama's birthday?
Oh, not yet. What about you?
It's a secret!
You've seen them, the other members...
...they're all trying to find out what each other's presents are.
They want to buy Miya-sama's favor with expensive gifts.
Hm...
Well, I can tell you, I guess.
Don't tell the other members.
What? Red roses?
Yes, the gorgeous red roses that she loves...
I'm going to fill up her banquet room with them!
I arranged it all with the flower shop at the Hotel Royale.
What!
Sorry, sorry! I was held up at my club.
Wow, gorgeous!
...2,3,4,5,6 zeros!
Those things are all two or three zeros off!
Have you lost your mind, Nanako?
Just looking!
I can't afford it, even if I stand on my head!
That would be my Dad's monthly salary!
That's true!
Oh! Over here!
W-What?
That's Medusa-no-Kimi.
That will be all.
Certainly. It's a pleasure to serve you, madam.
Please give our regards to your father and mother.
Wow! She must have bought a present for Miya-sama!
Yes.
All the nice things are too expensive for me.
There's nothing I can afford here.
Give up on the idea of competing with money.
But...
You don't have any, in the first place...
Thanks a lot! I'll tell Father that.
Instead you can compete with... this!
This, you say?
Yes indeed! How about your famous cookies?
That's just the same old thing.
Having your own style is really it.
It is so much like you!
We all call you "Cookie Nanako"!
What?
To my Dad, Mom, brother, and even our hamster, Pochi.
What? Pochi too?
Good morning.
Sorry to call you at this early hour.
Quite all right.
Isn't it the day you go to the promontory?
Yes, to the promontory, please.
There's still a wisp of fog...
Still, the ocean is beautiful here, this morning.
It's quiet... calm.
It's always like this when I come to visit you.
You know already...
...that Fukiko-sama will be turning 18, soon.
Is this the anniversary of your mother's death?
Time passes by, it's already been 3 years since your Mother died.
Yes. Then, your recommendation got me into Seiran Academy.
You rented an apartment for me,
...and gave me a monthly allowance to live on.
It's nothing.
It's really nothing to the Ichinomiya family.
Even though we had different mothers,
...we do share the same father.
By the way, my birthday party is this coming Sunday.
Won't you come? Please?
Being my only sister.
Happy 18th birthday, Miya-sama.
Thank you...
What could it be?
Oh, I love it!
A diamond necklace, made in Italy.
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
Your favorite French perfume.
Happy birthday!
A rose, your favorite kind.
And, in celebration of your 18th birthday,
...another one thousand, seven hundred, and ninety nine!
Oh my.
How incredibly beautiful.
How can I?
Look at these presents! Will she really like mine?
Nanako-san, what are you doing? It's your turn!
Ha... happy Birthday!
Um... Here. Backed for you, from my sincere heart.
Home-made? Thank you so much.
It's so like you!
Does anyone have any more gifts to present?
In 30 minutes, our guests will be arriving.
Now, junior members should prepare to serve our guests, please.
Yes ma'am.
Have some! This is port wine.
Welcome! Hors d'oervres are being served over there.
Damn, I think we're a little late.
Let's go.
Ok.
Welcome! We'll take care of your things...
Would you sign the guest register, please?
Thank you very much.
My brother!
Um... Good evening!
Hi! You look very nice today.
I had such a wonderful time at the university fair.
Thank you so much.
Sorry!
It's okay, it's nothing.
But...
Thank you.
I hope it's not going to stain.
Nanako-san!
What are you doing?
There are guests over there who need fresh drinks.
Oh... of course! Excuse me!
I forced him to come.
Otherwise he would have spent all day in the lab.
Welcome.
Sorry to barge in like this.
Happy birthday!
Thanks.
Mariko-san! More whisky and water.
Making some now.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Would you care for whisky and water?
I'll take one.
Good evening.
Saint-Juste-sama! When did you get here?
I've been here a while.
You just didn't notice.
Oh? I'm sorry...
I'm kidding. I just got here.
Oh! Saint-Juste-sama!
Won't you play something?
Won't you please?
Play something for Miya-sama!
Please, won't you?
Well, for the Guest of Honor then.
It was unbelievable.
At such a wonderful party,
...I could never have guessed what would happen next.
No one could have.
This is the song!
The one Miya-sama played at her country home!
You... you shameless bitch!
"Shameless bitch"?
Fukiko-sama!
I'm sorry, everyone... please go on with the party...
She'll be back shortly... so please... enjoy yourselves... please!
Why? Why, Fukiko-sama?
What could I have done?
That song!
"That song"?
That melody...
...is the one I hate the most in the world!
No!
I was sure you loved that song!
You used to play it! I've heard you play it!
Many times! Over and over!
Fukiko-sama!
Go home!
I never wanted you here anyway!
Shinobu-san... we can take you home in our car.
No thank you!
But, it's raining!
Nanako-san, watch what you're doing!
Don't let a man talk you into sharing your umbrella!
That incident brought an end to the party.
Neither Mariko-san nor I knew what to say.
We walked to the station without a word.
Such a happy little party...
...to end in such a violent storm.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Though Rei played a song she thought Fukiko loved,
...it somehow caused Fukiko to explode at her with rage.
So, Rei seeks out an explanation from Takashi,
...to ease her torment,
...and learns of the shocking events of 6 years earlier!
Next episode: Encore
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...