My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
How about this one?
Nope. It's too girlish for a yacht.
What about this one?
Mm... Not good enough, just too ordinary...
What about this? You'll be a star!
Isn't it too childish?
Well... You're right. It looks like Shichi-go-san.
Be a bit more serious, please!
I'm jealous! A party aboard a yacht!
Then dinner at a restaurant overlooking the beach...
That yacht is Miya-sama's family boat!
Hieeee!
"Hieeee" is right!
Brother, Dear Brother;
Mid-terms are over.
With lightened hearts, we went shopping.
Tomoko was helping me find a dress for the Sorority party.
Now really...
Mm?
This is the end of mid-term break.
Yes...
Tomorrow the results get posted on the wall,
...listing everyone from the first in the class,
...all the way down to number two-hundred-something...
I know.
I'm aiming for a little above the middle.
"Not to stand out, nor be looked down upon", is my motto.
But it's not the same for you, Nanako.
You need to rank in the top 50 to stay a Sorority member, right?
Yes.
But thank God! I'm so grateful now that I wasn't "Sorority Quality".
Nanako, you'll be okay! I guarantee it.
You're smart! You'll be 43rd, no... 38th...
My predictions are pretty good! You could call me "the Psychic Girl".
Anyway, my Dear Brother... mid-terms are over now.
The glare of the sun grows stronger each day,
...and I sense that the season is about to change...
15. Fukiko; The Sea Rumbles
Nanako! There you are!
You made it! You easily made the top 50!
Oh! Shinobu-san, you made it, too!
What a relief!
Junko, it's okay... considering the circumstances...
Nakaya-san...
What happened to her? She's been at the top since Junior High...
Yes... she's the one who had a high fever on the first day of mid-terms.
...and was hardly even able to write her name.
Even then she did pretty well... placing in the top 70.
Top 70? That's still better than me...
We had been digging in silence perhaps an hour and a half,
...when the dog began to bark loudly...
Nothing else will happen now.
Mid-terms are over.
Now, 3 months after entering Seiran,
...I must admit that I'm getting more used to it.
Nothing else will happen now,
...or at least, I won't let anything overwhelm me again.
I'm finally feeling more confident.
The matter of Saint-Juste-sama and Miya-sama,
...and Kaoru-no-Kimi's health...
...even though I may not fully understand these things,
...I think perhaps I am finally becoming more fond, bit by bit,
...of Seiran's solemn buildings and foreboding trees.
Nevertheless, something happened that afternoon
...at the Sorority House, something I couldn't accept.
We will now commence this emergency session of the Sorority.
The agenda concerns our Sorority's standings in the mid-term exams.
The chairperson will be Ichinomiya Fukiko-san.
Brother, it was as if a verdict were being delivered at a trial.
It was as pitiless as the sentencing of a criminal.
Junior member Nakaya Junko-san of section C...
Please stand.
Nakaya-san, stand up.
Ok.
It is regrettable we had to convene this emergency session,
...just so we could deal with your case.
Yes. I am very truly sorry.
First foreign language placed 56th; second foreign language 48th;
Literature 77; politics and economy 63;
Mathematics 82; sociology 85;
Statistical analysis 38. The total result 73rd.
Is that correct, Nakaya-san?
Yes, that's right.
This is a disgrace.
All our members placed in the top 50 of their class.
Except you.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You know the Sorority rules, right?
Yes!
It's unfortunate you couldn't meet our standards even for one term.
Yes.
However, since it would be heartless to expel you so abruptly...
Miya-sama?
...you have one week to resign voluntarily.
The next scheduled meeting is in two weeks.
Miya-sama! Miya-sama, I beg you!
I promise that I'll do really well on the finals...
Please wait until then! Please!
The resignation may be mailed... addressed to me.
Kiryu-san, Hayashida-san, please vouch for me!
Tell her I had a high fever during the mid-terms!
It's true! It's true, Miya-sama!
Nakaya-san was really, really sick!
Wouldn't you reconsider her case?
Besides, it's not fair to pass judgment based on only a single test period.
Yes, really! It's... it's...
That's very high-minded of you.
But Sorority members are responsible for their health as well.
There's no excuse for these shameful results.
This touches upon the pride of the Sorority. Do you understand?
Furthermore, I wonder if you realize who arranged for your admission!
Come on now! Listen to me!
Like I keep telling you, you mustn't oppose the will of Miya-sama!
Furthermore, I wonder if you realize who arranged for your admission!
Don't you realize what a mistake it would be to make Miya-sama angry?
Listen... why not take her some of her favorite red roses?
Don't you think you should apologize to her?
What did she mean?
Wasn't I admitted on my own merit?
I wonder if you realize who arranged for your admission!
"Who?" Who was it? Who?
You understand why, don't you?
You didn't even attend the party.
You shouldn't have been chosen.
We won't permit such an injustice!
Injustice?
There was no injustice!
If not by an injustice, how could it have happened?
I don't know how it happened!
Damn you!
Take it easy! Hey!
Yes! It's amazing!
There were fifteen candidates.
What kind of dirty tricks did you use?
You didn't even attend the party!
This is impossible!
I can't agree with this! It isn't fair!
I don't know what to do for this party.
Yes indeed! It's at the beach.
I have sensitive skin...
The skin's worst enemy is actually salt.
That's true!
Mona-Lisa-sama, Vampanera-sama...
Oh, Nakaya-san!
You're a bad girl.
Freshmen shouldn't come to a place like this.
I'm sorry... I came all this way to speak to you...
...and... both of you have been so kind to me... and...
What do you want?
Could you... could you ask Miya-sama to reconsider? Please?
I'm sorry, but doing such a thing would reflect badly on us.
You understand...
Let me treat you to some tea...
No thank you.
Miya-sama! Miya-sama! Miya-sama!
Red roses... Please, Miya-sama!
Miya-sama!
You know, my father has a yacht, too! Not quite as big though...
...but I'll ask him to take all of us out, Tomoko and you and I...
Nanako-san!
What's the matter with you, Nanako-san?
Nakaya-san didn't show up.
Isn't she on her way out, anyway?
I've really been looking forward to today's party.
Mid-terms are over now.
Everyone was looking forward to it.
Nakaya-san was too, I would imagine...
Listen, what are you thinking?
You'd better worry about yourself instead of her.
Did you apologize to Miya-sama?
Did you bring red roses to Miya-sama as I suggested?
Miya-sama...
Yes.
Nakaya-san was expelled solely on Miya-sama's authority.
What?
In that case... could it have been on her authority...
...that I was selected for the Sorority?
Why? Why?
I don't know. I don't know that.
Until now... I'd thought I was elected fairly...
...by open voting, though there might have been a little something else.
Still that was what I tried to believe.
Finally, just a little...
...I was beginning to feel some confidence, here at Seiran.
Here, I'm going to open the champagne! Let's toast!
These are the people whose birthdays are this month...
Kiryu-san, Suzuka-san, and Ukawa-san!
What a nice breeze.
Yes.
Haven't you been worrying...
about what I said the other day?
Well, I... Yes.
Don't worry about it.
Your selection as a Sorority member was done fairly.
I'm sorry. I regret what happened.
I got upset when you talked back, and I acted meanly.
It's true that your recommendation came from me,
...but you were chosen by all the sophomore's votes.
That's the truth.
It was rather cruel of me to say such a thing...
...knowing that you'd been hurt by rumors already.
Won't you forgive me?
What? Asking me to forgive?
Your hair is so soft...
Um....
And you are so pretty...
Her snow-white, almost translucent skin...
and the cool, faraway gaze that is sometimes in her eyes...
She looks somewhat like...
...Saint Juste.
Maybe they are indeed sisters,
Fukiko-sama and Saint-Juste-sama.
My Dear Brother...
These many dimensions of Miya-sama I saw tonight,
...are even more complex and mysterious
...than those of Saint-Juste-sama,
...darker than midnight, yet even sorrowful, as well...
Nanako-san.
Nanako-san?
Misonoo-san!
Yes?
Though I doubt that you would...
...might you happen to have a boyfriend you are seeing?
Well... I have a pen-pal... I asked him to be like my brother...
You do? I see.
Cease at once. It's too early for you.
But...
Cease.
You understand?
Y-yes...
My dear Brother, I'm sorry.
All I said was "yes".
It's not right, even from Miya-sama.
Deciding to whom I will write is something only I can do.
...as well as deciding who shall be my pen-pal.
I'll still write you... of course!
All I have to do is to not tell her...
...and there's no way she can find out.
So, why would she make such a demand?
So, had enough? You "Yacht-Girl"!
Bingo! I just got back and finished changing!
Let's have a report! What's new?
Anything happen? Any gossip?
Um... there was something.
I mean, yes and no...
So it was sort of so-so?
Yes... so-so. The ocean breeze was tiring.
Oh! Sorry! I have to go!
I'll call you back.
Darn interruptions...
Nanako, where are you going? It's late!
To see a friend! Up around the corner...
Nakaya-san.
I'm sorry to call you so late.
I really needed to talk to you.
I decided to leave the Sorority.
Today I sent my resignation to Miya-sama by express mail.
Nakaya-san!
I've looked longingly at the Sorority for so long...
...since I was in Junior High... and even before.
Such beautiful Sisters...
And such chosen, fortunate people... so splendid and magnificent.
Surely, I thought, their character had a goodness to match their beauty.
I can't explain how it changed, but now it seems more like a fantasy.
It's been only three months since I joined the Sorority,
but was there anything good that happened to me, I wonder?
My dear Brother!
To tell the truth, I've resented you a little.
Because Miya-sama seemed to favor you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay...
Here, this is a flower that will never die.
Thank you. For speaking up for me.
I'm so grateful. I won't ever forget it.
Bye!
Nakaya-san!
I don't like the Sorority that much, either!
My Dear Brother...
This season, a season of fairy tales, has come to an end.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
On the day of the basketball game,
Kaoru-no-Kimi suffers a bloody foul and must leave the court.
Mariko then panics and follows Kaoru-no-Kimi to the hospital.
There, Kaoru-no-Kimi's words bring tears to Mariko's eyes.
Next episode: Comeback
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...