My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
See you later!
What's she wearing today?
A purple dress...
She's going to a lot of effort...
Yes. Wearing something different every day...
It's been one week. So, I'd like to start out by telling you...
...about my "rotation" for this week:
Monday... a long tailored jacket with a pleated skirt.
Tuesday... on open-collared blouse with a cardigan, both beige.
Wednesday... a traditional single jacket-suit.
Thursday... the uniform. And Friday, a cobalt green dress.
But this no more than a plan, you know.
Depending upon my mood, I may change the "rotation".
Brother... The cherry blossoms are gone now...
There are so many fresh green leaves on the trees!
2. The Glass Slippers
Another letter...
What?
The letter! Aren't you still sending letters to your boyfriend?
No, he's not my boyfriend, he's my brother!
Same difference.
No, a brother is a brother!
I don't understand...
Well, you don't have to.
Well, my brother is noisy and obnoxious.
Oh, but I'm sorry...
Your dear brother is different...
Oh, leave me alone!
But, my brother, she's right...
You are neither my boyfriend nor my brother.
But on that day...
...the first snowfall of the season...
I thought you were someone I could not live without....
Ok everyone, you have 5 minutes to complete this quiz.
All right!
You had been teaching us at cram school
for the past four weeks.
It was your last day...
It wasn't love...
Surely it wasn't love...
When the last day came,
...and I realized that I might never see you again...
I just felt that I couldn't let you slip away.
I didn't want you to be like all the rest
...entering my life and then leaving.
I couldn't let that happen. I just couldn't!
Those eyes, those brown eyes, they somehow reflected my childhood days...
Maybe it was those mysteriously shining brown eyes that attracted me to you!
That's not love...
...surely it's not...
A question? Sure, On which page?
Please! Be my brother!
Your brother?!?
I won't bother you!
Just read... please just read my letters!
Now hold on...
And it would be great if you could write to me too...
I mean, if you have the time...
Now, look...
No, you don't even have to write to me!
Just read my letters, that would be more than enough! Really!
Believe me...
I don't know how I got the courage to do such a thing!
Um... your name is?
Misonoo Nanako.
What? Misonoo?
Are you the daughter of Professor Misonoo of Jyoto University?
What's keeping you, Henmi, let's go!
It's snowing harder and harder.
Sorry just a minute...
Do you know my father?
Yes... no... I mean, well, I've read a couple of his books...
Here's my address...
So?!
So that means?
Ok, but I'll expect the first letter to tell me that you got into High School.
O... Ok!
Bye...
Brother... brother...
the warm feeling of that word...
I've been so longing for that feeling since childhood!
My brother...
I felt that it became mine at that moment.
Seiran School, next stop.
Oh, Tomoko! Listen! Next Sunday...
My mother is going to let us use the kitchen!
Really? That's great! What's our challenge this time?
A chocolate cake!
Sounds good! With rum, nuts, and dried fruit!
And fluffy whipped cream!
And decorated with mint leaves!
That's perfect! That sounds wonderful!
We'll go dutch!
Yes!
Good morning!
Nanako-san!
Oh! Good morning...
I've been calling you. Didn't you hear me?
Do you always come to school at this time?
Yes...
I'll make sure I'm here to meet you, then.
Excuse me...
Let's hurry up!
The first class is Mrs. Imai's. She's always early.
Hmmph! "excuse" you!
How pretty! Today's dress looks really nice on you, Misonoo-san!
Good morning, big sisters!
Hi!
Hi! Good morning, pussy-cat!
"Pussy-cat"?
The bell is ringing!
Hurry! Take your seats!
...so anyway—
Come on! You two, take your seats!
You look so pretty when you are angry!
Lucky you! Being scolded by Kaoru-no-Kimi...
Please, scold me too!
You, could you please move...
I'd like to sit there.
What? Why?
No big deal. I just want to sit next to Misonoo-san.
What the heck?
What's going on over there?
Quiet! Hurry! Hurry up!
Here, take your things...
One of the most interesting ways to get to London is through the Soviet Union.
Of course, this country has its problems.
So you may have problems too.
However, I prefer to think of them not as problems, but as adventures.
I'm so happy I get to sit next to you...
Brother...
...regarding Mariko-san...
ever since orientation, I've been thinking
that there was something different about Mariko's face.
I finally realized...
...that it's her lips. Her very red lips...
So, why are you looking at me that way...
Oh! Your lips... your lips...
Oh, them?
I'll show you.
Look.
I constantly bite my lips like this.
...because the big sisters like red lips.
What?
So that... anyway, never mind... Perhaps you'd like to try it?
No... I couldn't!
What a gorgeous, but pushy girl!
And, somehow, also, mysterious...
Shinobu Mariko-san is so full of surprises.
Please, how much is this?
That's true...
it's a big deal in my family
since my mother was also a Seiran Sorority member.
Wow, a mother and daughter both in the Seiran Sorority!
Well, I haven't been chosen yet.
Oh, it's a sure thing, though.
Well, I already begged my father until he let me
get the dress made for the final selection party.
See!
Here, Nanako-san!
Finally, today!
What?
Why, the Sorority of course!
Today's the day, during 5th period,
that they'll announce the candidates.
That's why Misaki was talking about that...
Misaki Aya?
Unfortunately, she's probably one of the top candidates.
I don't like her.
Don't say such things!
But I hate her, I really hate her.
I've had to put up with her being in my classes since Junior High!
She's such a bitch.
What do you think?
About what?
About me! Do you think I'll be selected?
Well... I don't know much about the Sorority...
Actually, I'm quite sure of it...
Sorority membership...
Only the chosen few get to be in the club.
Mariko-san and Misaki-san have been so pre-occupied...
Before I came to Seiran, I didn't even know sororities existed.
This is a new world for me.
But now that I know more about them...
...I wonder if they are really such a good idea.
Saint-Juste-sama...
She saw me...
...but she didn't even recognize me.
She must have forgotten already.
What's the matter? Fifth period is starting...
Saint-Juste-sama! Saint-Juste-sama...
Thank you for this.
Oh, okay. I see that you're as popular ever.
Still, I'm no "Kaoru-no-Kimi"...
That's for sure.
Your taste in clothing is no better than before, I see...
I don't have bourgeois tastes like you.
"Classy" is the term I prefer.
What great pot-shots!
What great pot-shots! They're beautiful!
Back in the basketball club?
Yes.
What's so great about and dust?
That's my business... not yours.
Later then...
See ya.
Get out of my way.
As you wish...
The Sorority has arrived!
Finally, it's time!
Everyone, quiet please.
I would now like to announce the names of the candidates for Seiran Sorority.
Please, would those ladies whose names I call be so kind as to come forward...
Shinobu Mariko-san...
Here!
Great! Congratulations! I knew you could do it!
I'm still just a candidate.
Now...
Coming!
And next...
And next... Orihara Kaoru-san
Please come forward.
Thank you, but I decline.
What is that? State your reason...
I'm opposed to the very existence of the Sorority itself.
But since it's not "politically correct"...
...to say that I'm opposed to the existence of this Sorority
let me just say instead that it's because of my poor health.
I see...
I'm sorry to hear that.
But thank you for stating your opinion so honestly.
Now, the final candidate from this class...
Misonoo Nanako-san!
This is impossible!
I can't agree with this!
It's not fair!
Wait! Why isn't it fair?
It should be obvious!
How is Misonoo Nanako qualified for the Sorority?
That's right!
Misaki is right!
So you think you are qualified?
Shut-up! You, the daughter of a pornography writer!
W-What are you saying!
Ever since we were in Junior High,
I've known that Shinobu Hisaki
is your father, and he's a porn writer!
Everyone knew that!
We pretended as if we didn't know because we pitied you!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Even if your family's school endowment is huge,
you're still not qualified for the Sorority,
and neither is Misonoo Nanako!
That's enough.
It would be nice if it were otherwise,
but children cannot choose their parents.
Shinobu-san!
Oh sister, I'm cursed!
Don't fret, it's ok. It's not your fault.
Our selection...
Do you still oppose the fairness of our selection?
It's unfair!
Then I can let you be a candidate as a replacement for Orihara Kaoru.
However, my one veto vote will guarantee that you won't be selected.
Misaki!
Every year, it turns into a fight like this!
From competition comes strength.
Being able to survive this competition
is itself a qualification for being selected.
Misonoo-san...
Yes?
The final selection party is being held at noon this Sunday.
At the Sorority House.
Here. This the invitation.
My Dear Brother...
Misonoo-san!
Miso... Oh!
Hi, Nanako!
You're late! I've waited for over 20 minutes!
That was quite a scene!
The whole class went crazy over those announcements!
What's the matter?
I don't believe it!
No way! Why?
I don't know! But along with Shinobu...
It's true then.
So now?
What?
What are you going to do now?
Well... Um...
I think I have to attend the party...
That's next... Sunday!
Yes...
But the cake!
We were supposed to bake the cake next Sunday
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Tomoko!
Don't worry. I'm sure I won't be selected.
I'm so sorry, Tomoko.
I'm sorry, too.
My little Nanako has become such a Cinderella-Princess.
Let's show them they made a good choice!
Tomoko...
Let's go home. The main gate will be closed soon.
Misaki-san?
I can't...
I just can't let everything end like this...
My Dear Brother...
The Cinderella-Princess dropped her glass slippers
and became her everyday self when the clock struck twelve.
When will the clock strike twelve for me?
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
The other girls react adversely to Nanako's selection to the Sorority...
...and a slanderous note is posted in response.
The day before the selection party, Nanako receives a phone call
from someone claiming to be Miya-sama
Next episode: Nanako is Disqualified?
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...