My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
My Dear Brother...
Kaoru-no-Kimi is leaving the hospital today.
Though it was only overnight, and a simple basketball injury,
It is still a special occasion.
What's taking so long?
In attendance are Mariko-san and I.
Saint-Juste-sama is not present.
There she is!
Here!
Congratulations on your discharge!
Oh! You came to see me?
Hi!
Congratulations on your discharge!
Thank you.
But isn't this a bit much?
I was only in the hospital for observation.
But I couldn't sleep all night for worrying!
Ah... oh...
Oh I see! My worrying isn't important enough to concern you!
That's not true!
Oh, these are some of my favorite flowers!
Thank you... Mariko-san.
You made me so happy!
So happy!
That's the first time you used my first name!
My dear Brother...
Look at Mariko-san!
17. Post Scriptum
So she's already out of the hospital? Thank goodness!
I'm glad it wasn't serious.
Yes, and starting tomorrow she can even exercise a little.
But what a surprise! The way Mariko-san adores Kaoru-no-Kimi!
I had no idea!
Neither did I!
Really?
That's the truth!
That's true, my dear Brother.
I don't know when Mariko began to adore Kaoru-no-Kimi...
But this is love. Real love.
She's so honest and direct with her feelings!
Mariko-san just can't lie to herself.
It makes sense, you know...
What?
Kaoru-no-Kimi is more manly than the pathetic boys around here...
...and so good-looking!
And that way she talks: effervescent, like fresh soda!
So Mariko-san got to her first!
What?
It was Mariko-san who got her...
Tomoko!
I'm kidding! Let's just say I'm kidding.
I felt envious of her, my Brother...
Mariko-san is so direct...
I've come to like Mariko-san very much.
Saint-Juste-sama...
Nanako-san!
Your father wants to talk to you!
Ok! I'm coming!
Ok!
My dear Brother, when I compare myself to Mariko,
I just can't be as frank as she is.
I'm still sore.
Get in. I'll take you to school.
You played in the basketball game?
Yes.
So, what should I think of all this?
What?
Did you enjoy it?
Uh...
I'd really like to know, so I'll ask you again...
Well, yes. I did.
Is that so?
Is it?
Let me ask you once again.
Did you enjoy it?
No. They made me play. I had to.
Oh? That's better, then.
Please let go of me.
You must never forget...
...that there is no one who understands you better than I do.
Am I right?
Yes.
Good morning!
That's right. They only affect you. No one else.
But think of yourself for once. And you'll see you shouldn't.
What did Miya-sama say?
You came here together, right? I saw you getting out of her car.
Hand them over!
Do it! Hand them over!
You know, that basketball game...
...I had a great time!
You make me proud, Rei!
Kaoru-no-Kimi... ...won't you have lunch with us?
I'm sorry, I really should check in with the Coach first.
Besides, we need to go over the schedule for the city tournaments...
Come on, let's go...
Um...
Hm? Something wrong?
No, nothing.
Saint-Juste-sama!
She's as popular as ever!
It happened suddenly, my Brother...
My heart began to race.
I felt flushed and hot.
Though I wasn't sad...
...there seemed to be tears in my eyes.
Nanako-san!
Let's hurry! Tomoko might be looking for us.
Ok.
Mix lightly, put it into a lightly buttered and powdered pan...
...then put it into the oven at 180, wait for fifteen minutes...
...and it will turn light brown. Then it's done.
Since you're asking me all this, are you planning on baking something?
Yes... I'm planning on it...
Mm, hm!
Heartwarming, homemade cookies!
Someone would love getting cookies, don't you think?
Uh-huh...
Uh-huh... I wish I could just give her my soul!
Oh, Whatever you say!
Oh! I just remembered...
I have an errand to run at the student store...
Excuse me!
What's with her?
No idea...
I'm sorry. We just sold our last stamp.
Oh. I see.
Oh! Look at these flowers!
Saint-Juste-sama...
Saint-Juste-sama!
What is she thinking? What is she feeling?
What?
She's all alone in the gym, in the early afternoon...
...it can only be that she is love-sick for someone...
Um...
Who is it?
Upsetting a pretty girl like this...
Orihara Kaoru should be ashamed of herself!
It's not like that! That's not it at all!
That's not it!
No...
For goodness sake...
Kaoru-no-Kimi is for Mariko-san.
Geez!
My Brother...
I have misplaced a very important letter to you!
...written in plain English, the book is suitable for beginners.
That's how it goes.
Kusunoki-sensei, I have a question.
Yes, Miss Shinobu, go ahead.
If one omitted the word "being",
...would the adverb clause go from passive voice to active voice?
That's a good question, Miss Shinobu!
Look how alive Mariko-san is!
She is overflowing with self-confidence,
...and seems so much more positive than before.
Her beauty has even become more refined...
...and Love has given her a new allure...
But unlike Mariko-san...
...I just feel confused, my Brother...
Bringing it to school was a mistake...
I could have bought a stamp near home.
Anyway, at the next break I'll take care of it...
Hurry up, bell!
Nanako-san!
Where did I lose it?
A lost letter? Nobody's brought one to the student office.
What's the matter?
What happened?
What? A letter?
I was going to mail it at lunch time.
What'll I do now?
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me it's a letter to a boy!
Nanako-san! Is that it?
A boy?
A letter?
What's this about?
Come here...
I forbid it! You cannot date a boy!
It... it's not like that!
You mustn't! No way! Absolutely not!
You just don't know how men are!
They're dirty, disgusting, shameless, selfish, and abusive!
Mariko-san!
If they look gentle it's a only a front!
Only an illusion!
So, don't! Don't date any men! I forbid it!
Mariko-san...
Don't! Don't do it! Don't! Don't!
So, let's go. 6th period is starting.
I'll give up looking for my letter.
Ok?
I'll give up on it. That's what I told myself.
But I don't like the thought that someone might find it,
...and peek into our relationship.
But it shouldn't cause any problem.
There wasn't anything I wrote that would cause a problem for you...
...I thought.
Misonoo-san?
Yes?
Mona-Lisa-sama? Borgia-sama?
Fukiko-sama has something important to discuss with you.
W-With me?
Yes, Misonoo-san, with you.
Come to her house after school.
What's this about?
I'm sure you know already.
What?
Miya-sama likes you, so don't make trouble for her...
You understand?
I think we made ourselves clear.
Did you do something to upset Miya-sama?
No.
What if!
I was hoping my premonition would not be true...
How was that? That serenade was for you.
What? For me?
It was wonderful! Thank you very much!
I'm glad it appealed to you.
Would you be so kind as to make tea for me too?
Yes, I will!
I don't take sugar, please...
Yes, okay.
Here, please...
Thank you.
Henmi Takehiko...
Pardon me, but I saw to whom it was addressed.
I'm sorry! Excuse me!
But, thank goodness, it was a Sorority member who found it.
If it had been found by someone else,
...it would have started rumors.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You're nothing but apologies!
I'm sorry.
Didn't I ask you...
...not to date any boys?
...isn't that right?
But he's a pen-pal! Just a pen-pal!
Today, perhaps that is so...
...but how can you guarantee that a romance won't follow?
I like your gentle nature...
...and how obedient and submissive you are.
Now... tear it up.
What?
Right in front of me.
Go ahead.
My Brother!
I'm kidding!
I'm sorry. I just wanted to tease you.
Brother...
My dear Brother...
I'm going to drop this in a mailbox right now.
My heart travels along with this letter,
...so please read this a bit more carefully than past letters.
This is the letter that was lost.
P.S. from she whose heart beats faster around a certain someone,
...and from the one who has been a little strange lately...
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako and Saint-Juste skip class and go to the park,
...where they encounter Henmi and Takashi.
Saint-Juste calls Takashi her "brother"...
Nanako finally confesses her feelings to Saint-Juste.
Next episode: Into the Dream...
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...