My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Wow, great! Your bed is softer than mine!
Really?
Lights out?
Sure!
Good night.
Sorry I didn't call.
It's okay.
Brother, dear Brother,
...it all began that night,
...when Mariko-san suddenly showed up at my house.
Mariko-san?
Mariko-san!
Nanako-san!
At that time, I hadn't the slightest idea,
...what sort of pain she was feeling, or why.
27. An Incident of Bloodshed
I'm sorry I came over so suddenly last night.
Your father and mother are so nice!
Even after barging in like that, they said, "come and visit us again"!
So, when can I visit again?
Say, Mariko-san...
What?
Oh, nothing...
Good morning!
Tomoko!
Good morning, Tomoko-san!
Mariko-san! Since when do you catch the train here?
Curious, aren't you? Well, I stayed at Nanako-san's last night!
What?
I'm trying to take Nanako away from you!
Huh?
Mariko-san...
No time for any more practice now.
Ok.
I'm so sweaty! That's a drawback of morning practice.
Yes, and there's never enough time for a shower.
You're really improved a lot, Misaki-san!
Really? Thanks!
See you at lunch!
Okay!
Mariko-san, your slippers?
I... I'll be right back.
Hello?
This is Mr. Ishikawa. I'm not in right now.
Please leave your name and a message after the beep.
I'll call you back...
Let me see your notes. I didn't understand that part.
Sure, but I might not have it right, either...
Oh no! Homework!
What?
1st period French...
Oh, wow, that's unusual.
I suppose even a Sorority member can forget her homework...
The Sorority represents the student body.
So perhaps you two...
...should get your lives under better control.
Don't listen to then, Misonoo-san.
But even if you tried,
...some things in your life just can't be changed.
Isn't that so, Shinobu-san?
Listen, if you have something to say, say it!
What do you mean by that, I wonder?
Or is there really something?
There is!
Your reaction tells me I'm right.
Shinobu-san, class is starting...
"A pornographer's legacy is pornography."
So what lies in store for the daughter of a pornographer?
Bitches like you never know when to quit!
That hurts! Let me go!
What are you doing!?
What on earth is going on?
Let me go, Kaoru-no-Kimi!
I hate her, I hate her!
It's okay. Calm down.
That really hurt. You're more vicious than my dog!
You're a low-down filthy bitch!
Bark as much as you want.
You won't be at Seiran for that much longer...
What?
What does that mean?
Shinobu-san has to leave Seiran?
What did she mean?
You know, our generation prefers tight jeans over cotton pants.
This is only natural,
...since we have confidence in our figures.
Tomoko, you nut.
Guess what. My parents are getting divorced!
What!
D-Divorced?
Don't look so serious!
It doesn't bother me one bit!
Mariko-san!
It happens all the time!
A man finds a lover, has an affair, then leaves his family.
It's so common these days that it doesn't even make good TV drama.
See! Didn't I always tell you,
...men just can't be trusted!
But it's such a nuisance!
My home is so dreary now.
My Brother...
This is so exciting!
I'm hoping for lots of alimony!
My dear Brother... Divorce!
Mariko-san's parents are going to divorce.
Mariko-san spoke about it so lightly in front of us...
But this must've been the reason,
...the reason that she cried so sadly at my house last night.
Today, that same Mariko-san is cheerful,
...but her cheerfulness is forced.
What should I do, my dear Brother?
What can I do for her, as her friend?
Wait... It'll just be a moment...
This is Mr. Ishikawa.
Hello!
Mariko?
Yes.
How are you?
Fine. How about you?
I'm just fine.
Say, Papa...
Yes?
I'd like... to see you today.
Would that be okay?
Today is sort of... you know...
I see.
I'm sorry, Mariko.
Um... is she done?
Sorry... thanks for waiting.
Hey, why don't you come along with me?
Wow, it's so soft! Puyo puyo!
See, Tomoko-san?
Huh? Oh, yes! You're right! See, Nanako! Feels good!
Hm!
It is!
It looks great on you, Miss!
Really?
Yes!
Isn't it a bit too subdued?
No, it's very chic.
Really?
Beautiful!
Ok. I've decided.
I'll take it, please.
Ok!
Send the bill to the usual address.
Certainly.
Can you really spend that much without asking?
Sure, it's okay.
Now let's accessorize it...
What?
Come on, this way.
"Accessories, 4th floor please."
Pick anything you want.
It's on me today.
Oh, I couldn't!
It's my thanks for coming shopping with me.
Then, chocolate cake and lemon tea!
Same for me.
Is that all? Don't hold back...
This is fine.
I'm not that hungry, anyway.
Then, I'll have Key-lime pie, sorbet, crepes suzettes,
...and then lemon tea.
Right away, Miss.
What's wrong?
Bang! You're too extravagant!
Hey, that's what you always say!
You'll never change, I guess!
Just a minute. Excuse me.
Papa!
Papa?
Mariko?
Papa!
Mariko...
So... this is why... this is why you wouldn't see me today!
Mariko-san!
Mariko? Is that you, Mariko?
Oh! Mariko.
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Aren't you angry?
What?
I didn't come home last night.
Misonoo-san's mother called me.
But it was so lonely without you last night.
You must be hungry. Dinner will be ready soon.
I made your favorite, beef stew.
I saw Papa today.
That woman was with him!
Oh? Really?
Is that all?
That's all you can say?
Mariko...
How can you pretend it's nothing all the time?
Why don't you say anything? Why don't you get angry?
You care about him don't you? You love him don't you?
You cry because he's gone don't you? Answer me!
Stop it, Mariko! Please!
...please...
You're...
Mama you're crying again!
Mama!
Hi! You forgot this. We brought it for you.
Thank you.
I finally decided to just spend a lot of time with her.
The pending divorce was a major problem,
...and I was powerless over something like that,
...but staying close to her might help.
I wouldn't be able to help Mariko-san directly,
...but I hoped to ease her pain at least a little.
I figured that would be best.
See you later!
But, my Dear Brother, I was too optimistic.
That afternoon, my optimistic plans were destroyed.
Oh, Shinobu-san! I didn't think you'd show up today.
What do you mean by that?
Don't you know?
You have such a famous father.
Mr. Shinobu's divorce is official.
Look, big headlines, and a picture!
Your father's lover used to be an actress...
Isn't she beautiful?
You're met her, haven't you?
You want to know all about it don't you?
Misaki-san!
There's more... here.
It says how much alimony your mother's getting...
Misaki-san!
What was that for?
Do you realize what you're doing?
No I don't.
How could I.
I'm not one of the all-knowing members of the Sorority like you.
Here, you can take this... take a look at it later.
Misaki-san!
Anyway, it's the end for you.
Your family gives a big endowment to Seiran.
Without it you may lose your membership in the Sorority,
...and your attendance at Seiran itself could be at risk.
But knowing you, you might still choose your father.
It's a difficult decision: take the money, or dump your mother...
Mariko-san!
Mu... Mu... Murderer!
Murderer!
What is it? What happened?
Mariko-san!
What happened, Shinobu-san?
I'm sorry.
Mariko-san!
I'm sorry, Nanako-san.
No!
My Brother...
It wasn't Mariko-san's fault.
I don't think it was really her fault.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
When she learns that the divorce caused this incident,
Mariko's Mother is ridden with guilt.
Mariko is also overcome with guilt feelings.
Their family's love leads to their family's destruction.
Next episode: The Christmas Candles
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...