My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
I need... to talk to you.
I'm still asleep...
Go ahead and talk. Don't expect a response though.
Ok. Good enough.
In Junior High, we both used to play basketball.
After practice we'd stay over at the court and practice shooting.
We were just playing at first... but we became very competitive.
We'd play until we were exhausted.
That story again?
That's nothing new. I'm hanging up.
You're still part of the team.
So what? I'm not interested anymore.
Your number is still here, waiting for you to come back.
I'm hanging up. For sure now.
Wait!
Goodnight.
16. Comeback
So, now no one's left here.
With only a single light illuminating the one hoop,
...and without applause, you continue to take shot after shot.
Is all this sweat proof of the flower of your youth?
Or is it to help you forget the pain?
There's no pain in my life!
This makes me feel great. You deciding to come back.
No way! I'm just here to tease you.
But you know, you don't really need this extra training.
Seiran's star player Orihara...
...has been famous as a national-class player since Junior High.
I need to make up for my recent absence.
I'm no natural. Not like you are.
A "woman of effort and diligence", you used to say...
Shut up!
This "woman of effort and diligence" has at least one crazy fan.
What?
She's been watching you intently...
...since long before I arrived on the scene.
Who's there?
What's going on? Why are you running away?
I'm not running away!
Come here. I can get you an autograph.
I'm not a groupie!
Now, now!
I'm no groupie, you understand?
You're not.
See! See! Kaoru-no-Kimi confirmed it.
Then may I ask, considering that it is very late and after school,
...just what it is you are doing here?
Checking on the state of her health.
"State of her health"?
Yes, really! Tsurugaoka School is a tough opponent!
Even though it's just an exhibition match tomorrow,
...we need Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Is she truly recovered? Or is she just making an enormous effort?
It's natural to worry about it!
You can't expect me to just go home and watch TV!
Hey now, isn't this exactly like a groupie?
No that's not it!
Excuse me... Kaoru-no-Kimi?
Yes?
Please take this.
Excuse me!
What is it?
Sports drink.
My Dear Brother,
Finally I have a moment to write you a pleasant letter.
Actually, I think I really want to write a lot.
Tomorrow is Kaoru-no-Kimi's first game,
...after a long absence.
Oh no! You can't make it after school today, Tomoko?
No, there's my Cooking Club.
We're baking apple pie.
Don't go! Which is more important?
Kaoru-no-Kimi or apple pie?
But I don't understand the first thing about basketball...
You'll understand and enjoy it. It has such power!
Especially Kaoru-no-Kimi's 3-Point shot!
It's so magnificent!
Do you know anything about this, Nanako?
This 3-point shot?
Sure.
Well listen up! There's a 3-point line marked on the court,
...so we're talking about shots taken outside that line.
I get it now.
It's so difficult!
And rarely successful since it's so far from the goal.
That's why it gets 3 points.
She doesn't get it.
Besides, it's her comeback game!
...even though it's only an exhibition match.
Tomoko don't you have any sense of obligation?
You're really hot on...
On what?
Kaoru-no-Kimi! On Kaoru-no-Kimi!
It's suspicious.
No way! She's such a tomboy!
Don't say such nonsense!
You're blushing!
I don't think I like Tomoko-san after all!
How come she's so mean?
She's been like that since childhood.
I hate you!
Good morning.
See you after school!
Tomoko, see you after school.
We'll see! Bye!
Kaoru-sama, best wishes for today's game!
I'll come to see you!
This is for you.
It'll be "Kaoru-no-Kimi Day", all day today!
Oh no, no! Shame! Kaoru-no-Kimi doesn't like groupies.
Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Please let me have your autograph!
To commemorate today's victory!
What? The game hasn't even started yet.
I know you'll win!
How are you?
Uh... Oh!
You look like you're in a hurry.
Saint-Juste-sama!
G-good morning!
Mm, you look fine.
Yes, thanks! And you, Saint-Juste-sama?
Just the same as usual...
My Dear Brother...
I have a premonition that today will be truly, truly wonderful!
Coach....
What's wrong, Orihara... everyone's already on the court.
Give me a few more minutes.
I'm very nervous, believe it or not.
You? Nervous? Ha, ha... I guess so!
I want to win so badly... today.
Hey, now. Don't try to make up for when you weren't playing.
I'll be easy on you today. Don't overdo it.
Right.
See ya. I'll be out front.
Sure!
Thanks, Coach.
But I want to be a winner.
I want to win everything from now on.
Then, I won't have to remember...
I can forget, because I love.
I can forget, because I've loved.
And I'll even forget that I've forgotten.
I loved you that much...
If I can be a winner from now on...
...then I can stay positive about the future.
Here. For you, Orihara-san.
We offer this special commendation to you, Orihara-san,
...to mark your return as Seiran team captain after a long absence.
We wish you the very best.
I'm not a member...
The Sorority may choose to honor any Seiran student with a commendation.
You don't understand.
I must accept that a Sorority does exist on campus,
...but I don't accept that it is a valid part of Seiran in the least.
Excuse me.
Orihara-san...
If... if and when you permit Asaka Rei to rejoin our team,
...perhaps then I may accept flower from you.
Bye.
The exhibition match between Seiran and Tsurugaoka will now begin.
Let's go!
Fight!
Kaoru-no-Kimi! Go for it!
Listen! We've got to stop Orihara-san!
If we can block her, Seiran is nothing.
Play this game on our terms!
Fight!
Darn!
What's the matter with Kaoru-no-Kimi?
She doesn't look like herself.
Their whole team is blocking her! She has no room to play!
She must be tired.
Right after her recovery...
Maybe it's too soon.
I've hardly begun.
I'll still win this!
It's not working. She's recovered!
More, then! Put three on her!
Orihara, don't overexert yourself!
This isn't an official match.
I'm worried you might hurt yourself.
Hurt myself? Me?
We're about to catch up to them!
Besides...
"Besides"?
It's been so long...
...since I could play this hard!
What?
Let's go!
Blood!
Orihara!
Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Mariko-san!
Bring her to the nurse! Get a stretcher! A stretcher!
I can't believe it.
I know I fouled her, but I didn't hit her that hard.
Leave me alone!
I'm fine. Get away!
Rei! Rei!
Get away! Don't touch me!
Rei!
I'm right here. Right here.
Calm down.
You're not yourself.
I'll take her to the nurse.
Um... yes, do...
Please...
Open the door.
Wait a minute.
Why?
I'm fine.
Huh?
I'm okay now. I was just in shock.
But there's something I want from you.
I want you to play for me... in this game.
Coach!
Please announce a player change.
We will have a replacement player for Seiran.
Seiran's Orihara Kaoru-san will be replaced by Asaka Rei-san.
She's back! The great Number 16!
Saint-Juste-sama!
My Dear Brother...
Because of Kaoru-no-Kimi's injury,
...the outcome of the game became impossible to predict.
But it was so exciting when Saint-Juste entered the game.
Trying desperately to lead the inferior Seiran team to victory,
...Saint-Juste-sama furiously traversed the court.
Her carriage, her expression, and her eyes...
...they were those of a wild animal!
Her eyes gleamed like a young boy's.
I'd never seen Saint-Juste-sama like this!
She was alive! She was really alive!
Brother, something must have awakened within her,
...something that had been asleep, something vital...
Amazing! Saint-Juste-sama made another shot!
Mariko-san?
Rei played in the game?
Yes. She replaced Orihara, who was injured.
I see.
The game just ended...
And the result?
Yes, the game was...
Mariko-san! Wait!
I don't understand! She's not in the nurse's office!
This doesn't make sense!
Where did she disappear to? Where is she?
Maybe she...
Where? Where?
Did we win?
We got within 2 points... 8 seconds remaining...
I stole a pass from them in our territory, shoved my way clear,
...and then made for the goal.
It was tough... everyone was defending against me...
I couldn't get close to the goal,
...and we were two behind, with only a 3-point shot left...
You went for it? You took a 3-point shot!?
It was a bit far, but I did... There was no other choice.
And?
It was close.
The ball circled the rim and fell out, onto the floor.
I tried... my best.
Thank you.
That's fine.
There are always times like that.
Yes. I've had times like that.
Hurry up Nanako-san!
Mariko-san!
You're so slow!
Mariko-san! Wait for me!
No running!
How's your injury?
One of them re-opened. It's nothing serious.
But the doctor is telling me to stop exerting myself.
Who is it?
Saint-Juste-sama!
Were you listening?
What?
Were you listening to our conversation?
No... we just got here.
What about Kaoru-no-Kimi's injury?
Don't worry. Nothing serious.
Liar!
What?
It was too bloody to be "nothing serious"!
Get away. Let me see Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Mariko-san!
I heard you threatening Rei in the hallway. What a scene!
I'm glad you're here.
Thanks for coming. I appreciate it.
It... It was Nanako who insisted on coming.
Are... are you really glad I came?
Hm?
You said you're glad I came. Really?
Yes. Of course.
Thank goodness.
My Dear Brother...
This was the moment when I first realized it.
She had deep feelings of love for Kaoru-no-Kimi.
So perhaps the most magnificent person that day...
...wasn't Saint-Juste-sama or Kaoru-no-Kimi.
Perhaps it was Mariko-san instead.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako finds that she is envious
...of Mariko's directness in expressing her inner feelings.
Nanako then accidentally misplaces a letter to Henmi...
...and the letter ends up in Fukiko's hands.
Next episode: P.S.—
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...