My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Wait!
I'm not letting you go. I'm serious.
I'll kill you if you go.
P-please...
Don't kid with me. What is this?
Wait! Don't go! Please! Wait!
Stop that! Mariko!
No, I won't let you go! I won't!
Let go of me. Let go! Let go of me!
Mama! Mama!
Mariko!
So how was Shinobu's birthday party?
Um? Um...
Only three people?!
Mariko, her mother and myself.
Rich people!
Renting a ball room for a birthday party for three!?
Usually only two. She and her mom.
So? What happened?
Eh?
Your expression says, "I'm depressed"
Nothing really. Nothing happened.
After the party at the hotel, I stopped by her house. That's all.
Oh... look!
It's Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Hi!
Do you run here every weekend?
No, not usually this far...
...but I'm doing extra training for the district basketball tournament.
Bye!
I'll be there!
Me too!
I can't believe she was hospitalized for a year. She is so energetic!
I envy her.
What?
She's so vibrant!
That's for sure!
My dear brother...
That night at Mariko-san's home...
I can't even talk about it to Tomoko.
Tomorrow is Monday.
How is Mariko-san going to act then?
I really don't think I can bear seeing her.
9. Relapse; Broken Heart
Mariko-san...
Mariko-san! When are you coming out?
Come on, dinner is ready.
You'll look like a prune!
Mariko!
Mariko, you're...
Mariko, what on earth were you doing?
Nothing special.
Morning!
Good morning!
See you, Nanako!
Sure!
Good Morning, Nanako-san.
About the day before yesterday...
During first period and even through second period...
...I couldn't look at Mariko-san, sitting right next to me.
I couldn't say a word to her.
Or even breathe.
I could smell her subtle scent of Rose cologne,
...and hear her quiet breathing, and my heart sank.
Dear brother... I couldn't forgive her.
I just couldn't...
It's going to snow tomorrow.
What?
This is the first time you asked me to lunch since we entered Seiran.
Is... is that right?
It is really a pleasure.
Sometimes, of course, Tora wants to lunch with Tama.
But Tama is a friend of Mike, and Tora, and everyone else too!
Hey Tama, you don't have much appetite today...
Meow!
See you on the way home!
Goro Nyan!
There is only one true love for me. Only one.
She was the world to me!
Under this shrouded moon, I will jump into the river;
...with a scream from deep within my heart.
I am sorry. You are no substitute for her.
Despite all your beauty and devotion.
...you cannot fill my emptiness.
Giovanni-sama!
Still, my dear, won't you come die with me?
Kaoru-sama!
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Please hold on! Where... where does it hurt?
What can I do? Help!
Please...
I need... could you get me some kind of painkiller?
Painkiller?
Yes. Go ask Rei. She should have some. Tell her I need it.
Ok... please wait here!
I'll be in the clubroom. The basketball club.
Ok!
Dear brother... what's happening to Kaoru-no-Kimi?
Asaka-san? I don't know... She was here in the morning...
Thank you.
Maybe!
Saint-Juste-sama...
At the theater.
Hadn't you heard? She's a guest performer in the play.
And today the first rehearsal in open to the public.
Wow! We got to come see it.
Thank you very much.
This will definitely be a success.
Sure, bye!
Please take these flowers.
I was moved to tears! I won't be able to sleep tonight!
It was no big deal. I messed up three of my lines.
Saint Juste-sama! It's Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Saint Juste-sama!
Please, please let me through.
Who're you... cut it out!
Saint Juste-sama!
Oh... she's the one who tricked her way into the Sorority...
Get lost!
It makes no difference with whom I die.
The cold wind blows through my soul.
Kaoru-no-Kimi is asking for a painkiller! Please give her one of yours!
Soon to end my life, I look up from the river's side...
...and see a single streak of cloud over a celebrating moon.
Strange insects buzz around my ears, and fireflies...
Saint Juste-sama!
This icy water will be the last warmth I feel during my final moments.
Kaoru-no-Kimi needs it. She's suffering!
Won't you die with me?
How can you laugh?!
What's so funny! Our friend is suffering!
Please give it to me!
Ma cherie La Poupee...
A painkiller, you say?
Well these are tranquilizers, here...
...and a hematogenic, and vitamins...
Ah, found it. Here they are.
Tell her not to take too many...
Th... thank you!
Ma cherie La Poupee, my dear Poupee, who slapped me...
Drugs... and more drugs.
Saint Juste-sama is drenched in drugs!
Excuse me, I'm going now...
Bye, see you later...
She asked for a painkiller. Is it that serious?
Thanks.
I'll be fine. Very soon.
You should go. Afternoon classes are starting.
But...
I will be resting here for a while.
I will stay right here!
Don't worry, silly.
I'm still recovering, like I said before.
Please let me stay!
You're more stubborn than you look. okay then, but only for fifth period.
Ok!
What a fuss!
How about sports?
Were you in any sports clubs in junior high?
Nothing in particular...
I'm not talented at sports.
But the ones I like are tennis, swimming and basketball.
I see.
But talent doesn't matter.
But I'm so ordinary!
What's funny?
I was hospitalized for a long time, remember?
Yes.
Now... I have a craving...
...to run very hard... up to the limit.
Until my heart... bursts.
My heartbeats...
I can hear them like music, cheerful and happy...
It made me realize that just ordinary living is a great thing.
...and I feel great...
...and run some more...
...and chase the ball...
Now, I feel much better.
That's good.
Can you come wake me up, after sixth period?
Feeling drowsy like this, I may fall asleep...
Yes, of course!
Our hopes were too quickly drained there.
The sights during that time and the group's decisions were such that we reported them.
Dear Brother, during sixth period that day...
...I was in another world, removed from both school and Mariko-san.
At first we thought that...
I was worrying that whole time,
...worrying that she might wake up in the clubroom, alone, and in pain.
Oh, excuse me... where is Kaoru-no-Kimi?
She left early.
Left early?
She left a note saying "I will be leaving early today".
I... I see...
She must have had a relapse then!
So then... I should get her phone number from the office and call her!
Excuse me, listen, Nanako-chan...
I need to say something, it's important.
Sorry! I'm in a hurry!
Many times, Dear Brother, so many times I called...
...using the number I got from the school office.
That was all I could do.
And even if she answered the phone,
I knew I still couldn't really do anything for her.
Hanging up the phone would just make me worry more.
There was no answer, and I didn't know what else to do.
Finally, I stopped trying.
No one understands. Nobody truly understands another.
But someone who cares can still try.
Does that mean that even if we worry about others,
...there is nothing we can really do for them?
Is that what you mean?
Doctor, thank you for your time.
She came here today, didn't she?
Yes, but not for a routine check up; she said she had a sudden pain.
And? How bad is it?
Don't worry. Don't concern yourself.
This sort of thing happens.
I see. Thank goodness.
The pain is gone, and she said she was off to a night practice at school.
Thank you so much.
It's good that she plays basketball.
What does that mean? You mean, while she can?
Don't say such stupid things!
I'm sorry...
Please, won't someone explain to me...
What is the point of our being born and living?
No one truly understands another.
I cannot feel her chest pain,
So the seriousness of her illness, and what that illness is, I can't know.
...because no one can truly understand another.
But, brother...
...if someone so alive and vibrant...
...has such a sadness and a dark side...
She, the very last person I would have guessed...
I cannot bear the thought!
Here, Mariko-san. You should eat...
Go ahead, Mariko...
Keep the hell out of my life !
Mariko!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Nanako continues to shun Mariko.
One day, Mariko suddenly faints while at school.
When Nanako goes to Mariko's house to let her mother know,
Nanako learns about Mariko's shocking secret.
Next episode: Mariko
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...