My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
The secret ballot was unanimous.
It is decided that Shinobu Mariko-san will be expelled from the Sorority.
That's not fair! That's too severe!
This is too one-sided!
Why didn't you listen to Shinobu-san's side of the story?
Misonoo-san!
You can't speak to her like that!
Do you know what you're saying?
Then, I will leave the Sorority too!
Right now! Right here!
I just now left the Sorority!
29. The Assembly
What?! You quit the Sorority?
Yes. I quit. Just now.
They expelled Mariko-san, so I decided to leave, too.
Besides, I think I would have decided to leave anyway.
So, what about the cake?
You know, for Mariko-san!
Oh yeah...
Wow! Cranberry cheesecake!
I've always wanted to try some!
Oh, good!
I'm thrilled.
It was Tomoko who picked it out.
Thank you, Tomoko-san!
A lucky guess...
Come on, Tomoko. Shall we eat?
Um... thanks... later.
What's wrong with Tomoko-san?
Tomoko's a little strange, sometimes.
Ah... Two or three lost seagulls... headed west,
...searching for somewhere to spend the night...
What?
Thanks, Tomoko-san.
I'm fine. I knew I'd be expelled.
They called me on the phone... It sounded like it was Mona-Lisa-sama.
She said that as of yesterday, I was expelled...
But it doesn't matter anymore.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
In my case, I never really gave the Sorority a second thought.
I really couldn't have cared less about it.
The more snobbish they got, the more I disliked the whole idea.
But, I know that Nanako really got caught up in it,
...and she's put out so much effort, and...
What?
Tomoko!
It didn't matter! It was nothing!
Really?
All that shouting and crying on the swing...
That was nothing? Did you forget?
Yes, I've completely forgotten all that!
Like I told you, I'd been thinking about quitting anyway.
Nanako-san... you mean... you quit the Sorority?
Yes.
Because of me?
No!
I'm sorry!
No! Oh, for goodness sake!
Come on, Tomoko! How can it be such a big deal with you?
It's okay! If it's okay with you, it's okay.
That's it. End of story.
Tomoko!
Tomoko-san!
I think I'll have some cake.
Um, it's delicious!
So that's what it's like.
With the Sorority, I mean.
What?
I guess so. Once you've been in the Sorority, you think nothing of it.
Originally I thought there might be more to it than that.
But, everything's fine now.
I don't understand what you're saying, Tomoko...
Good tea! Darjeeling, I guess?
My dear Brother...
The school decided on a punishment for Mariko-san.
She was to be suspended 3 months.
They must be kidding!
What's the school think it's doing, anyway?
What good does it do to put her life on hold for three months?
This was because some low-life girl was slandering her, that's all.
Oh!
"Low life"? Who says so?
Misaki-san was hurt! She could have died!
And you're siding with the attempted murderer?!
Yeah! You got a problem with that?
"...could have died"? That's ridiculous.
Oh, wow. Miss Expelled-by-the-Sorority sure is taking big now.
Tomoko!
I've had it with you bitches!
You're in for it!
That hurts, damn it!
Stop it! I'm not kidding! Cut it out!
You're the only one who can end this.
What?
Do it. Now.
Stop it! Please! Stop!
Strange. You don't usually come to hear me play.
I thought we could talk.
Sure. About what, pray tell?
Did you know Misonoo Nanako left the Sorority?
I heard something. A rumor.
And?
Um.
So?
What is it?
Well... um.
Maybe... this isn't the place or time.
What's the matter? Not feeling outspoken today?
I'll let you know... before I do it.
Let's wait, then.
How's the pain?
There is some, now and then. Just a bit.
It's happening more and more often.
Am I right?
Please... you must tell me everything.
Um... well...
Coming! That must be Nanako and the others.
Come in!
Hi again! We're back!
Wow, Tomoko-san, what happened to your face?
Just a rash. I have an allergy. It's nothing.
Algebra and geometry are at the scheduled point in the syllabus,
...but in English class today...
...we covered up to here and we're supposed to...
Never mind, Nanako-san. It's okay.
I can't go to school for the next 3 months anyway.
But...
I'm happy just to see you everyday.
There's no point in studying. It wouldn't stick with me anyway.
By the way, how is she?
That girl... Misaki-san.
She... she was at school. Today.
I saw her.
Hm...
Misaki-san and I have constantly been rivals since Junior High School.
I despise her more than anyone else I've ever known.
She's an arrogant, self-centered braggart who has to be first at everything.
And she's utterly alone and desperately lonely.
But... last night I couldn't sleep...
My eyes stared into that awful darkness and I thought of her.
Then I finally understood.
She... she and I are too much alike!
Those very things I can't forgive myself. I see them all in her too!
How could I... how could I have been so cruel!
Mariko! Mariko!
Stop, Mariko!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Misaki-san!
What the matter? What is it, Halloween?
You've been waiting for me to come home?
Thank you, Halloween...
My Dear Brother...
A victim... and an assailant.
Which of them suffered the greater pain?
Suspension... expulsion...
Perhaps in the long run, these things are unimportant.
I think I should finish telling you the rest of the story.
Hey... I hope you realize you're invading my bedroom.
At the next student assembly...
"Don't disturb..."
At the next assembly,
...I'll make a motion to abolish the Sorority.
What did you say?
Is there something you want?
No, not really.
Go home, then.
You can't just ride the club's horses anytime you want.
I asked for permission, and got it.
Oh?
Let's race! Please. Just you and me.
You want to abolish the Sorority?!
Yes.
You can't be serious! You can't!
I couldn't be more serious.
But why? You don't give a damn about the Sorority!
Wouldn't you be meddling in someone else's business?
Meddling?
I hardly think it is meddling.
The problem is that the Sorority has become a permanent school tradition.
It would be too cruel.
Cruel?
Because, the Sorority is... the Sorority is Fukiko-sama herself!
This is just the final legacy of a corrupt tradition.
She may be the head of the Sorority,
...but she and the Sorority are separate things!
But her pride!
That's her final reserve of dignity and pride!
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have mentioned it.
I'll do this on my own.
No! I can't let you do it!
Her self-respect is so vital I would sacrifice my life for it!
You're a strong one, Rei.
But for me, I love living.
Life is so precious to me,
...I couldn't bear to lose it.
I am the winner, Rei.
Yes, Fukiko-sama!
Something strange was in the air that day.
All the white doves had left the campus.
Not once that morning did I hear the flapping of wings.
Surely I was not the only one who noticed, though.
Brother, Dear Brother,
...in the afternoon, the student assembly was convened.
Say, Tomoko...
Yes?
Do you know anything about... the doves?
Doves? What doves?
Today, on the occasion of the school's 90th anniversary,
...we have called this first assembly of the year.
First, permit me to begin by going over today's agenda...
What was that about the doves?
Nothing. Never mind...
We have issues regarding scholastic grading practices, and the issue of on-campus clubs...
Say, why don't we take Mariko-san out today?
That's a good idea. She's been stuck inside the house.
...which are already planning their activities for the first half of the year...
How about Fairyland?
Sure! That'll do.
That is all.
Now, we may proceed on to the discussion.
Madam President!
I want to make a motion.
Go ahead, B-class freshman Orihara-san.
You may proceed.
Thank you, Madam President.
I move that the Sorority be abolished.
Excuse me... Could you repeat that, please?
I move that the Sorority be abolished!
Kaoru-no-Kimi!
Order! Quiet, please!
Abolish the Sorority?
Yes, that's right. Let's put it to a discussion.
I'm sorry, but I must reject this motion.
Why?!
Because the Sorority is part of Seiran's tradition.
A school with a traditional caste system?
A "caste system"?
How can you call it a caste system?
The system assigns a value to each person.
That value determines how much their future is worth.
"We're different from other students!" "We're special and elite!"
Then, this idiocy goes on and on each year,
...and students fight each other to get in, and many get hurt doing so!
We would be better off without the Sorority.
We must abolish the Sorority now!
Kaoru-no-Kimi is right!
Yes, it's wrong that the Sorority is so special!
It really is a sort of caste system!
No, listen, Seiran is great because of the Sorority!
Yes, let's abolish the Sorority!
Oh!
What?
The Doves!
The doves have returned, my brother...
Quiet! Quiet, everyone!
Please shut up, all of you!
Anyone wanting to speak must get permission from the chair!
Otherwise you will not be allowed to speak!
I move Madam President be replaced.
She cannot preside over this discussion without personal bias.
I move to replace her with someone not associated with the Sorority!
Rei!
That's right! The Sorority president shouldn't preside over the student body!
Yes, please resign as student body president!
Let's stop kissing up to the Sorority!
Replace Madam President!
A problem like this is not one for discussion solely among ourselves!
We have to consult the school board members, teachers, and the alumni.
Please, don't allow your emotions to get out of control!
Who's out of control?
We're certain we can get the necessary two-thirds majority.
Go right ahead, then,
...if you think you can so easily abolish this venerated tradition.
My dear brother,
...thus, the stormy assembly came to an end.
Nothing was decided, nothing was settled.
But clearly, that day, something had begun.
It's been on my mind a lot, since then.
What's the best thing for her?
I helped you out because of what I decided.
She doesn't have to always be in a rose garden.
She can be her beautiful and proud self without that.
If she persists in clinging to those thorny roses,
...they might someday pull her down,
...her and her pride both.
That's what I was thinking.
Her exquisite dignity and sense of self,
...I want her to keep all that,
...because that's the person she is.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...