My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Mom, is this a little too childish?
Well, it is cute!
I'll take this, and the same for Nanako too.
Matching pajamas!
We will be sewing pajamas next week in home economics.
Nanako-san?
Misonoo Nanako-san, I've told you about her!
Oh, yes...
Pleased to meet you! I am Shinobu Mariko, Nanako's classmate.
Sorry to stop by on a Sunday without calling.
but I have something I wanted to show Nanako.
Shinobu Mariko-san?
Yes!
I'm sorry, Nanako is out seeing a movie with her friend.
Arikura Tomoko-san is her friend's name.
I see.
Say, what was is it that came between us?
What do you think it was?
Probably because you've gotten too popular!
What?
Like Mariko Shinobu!
Mariko Shinobu likes you so much.
She really adores you!
And everyone wants you to herself.
She...
Who?
Mariko-san.
I... sometimes she scares me a little....
8. I Want You
Seiran School, next stop.
I can't believe it!
A test, first period! That teacher is a demon!
Don't fall asleep during the test!
The real me is wide awake... but perhaps not my brain...
No way!
Bye!
Bye...
Oh, Tomoko...
Yes?
Tomoko, we can go home together today, right?
Of course! Bye!
Bye!
What is the meaning of this?
What is the meaning of this, tell me!
I told you Misonoo-san is no longer the Misonoo-san you knew!
Can't you understand that?
I understand enough!
I understand Nanako is Nanako no matter what happens.
No matter what you say... or make up... I understand her well,
...because I've known her since we were both little kids.
Pardon me...
How did it happen?
How did you get back together with Misonoo-san?
Tell me!
Ow! Let me go!
No! I won't let go of you!
And I won't let go of Nanako!
Hey, hey...
What are you two doing? Class is starting.
Good morning!
...Misonoo-san.
Oh! Good morning, Shinobu-san!
First period is Literature.
Stand!
Surprised by my footsteps, the face turned back towards me...
Being an untalented poet, I cannot express well enough...
Those dewy eyes! Those deep, shining eyes...
I need to talk to you later. Something important.
Oh?
Your birthday?
Yes, next Saturday.
I'm going to have a little party.
I really want you to come.
Well...
If you don't want to, that's ok. In fact, I'll understand if no one comes at all...
...since it is a party for the daughter of a pornographer...
Don't say that! I never thought of you that way!
Then, you'll come?
Well... ok!
Really? For sure?
You'll come? Terrific! Wonderful!
I'm so excited! I have to tell my mom!
It's next Saturday at six at the Hotel Royale.
Yor are crushing me.
I rented "The Rose Room".
"The Rose Room"?
Misonoo-san, thank you! I'm so happy!
What an impudent girl!
She is going to stay in the Sorority.
Misaki-san, you'd better come up with something new!
I have some new ideas...
Misaki Aya-san?
Could you come to the Sorority house now?
Yes...
Miya-sama is waiting for you.
Yes!
So this is the Sorority House!
If it weren't for her being chosen, then I...
I'm so sorry to trouble you...
No, not at all!
What's your impression of our Sorority House?
Wonderful! It's gorgeous!
I've adored it ever since Junior High.
Were you aware...
...that there were times when members left the Sorority...
...and we accepted new members from the freshmen?
Really? Then... I still have a chance!
No. There is no chance that you will be chosen.
At least, not now.
Why not!?
I think you already know why not.
I give you fair warning.
Don't become a victim of your own device.
You'd not only lose your chance to become a Sorority member...
...but you would forever face the hostility of the entire Sorority.
Why is Tomoko so late?
Cut it out!
Tomoko! It must be Tomoko!
Stop, let go!
Shinobu-san!
No, I'm sorry, I'm not Tomoko...
Don't forget about this Saturday!
Oh... your friend's birthday party?
You can wear the dress your father bought you the other day.
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing...
I was just wondering what to bring for a present.
That's just like you...
Just like me?
You're amazing!
For you to agree to go to Mariko's party is hard enough in the first place...
...but you're even baking cookies for her!
And who is it helping me bake these cookies? You should talk!
No way! I want to make them with lots of salt and tabasco!
So, what are you going to give to me?
What?
For my birthday!
Oh? And when is that?
You brat!
It's fabulous...
A birthday party... Here?
Whoever could be coming?
Um... excuse me, where is "The Rose Room"?
Would you be Miss Misonoo?
Yes!
Miss Shinobu is expecting you.
If you would come this way, please...
I'm honored to be invited today...
Misonoo-san!
You did come!
Um...
Happy Birthday! I am honored...
Cut it out! Come over here...
...and meet my Mom!
Shinobu-san is so beautiful...
Especially beautiful, today...
Pleased to meet you! Mariko has told me so much about you.
Pleased to meet you! I'm Misonoo Nanako.
She talks about you all the time.
I'm so happy you and Mariko have become friends!
Not at all! It's my pleasure!
I hope you will be a blessing to her!
Too many formalities! Let's eat instead!
Mom!
Mariko, why don't you blow out your candles?
Oh, right...
But will I be able to blow out all 16 of them?
Go for it!
Yes... go for it!
Here goes!
Please go ahead and eat...
Do you like caviar? What about some wine?
So...
...where are all the others?
You're the only one!
What?
You heard me...
You're the only one I invited!
Only me?
You rented this... this enormous room...
Just for me?
Just me?
Until last year, it was only Mom and me...
Nobody would come if I invited them anyway.
Even my father would remain in his study, working...
Mariko, stop that!
Why? It's the truth!
Mariko-san...
Mariko-san!
Here, take this.
It's nothing special...
For me?
Really? Can I open it?
Of course!
Look! Mom, cookies!
You baked these yourself, right?
Thank you, thank you Misonoo-san!
Mom, take a look!
They look delicious!
How wonderful!
They look so pretty!
You're such a good cook, Misonoo-san!
It seems like... I didn't really know much at all... about Mariko.
I... I guess...
I guess I'm glad I came after all.
I want you to know...
I'm very grateful for today.
...and for all the things you did for me, and...
...thank you for bringing me home!
Oh, not at all, it was nothing!
It was you that made the party special.
It was our pleasure, really!
By the way...
Do you still have time?
What?
My house is right here... I'd like to show it to you.
Well, I don't want to impose...
Nonsense! No imposition at all, right Mom?
Of course not! It's a bit sudden but Nanako would be very welcome!
Ok? Ok? Please?
Ok. Just for a little while...
Turn around, let's go home!
Wow, these are delicious!
You're really good at baking cookies!
Oh, here's some coffee...
Do you want Cafe Royale, with brandy, or cafe-au-lait?
Oh, regular coffee is fine.
Are you sure?
Oh I wonder...
Mariko-san, could I stop by and bring you some pies?
Because you pity me?
If so... no thank you, I'm content as-is.
I'm sorry.
Really... I do very much appreciate your kind heart.
Honestly.
So, please, come by anytime!
Ok.
By the way, would you like to take a bath with me?
A bath?
Sure! Don't friends do that?
You do that with Tomoko, don't you?
No...
No way! You're kidding!
Your back is simply marvelous!
What?
Your skin is so clear and pale!
So beautiful!
Stop staring at my back!
I like all beautiful things!
I like my body, too...
Just between you and me...
Sometimes I gaze into the mirror for hours and hours
...admiring the beauty of my body!
What I really want is to be grown-up!
I want to be grown-up!
No doubt, Mariko's breasts are much bigger than mine!
She's like a beautiful rosebud, waiting to bloom...
Oh no, it's really late!
Mariko-san, I have to go!
No, you mustn't! Please stay overnight!
What?
Now it's raining, too!
I'm sure it will be ok for you to stay!
You've stayed overnight with Tomoko, haven't you?
Good friends do that, don't they?
Yes, but I wasn't planning on it...
Mom and Dad will be worried if I don't come home.
It's ok! I'll just call your parents!
So please, won't you?
I'll come another time, when I have permission from my mom...
No! Don't go home!
Oh, Mariko! Please!
No, you can't! I won't let you go!
Wait!
I won't let you go.
If you do, I'll kill you.
I'm serious, I'll kill you and then myself.
No, please let me go!
Why are you doing this?
Don't!
What are you doing!
I won't let you go!
I absolutely will not let you go!
Open up! Open the door!
Mariko! What are you doing?
No! Stay away from here!
What are you doing?
No, don't!
What's the matter with you! Your friend is...
I told you to stay away!
Mariko, what on earth is the matter with you?
It's none of your business!
No, wait! Don't go home!
Don't go home! Wait!
Why are you going? Isn't it ok to just stay overnight?
Aren't we friends?
What! How can you say that? This isn't "friends"....
Please, get a hold of yourself! Mariko!
I won't let you go! I won't let you go!
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
Mama!
Mariko!
Help me! Help me Mom! Help!
My Brother!...
Snow white...
My mind went blank...
Everything around was white... I kept running.
Brother...
The rain was so cold...
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
Suddenly, Kaoru-no-Kimi again suffers from her recurring chest pains.
Searching for medicine, Nanako goes to Rei for help...
But, Rei seems ambivalent and unresponsive...
So Nanako slaps her!
Next episode: Relapse!
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...