My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Dear Brother... I am at Saint-Juste-sama's funeral.
35. Beach of Dreams
Dear Brother...
On her final day, the day she passed away,
...Saint-Juste-sama sent roses to Fukiko-sama.
The day was also unusual in that she'd cleaned her apartment,
...and arranged to return a book to Kaoru-no-Kimi.
For me... the special day was the one just before,
...when she promised to take me to see the sunset.
Saint-Juste-sama!
She was enveloping us, all of us, with her happiness...
I'd rather not believe it was destiny,
...but it's as if she were passing on her happiness to us,
...knowing she must soon depart.
Dear Brother...
After crying so much, my tears still will not stop.
Fukiko, it is time now.
Yes, Brother, I know.
Fukiko...
But please...
I just need two minutes.
Would you leave Rei and I alone?
I want to say a final farewell, just the two of us.
Very well.
Excuse me, but we must take the coffin out now.
Please... just five, no, ten minutes more. Please!
But if we wait longer, I'm afraid the traffic will be bad.
It's only ten more minutes!
She only lived for 17 years. This is her last ten minutes!
Is i impossible to wait?
No matter what the reason is, surely you can wait ten minutes!
Ichinomiya!
Henmi...
Get a grip of yourself.
Rei, were you watching?
During your entire funeral, I did not let one tear escape.
I never allowed my emotions out.
I remained calm and dignified as I accepted the many condolences.
Yes, I was the proud Fukiko that you have always loved.
...because you are the only one who can see my tears.
My tears... my tears are for you only.
Rei!
Rei...
Rei... Rei!
I loved you.
Rei, I loved you.
I did love you so!
Now I must say good bye.
I'll miss you.
See, I told you.
It doesn't suit you.
Saint-Juste-sama!
I'm so relieved! I was having a terrible dream.
A very, very scary dream.
Saint-Juste-sama!
And where shall it go, this body of mine?
At one with the wind, wherever it may lead, like a lone sea gull.
Please. Please take me with you.
I will fly. Higher... and higher...
Saint-Juste-sama!
...and higher!
Didn't I tell you? It doesn't suit you.
Saint-Juste-sama I won't stay forever.
But just a little longer...
I want to stay here in this dream just a bit more.
Inside your dream... deep within your dream...
Dear Brother...
I couldn't sleep.
Being unable to sleep, I went for a walk,
...and before I knew it I was at Saint-Juste-sama's apartment.
Saint-Juste-sama!
What if... what if my emotions lead me to her room for a reason...
There was definitely a flicker of light coming from that room!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Miya-sama?
I thought you were her.
For a moment I thought you were her, coming back home.
I'm so sorry.
It's quite all right.
I was merely dreaming.
A dream that her death was just a dream...
I was feeling so grateful that it was only a dream...
Then I awoke, and realized I was here.
It all must have seemed very peculiar to you...
The relationship between Rei and I.
But I did love her.
I had to be the only one she admired; if not, I would become anxious...
...terribly anxious...
Dear Brother...
With those words, Miya-sama became silent,
...and the two of us quietly stood there, staring out of the window.
Through the window, we could see a canal and the bridge.
Oh... yes! This is it!
This is the landscape Saint-Juste-sama looked over every morning.
Now Miya-sama and I are looking out in place of Saint-Juste-sama.
Saint-Juste-sama, can you see?
It is almost dawn now.
It begins without you.
A day is about to start without you.
Nanako-san.
Yes?
If there is something that you like...
Today, my father and brother will come to clean out this room.
Before they do... perhaps you would like to choose a memento of Rei.
I'm sure Rei would be glad for you to have something.
She liked you.
Ma cherie la pupe.
You look just like her.
Very well. That will be fine, Nanako-san.
Did you know this doll is one I gave to Rei?
Yes.
Yes. I gave it to her...
I won't be able to live with you,
...but keep this near you, and think of me always.
Isn't it funny...
I couldn't remember it before, but now I remember clearly.
The name of that beach...
Fukiko-sama so this is where you've been.
Nanako-san, please come with us.
We will take you home.
Ok.
Nanako-san...
Yes?
There is something I swore I'd never reveal to anyone else.
But perhaps I could... ...yes, I do want to tell you.
The truth is, Rei and I are not stepsisters.
We share both parents, and are full sisters.
The woman I'd thought was my mother, on her deathbed,
...finally told me the truth before she passed away.
I thought the truth was too terrible to bear.
The father in whom I'd trusted had another woman.
So I was not a true Ichinomiya, I was her child instead,
...and I had a little sister too.
So I felt great hatred for Rei or at least, I tried to.
But I couldn't hate her.
Because she is my sister.
My only sister.
I couldn't talk to Rei about it.
I knew if I told her, she would suffer more than ever.
...at least, I thought so.
But maybe I should have told her anyway.
Perhaps then I could have loved her in a different way...
Saint-Juste-sama had known!
I cried out silently within...
But I couldn't speak it aloud. I couldn't!
How could this happen, Dear Brother?
Miya-sama and Saint-Juste-sama were unaware that the other one knew.
Each protecting the other from the sad truth.
Now I see the strong bond of love between the sisters.
Love, strong beyond my comprehension... a bond of love.
Brother, the two sisters entrusted me with this secret.
I will guard this secret forever.
I will keep it in my heart, secured by a lock marked "forever".
It's sad, isn't it, how you and I ended up being such wonderful sisters.
It's sad that we have different mothers.
If we act now, we can stop time at this moment of beautiful sisterhood,
...nothing will ever take it away.
Otherwise sadness will overtake us, and it will be too late.
Miss? Are you traveling alone?
No. I'm with my younger sister.
How wonderful.
If she is your sister, she must be very beautiful.
Yes. We both take after our mother.
Are you traveling far?
No...
My journey is at an end...
...finally.
It is all over now, Rei.
We will now discuss the petition submitted by the students,
...regarding the abolition of the Sorority.
Yes?
Excuse me.
Ichinomiya-kun...
I'm sorry that you had to convene a meeting on the subject,
...but the discussion is not necessary.
As the president of the Sorority, and as its last member,
...I voluntarily request the dissolution of the Sorority.
Dear Brother...
The Sorority has been officially abolished.
For certain, something has ended, and something has changed.
And I am left with one fact only... that Saint-Juste-sama has passed away.
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...