My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Mr. Shinobu's divorce is official.
Look, big headlines, and a picture!
Here, you can have this... take a look at it later.
Misaki-san!
Anyway it's the end, for you.
But knowing you, you might choose your father.
It's a difficult decision: take the money, or dump your mother...
Mariko-san!
Murderer!
28. The Christmas Candles
Hello, Shinobu residence...
What? Mariko did what?!
How badly was Misaki-san hurt?
We sent her to the hospital.
We are fortunate that only her arm was injured,
...and with treatment it should not be serious.
But, it's the first such incident in the school's history,
...and we are very deeply concerned.
I'm terribly, terribly sorry.
I'll get there right away!
What? Mariko is not at the school?
She left the classroom after the incident...
Are you sure that she's not home yet?
I suppose I shouldn't ask... but what happened?
Blood spurted up to the ceiling!
They say she always carries a knife in her bag.
Her father had 3 lovers.
The classroom was an ocean of blood!
My dear Brother...
The school was in an uproar over Mariko-san's incident.
I heard that girl is a Sorority member!
What! You're kidding!
I'm going to call her...
I'll... go with you.
No one's home?
She may not have gotten home yet.
Where can Mariko have gone?
What can we do?
Misonoo-san?
Obasama!
The vice-principal called, and I was just now speaking to him.
Misonoo-san...
Yes?
Do you know why Mariko would do such a thing to that other girl?
Well, uh...
I...
Oh, I see. I thought so.
Our family situation...
I'm sorry that it caused you problems too...
But...
But... what did the vice-principal say?
She's suspended until the school board decides what to do.
Suspended? I see...
If it's okay... we'll stop by after school.
Thank you. I'm going to the hospital now to see Misaki-san,
...and then I'll be going home.
If I see Mariko-san, I'll call you.
Thank you, Misonoo-san.
Takada Hospital, in Kyozaki City, please.
My dear Brother,
...in the afternoon Misaki-san returned from the hospital.
But I felt a sense of relief.
It was obvious that her injury wasn't that serious.
She's not back yet?
I see.
We'll check several places for her and then stop at your place later.
Thanks, bye.
Where shall we start?
Around the station I guess.
Ok! Let's hurry!
Ok!
Hey, ease up! It's right in front of me now and I'm working on it.
Oh? Is that you, Hisako?
Are you alone, now?
Of course! Don't be silly.
Then, I need to talk to you a little...
Listen, I have a deadline today.
I'll call you back later.
But, Mariko...
"Mariko" ...she said?
Misonoo-san?
We need to prepare tea for ten. Can you lend a hand?
But... today isn't scheduled as a Sorority...
It's an unscheduled meeting.
This is only for senior Sorority members.
This concerns the case of Shinobu Mariko-san.
She has brought disgrace upon the Sorority.
We need to consider an appropriate punishment.
Punishment?
Yes, Miya-sama is deeply concerned as well.
I am really sorry, I have a commitment.
Please ask another member for help.
Let's go, Tomoko!
Okay!
She's been suspended until the board meeting.
How do you think she'll be punished?
The rumors say 2 or 3 months suspension...
She's the daughter of a celebrity who gave the school an endowment.
So the school will want to be careful...
Oh, don't give me that nonsense!
Just hold the meeting and expel her now!
Won't you all be quiet? My wound is hurting.
Oh! Sorry!
Does it hurt really bad?
Yes, of course.
Hello? Sorry to bother you.
But I've been waiting for you to call back all this time.
I don't want to disturb your work but,
...but something awful happened concerning Mariko...
Hello?
I'm terribly sorry... your husband just left.
I'm very sorry.
I'm sorry...
...Mariko!?
Mariko! It must be Mariko!
It's you...
Hisako! What happened... to Mariko?
Dear! Dear!
I don't know what I'd do if my parents...
Unlike yours, mine aren't really that close, you know.
Let's go to the harbor.
Ok.
My dear Brother...
Right now, I'm wondering,
...how is she feeling, alone and crying somewhere...
Mariko-san, who is helpless to do anything about all this.
Loving both her parents, she doesn't know what to do.
My dear Brother...
...just because it is a matter of love between adults,
...we mustn't get involved?
2 hotdogs and 2 cups of soup, please...
Thank you!
Here, have some. You must be hungry.
I don't eat stuff like that.
Ok, I'll eat both.
Mm! Not bad. It's good!
It's not the best, but it's warm, and good enough for now...
Don't talk with your mouth full, barbarian.
Ooh... this mustard is hot!
What? Did you say something?
Never mind!
Hey, I'm not asking you,
...I'm asking your stomach!
That's good. Your stomach is honest.
Here you are.
So, where to now?
We zoomed around the freeway like crazy,
...and climbed up the observatory at the harbor,
...so we could go to Chinatown, or the foreign cemeteries...
Just say where, and we'll go there.
Yes. She finally calmed down a bit.
That's right, she wanted to drive, so we drove around.
Yes, we went pretty far, but now we're back at the harbor.
We had a light snack, and now she's dozing.
She insisted I not call anyone, so I sneaked out when she nodded off.
Yes, that's right.
By the way, was the girl badly injured?
She's worried about that, and starts panicking when she thinks of it...
Ok. I'll watch her a bit more, then bring her home.
So, tell her family not to worry.
Oh good, both of you can relax...
Ichinomiya-san is with her.
What's the matter, Nanako?
I'm so relieved and exhausted.
I am too... I'm... I'm very relieved. Thank you very much, both of you.
Dear...
It's okay, it's lit. But, thank you...
That night,
...Mariko-san returned shortly after 8 o'clock.
Mariko!
Mariko-san!
Welcome home!
Mariko!
I'll be leaving...
Thank you for all you've done.
Thank you so much.
I can stay here with you tonight.
I'd like to, too!
Thank you! Please, I'd like that... Please.
Ok. Let's play a card game before we go to bed.
But, first I have something to do...
What's that?
Mariko...
Everything's okay. Try not to worry.
We went to visit Misaki-san at her home.
She wasn't seriously hurt... it's nothing serious.
Why are you here?
After abandoning my mother and I... Why are you here?
Mariko!
It's none of your business anymore what I do.
Whether I attack my classmates, or kill somebody...
Don't try to be nice and pretend to be my father.
Mariko!
Go back to that woman!
Why don't you scold me!
Why do you keep forgiving him?
Everybody is lying! This house is filled with lies!
The fact I was born is a lie.
My own existence right now, is a lie!
I should just disappear! I want to disappear!
I... I hate myself!
Nanako, come on, let's go.
No...
What?
I can't leave Mariko-san alone.
Nanako!
Mariko-san!
What is... what are you doing?
Aren't they pretty? I've been collecting them since I was little.
On birthdays or Christmas, I would fill the house with candles.
I wanted to spend time with my family and my holiday candles.
But... Papa was never here to share them.
Over and over, never able to be with us...
But... today... he's finally here. So...
What's today? What special day is today?
The last day.
What?
The last day!
No! Mariko-san!
Mariko-san!
What are you?!
Let go!
Don't!
What... are you doing?
I'd rather see it burned down! The whole house!
Go ahead, Mariko.
Burn everything down if you want.
Do whatever you want.
But... but listen to what I'm saying.
Whatever you do... and whatever happens... never hate yourself.
Don't treat yourself like dirt.
Without resorting to boasting or arrogance,
...you can find the good within you and love it always.
No! I hate myself! I hate me!
I'm selfish and irresponsible!
I hurt everyone around me, and no one cares about me!
It may seem to you that I'm a worthless man,
...and people who know me probably think I'm worthless,
...not taking care of my family, a job without prestige,
...and a life without any real direction.
But I believe even I have some good inside of me.
Maybe no one else notices it. I'm the only one that knows.
It's something for me to nurture and love in secret.
Do you know why?
Because you can't live without it.
Or rather, if you have only that much and nothing else, you can live.
If you can't love yourself, who will love you?
And if you don't love yourself, whom will you love?
Yes, you can. Because I love you in spite of everything, Papa!
Mariko!
Forgive me, Mariko!
Forgive me!
My dear Brother,
...what a wonderful Father, and loving Mother,
...and such an honest Mariko-san.
Each of them is such a great person.
Yet, in spite of that, their family is being destroyed.
Why is that, Brother?
How can that be?
I don't understand.
It's just too sad for me, and I can't understand.
As you all know,
...yesterday a shameful incident disgraced our school.
Last night we convened an emergency meeting of the senior members.
At this time, I'd like to make an announcement to all the members.
A decision was made unanimously by secret ballot,
...to expel Shinobu Mariko-san from the Sorority, effective yesterday.
Please state your objections now, if any...
That's not fair! That's too severe!
My dear Brother,
...I don't know what got into me.
Something inside forced me to jump up and start shouting.
This is too one-sided!
Why don't you listen to Shinobu-san's side of the story?
There must've been some reason for Shinobu-san to do what she did!
That's true. That's a reasonable point of view.
Continue, Misonoo-san. State your opinion.
But the decision is already made and it is absolute.
Please understand this, and then state your opinion.
As I said, the decision was based on the shameful facts.
The cause of her actions is irrelevant.
Please go ahead.
"Decision"? "Absolute"?
What kind of Sorority is this?
We are all students in the same school.
An "absolute decision"?
Decisions can't be forced on one student by another like this!
What authority justifies such a thing?
Watch what you say!
Do you know what you're talking about?
Quiet, please.
Everyone has a right to state her opinion.
Go on. Continue.
Then, I will leave the Sorority too!
Right here and now!
That... that is my "decision"!
My dear Brother, I... I left the Sorority!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
After Mariko's incident,
...Kaoru becomes convinced that the Sorority must be abolished.
When she confides to Saint-Juste her plan,
...Saint-Juste is shaken.
Each follow their own feelings.
The fated day of reckoning draws near.
Next episode: The Student Assembly
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...