My right hand holds a bowl of gold,
And my left holds one of silver.
Never one without the other,
Two unseen bowls for each of us.
The golden one is filled with joy,
shining warmly.
Since we met, my golden bowl
cannot hold all my happiness and love.
Golden joy, silver sadness,
I would leave my past behind...
For you, for the sake of love,
I would empty the bowls of my past.
Here's your dinner.
Aren't you going to eat?
Keep the hell out of my life!
I won't eat! Damn it!
Mariko!
The main clause, "I heard..." is in the past tense,
...and the subordinate clause is in the past tense also.
Then Ruland picked up the scythe and created with it a circular space,
...three or four yards in diameter, just for the insect.
Then he told Jupiter to let the string go, and come down from the tree.
Excuse me. My eraser...
Aren't we eating too much?
It's okay, we're growing, you know!
I just worry about growing sideways...
What's the matter?
Shinobu-san?
Yeah...
She's probably eating lunch alone somewhere. Who cares?
10. Mariko
What are you doing here?
Finished with lunch?
I will not eat!
I don't want anything.
Mariko, what do you want for dinner?
Nothing, like I said.
But it's been three days.
How about a steak?
With lots of French fries! Hm?
I told you I don't want anything!
Go away!
Mariko...
Don't you see how unhappy this makes me?
Please eat something. For my sake.
You are all that is precious in my life.
There isn't anything else for me.
Please, Mariko? Won't you?
"Please", "please"!
Can't you say anything but "please"?!
Get angry!
Being like that is what made my father... made him...
Go away!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Let's see... "confusion"...
What is the synonym of "confusion"?
That's odd...
A page is missing!
Geez, what am I doing with this cheap dictionary?
May I come in, Nanako?
Dad!
You've been studying so hard lately!
Yes, you know mid-terms are coming soon.
Here. A reward for you.
Great! An English-to-English dictionary!
So... "confusion"... "confusion"...
How did you know I needed a new dictionary?
He was watching you study in the living room the other day.
Oh! Thank you, Daddy.
Here's a dessert for you. Keep up the good work!
I made your favorite... apple pie!
Brother, dear brother...
I am surrounded by the warmth of my father's love, and my mother's too.
I realize how happy I am.
I don't think I care how they met.
But brother...
...I just don't understand about Mariko-san.
Call again!
Please. Please!
Nanako-san!
My first section is Physics, rats!
Mine is English.
Nanako, sheesh, you're really working hard!
Of course. I have a new dictionary!
Shinobu-san?
Mona-Lisa-no-Kimi!
Good morning!
Oh good! Fukiko-sama has a favor to ask of you both...
Fukiko-sama?
She wants us?
So! See you at lunch!
Could you bring flowers for the tea ceremony today,
From the College Union?
Flowers for a tea ceremony?
We will rely on your good taste.
Misonoo-san, you seem reluctant?
No!
If you would be so kind, then...
The Sorority holds a tea ceremony once a week.
Afterwards they discuss upcoming events and such...
These ceremonies are so important!
To think we'd be chosen to select the flowers!
What an honor it is! It's wonderful!
Don't you think so too?
Yeah...
About the other day...
Misonoo-san, I really...
A Tea Ceremony? What an elegant life!
So then? You two picked the flowers, right?
Yeah...
I was right about that birthday party.
Something happened, didn't it?
It's okay. If you can't talk about it...
Thanks.
I figured you'd be here.
Here's one for you.
So skinny! You're wasting your natural beauty.
Please leave me alone.
You're so pale.
You can't go on abusing your health this way.
Leave me alone.
What good is health? Who cares about health!
You don't care!
You're talking nonsense!
You wouldn't say that if you weren't still healthy.
Kaoru-no-Kimi...
...you just don't understand how I feel!
Can't you see just a little?
You've always been adored by so many... Can't you see?
Oh wow, I want a hug from Kaoru-no-Kimi too!
Hey, me too!
Me too!
All right, everybody!
Quiet down and get ready for sports.
Okay! okay!
Ok!
I'll get you warmed up!
You too, Misonoo-san.
Ok...
Ok! Are you ready to take a serve?
Oh, no... Her serve is so strong!
She's such an athlete!
Heads up! Go!
My nap was interrupted by your ball.
It figures, that it was you...
It's Saint-Juste-sama!
Saint-Juste-sama!
Rei, throw the ball back, already!
Why don't you come up instead of playing with this stupid ball.
The view from here is splendid.
Everything looks small and beautiful.
Even people.
Orihara Kaoru looks small too. From here.
Stop the nonsense, come down. I'll let you join us!
That would be a pleasure!
Saint Juste-sama!
Rei! Throw the ball!
Rei! Stop that!
She'll jump!
Saint-Juste...
Angel of Death.
Back with it, everyone. Don't bother with this lazybones!
Shinobu-san!
Help!
What happened?
Hurry! To the nurse's office!
Aren't you coming with us?
Yes.
I heard about her. My god!
Yes! And she's unconscious!
What!
And I can't reach her mother.
I'm going to go to her house.
Her mom might still be out.
I'll wait for her in front...
...it's best for her to be told in person, because of the shock.
Yes, good!
I want to help her as much as I can...
...because despite everything, she is my friend.
I'll take your bag home for you.
Thank you! That will help.
Darling...
What? Hospitalized?
Orihara-san just called to tell me...
She needs to stay in the hospital for a couple of days.
Yes, it's not that serious.
They say it's anemia and malnutrition.
Malnutrition?
Did you talk to her mother yet?
Not yet.
Stupid.
Stupid girl.
Abusing her precious life like that...
These kids... how could they?
Shinobu-san suffering from malnutrition?
Malnutrition? How could that happen?
Misonoo-san! You've come!
Thank you thank you!
Excuse me but... Mariko-san has fainted!
Mariko... fainted!?
What! Mariko stopped eating because of me?
She won't eat until you forgive her...
Not even a bite.
No more than a sip of tea.
Oh, no... Oh no!
That was Shinobu-san asking for... forgiveness.
She wanted to wait as long as it took until you forgave her...
...of your own accord.
That girl!
I didn't know. I had no idea!
There was nothing I could do.
I'd made up my mind to force her to eat something today.
She probably was hoping I would. I finally realized that.
Brother, brother!
Mariko-san... Mariko-san was...
It was all because of me... I...
Kaoru-no-Kimi...
You've stayed with me all this time?
Your mother will be here soon, Misonoo-san, too.
Just like I figured.
No. I didn't...
Nevermind. Put an end to this foolishness.
Mariko?
How are you? Are you really all right?
Mariko, Nanako-san is here.
How do you feel?
What? I don't need you. I have a lot of friends.
Well, I'll be leaving now.
Bye!
See, I missed saying goodbye to Kaoru-no-Kimi, because of you!
Damn... as for you, you aren't my only friend!
Really, I swear!
My life is completely full... of so many friends!
My dear brother...
To forgive her, or not to forgive her...
Who am I to be so judgmental or presumptuous?
The school called my publishing company...
Thank you, dear.
Mariko-san is facing loneliness, and her own self, head on.
If it were me, I'd try to ignore it or try to avoid it...
She's 16, same as me.
She's a 16-year old hero.
Bravo!
I dreamed I was chasing a rainbow...
Then the rainbow I was chasing was you.
Before, I had no strength, no will.
But now because of you, I do.
Feelings of love, like raindrops
Come pouring from the sky.
This is surely a game
Of some mischievous fairy...
Always dancing,
Always capricious...
While waiting for Fukiko in a heavy rainstorm under an elm tree...
Rei gets a high fever and collapses.
When Nanako takes Rei to her apartment,
...she is shocked to find the room filled with mirrors!
Next episode: Under the Elm Tree
Brother, Dear Brother... There is no end to my tears...